RedOne!
Oh
Let's go to the beach, each
Let's go get away
They say, what they gonna say?
Have a drink, click, found the bud light
Bad b-tches like me, is hard to come by!
The patron own, let's go get it on
The zone own, yes i'm in the zone
Is it two, three? leave a good tip
I'mma blow off my money and don't give too quick
I'm on the floor, floor
I love to dance
So give me more, more, till I can stand
Get on the floor, floor
Like it's your last dance
If you want more, more
Then here I am
Starships were meant to flyyyy
Hands up and touch the skyyyy!
Can't stop 'cause we’re so hiiigh
Let's do this one more time
Starships were meant to flyyyy
Hands up and touch the skyyyy
Let's do this one last tiiiime
Hands up...
(we're higher than a motherf-ck-r)
Bump in my hootie hottie hottie hoop
I own that
And I ain't paying my rent this month
I owe that
But f-ck who you want, and f-ck who you like
Dance how a life there's no end inside
Twinkle, twinkle little star
Now everybody let me hear you say ray ray ray
Now spend all your money cause they pay pay pay
And if you're a cheat, you a chea-chea-cheat
My name is a n-gga, you can call me Nicki
Get on the floor, floor
Like a chola's dance
If you want more, more
Then here I am
Starships were meant to flyyyy
Hands up and touch the skyyyy
Can't stop 'cause we’re so hiiiigh
Let's do this one more time
Starships were meant to flyyyy
Hands up and touch the skyyyy
Let's do this one last tiiiime
Hands up...
(we're higher than a motherf-ck-r)
Starships were meant to flyyyy
Hands up and touch the skyyyy
Can't stop 'cause we’re so hiiiigh
Let's do this one more time!
Starships were meant to flyyyy
Hands up and touch the skyyyy
Let's do this one last tiiiime
Hands up...
(we're higher than a motherf-ck-r)