If I was your boyfriend
I'd never let you go
I can take you places you ain't never been before
Baby take a chance or you'll never ever know
I got money in my hands that I'd really like to blow
Swag swag swag, on you
Chillin by the fire why we eatin' fondue
I dunno about me but I know about you
So say hello to falsetto in three two
I'd...
Nhacso Lyrics
If I was your boyfriend
I'd never let you go
I can take you places you ain't never been before
Baby take a chance or you'll never ever know
I got money in my hands that I'd really like to blow
Swag swag swag, on you
Chillin by the fire why we eatin' fondue
I dunno about me but I know about you
So say hello to falsetto in three two
I'd like to be everything you want
Hey girl, let me talk to you
If I was your boyfriend
never let you go
Keep you on my arm girl
you'd never be alone
I can be a gentleman
anything you want
If I was your boyfriend
I'd never let you go
Tell me what you like yeah tell me what you don't
I could be your Buzz Lightyear fly across the globe
I don't never wanna fight yeah, you already know
I am 'ma a make you shine bright like
you're laying in the snow
Burr
Girlfriend, girlfriend, you could be my girlfriend
You could be my girlfriend until the ---- world ends
Make you dance do a spin and a twirl and
Voice goin crazy on this hook like a whirl wind
Swaggie
I'd like to be everything you want
Hey girl, let me talk to you
If I was your boyfriend
never let you go
Keep you on my arm girl
you'd never be alone
I can be a gentleman
anything you want
If I was your boyfriend
I'd never let you go
So give me a chance
'cause you're all I need girl
Spend a week wit your boy I'll be calling you my girlfriend
If I was your man
I'd never leave you girl
I just want to love you, and treat you right
If I was your boyfriend
never let you go
Keep you on my arm girl
you'd never be alone
I can be a gentleman
anything you want
If I was your boyfriend
I'd never let you go
never let you go
If I was your boyfriend