Bori, bori, bori, aha!
Ehhh, historico
Ole, ole
Don y yandel
Ole, ole, (quien!?) ole, ole, J.lo!
Ole, ole
Baby, the way that I'm working my body
Can tell that you already like it
I make you lose your cabeza, go loca
Baby we don't even need any music
Cause we make the beat when we moving
You know that it's making me hot, hot
We belong to the night, we belong to the music
So let's live in the moment of freedom that will get you wild
Let's ignite this fire up, across the world we take it up
Let me hear you screaming out loud
When I say go,
When I say viva
We'll take it low
Let's lose control
When I say go
We'll get it louder
Let's make it blow
Let's lose control
Siente el ritmo
Follow the leader
I wanna see ya
Ando buscando una latina
Creo que la encontre
Yo y ella hicimos un clip
Regia, pelo largo
Christian dior con cartera Gucci, bella, bien chic
Los lideres con la diva, combinacion nociva
Se juntaron los bori, Creando otro hit
Damas y caballeros suban las manos arriba
Sigan instrucciones, Cero presiones
Que fluyan tus emociones
Y dejate llevar por el hit
Ahora falta que se vaya
Dale restrella
Mami pa pasarte de la raya
Tu eres la dura dura, tu tienes agallas
Robame un beso
Apunta y no falla
Let’s ignite this fire up
Across the world we take it up
Let me hear you screaming out loud
When I say go
When I say viva
We’ll take it low
Let’s lose control
When I say go
We’ll get it louder
Let’s make it blow
Let’s lose control
Siente el ritmo
Follow the leader
I wanna see ya
Chequea como la leyenda viviente lo hace
Mami me gusta cuando me provocas
Tu pelo, tu piel y tu boca
Te mueves de pies a cabeza
Como loca
Dicen que la musica sigue y no para
Yo la mire directo a la cara
Y le dije que me siento hot, hot, hot
Soltura, Negrita dale hasta el suelo
Mucho calor
Sudandote el cuello
So paid attention to me cause now I'm the teacher
When I’m on the floor my hips are recharged
So follow the moment and just let it got you (Se siente caliente)
Mi gente sexy let me hear some yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah…
Ole, Ole
When I say go
When I say viva
We’ll take it low
Let’s lose control
When I say go
We’ll get it louder
Let’s make it blow
Let’s lose control
Siente el ritmo
Follow the leader
I wanna see ya
Dj SiRiPaLa  m/