I’m at a payphone trying to call home
All of my change I spent on you
Where have the times gone
Baby, it’s all wrong
Where are the plans we made for two?
Yeah, I, I know it’s hard to remember
The people we used to be
It’s even harder to picture
That you’re not here next to me
You said it’s too late to make it
But is it too late to try?
And in our time that you wasted
All of our bridges burned down
I’ve wasted my nights
You turned out the lights
Now I’m paralyzed
Still stuck in that time
When we called it love
But even the sun sets in paradise
I’m at a payphone trying to call home
All of my change I spent on you
Where have the times gone
Baby, it’s all wrong
Where are the plans we made for two?
If happy ever after did exist
I would still be holding you like this
And all those fairy tales are full of shit
One more fucking love song, I’ll be sick
Oh you turned your back on tomorrow
‘Cause you forgot yesterday
I gave you my love to borrow
But you just gave it away
You can’t expect me to be fine
I don’t expect you to care
I know I’ve said it before
But all of our bridges burned down
I’ve wasted my nights
You turned out the lights
Now I’m paralyzed
Still stuck in that time
When we called it love
But even the sun sets in paradise
I’m at a payphone trying to call home
All of my change I spent on you
Where have the times gone
Baby, it’s all wrong
Where are the plans we made for two?
If happy ever after did exist
I would still be holding you like this
And all those fairy tales are full of shit
One more fucking love song, I’ll be sick
Now I’m at a payphone.....
Man fuck that shit
I’ll be out spending all this money
While you’re sitting round wondering
Why it wasn’t you who came up from nothing
Made it from the botton, now when you see me I’m stunning
And all of my cars start with a push of a button
Telling me the chances I blew up or whatever you call it
Switch the number to my phone so you never could call it
Don’t need my name on my show, you can tell it I’m ballin’
Swish, what a shame could have got picked
Had a really good game but you missed your last shot
So you talk about who you see at the top
Or what you could have saw
But sad to say it’s over for
Phantom pulled up valet open doors
Wiz like go away, got what you was looking for
Now it’s me who they want
So you can go and take that little piece of shit with you
I’m at a payphone trying to call home
All of my change I spent on you
Where have the times gone
Baby, it’s all wrong
Where are the plans we made for two?
If happy ever after did exist
I would still be holding you like this
And all those fairy tales are full of shit
One more fucking love song, I’ll be sick
Now I’m at a payphone.....