There's a place that i know
It's not pretty there and few have ever gone
If i show it to you now
Will it make you run away
Or will you stay
Even if it hurts
Even if i try to push you out
Will you return?
And remind me who i really am
Please remind me who i really am
Everybody's got a dark side
Do you love me?
Can you love mine?
Nobody's a picture perfect
But we're worth it
You know that we're worth it
Will you love me?
Even with my dark side?
Like a diamond
From black dust
It's hard to know
It can become
A few give up
So don't give up on me
Please remind me who i really am
Everybody's got a dark side
Do you love me?
Can you love mine?
Nobody's a picture perfect
But we're worth it
You know that we're worth it
Will you love me?
Even with my dark side?
Don't run away
Just tell me that you will stay
Promise me you will stay
Don't run away
Just promise me you will stay
Promise me you will stay
Will you love me? oh
Everybody's got a dark side
Do you love me?
Can you love mine?
Nobody's a picture perfect
But we're worth it
You know that we're worth it
Will you love me?
Even with my dark side?
Don't run away, don't run away
Don't run away, promise you will stay...