You-u-u-u-u-u got me good
I-i-i-i-i-i-i
You-u-u-u-u-u
I like this right here.
Word on the street is that you're single
So, so baby have you heard my single?
It goes la di-da and it hits like a symbol
I drew a heart with my finger on your window.
What's up?
Even with your hair up
Girl, what's up?
Even in your sweat pants
Even when you wake up without any make-up, I'm in love.
Cause I'm
So tired of the same old things
I'ma need something new in my life, yeah.
So tired of the same old games
Yeah it's my time I start feeling right.
Cause you-u-u-u-u-u, got me good girl
I-i-i-i-i-i-i felt so good girl.
Youuuuuuuu, got me good
And you know that I need you so bad!
You said you're talking to your ex-boy
Well, well just remember he's your ex-boy (ugh)
Well maybe I could be your next boy.
And just remember that you're better than the rest.
So baby, what's up?
Even in your work clothes
Girl, what's up?
You know how to wear clothes
Girl, you got me lost in your eyes, I'm in paradise
What's up!
What's up?
Cause I'm
So tired of the same old things
I'ma need something new in my life, yeah.
So tired of the same old games
Yeah it's my time I start feeling right.
Cause you-u-u-u-u-u, got me good girl
I-i-i-i-i-i-i felt so good girl
Youuuuuuuu, got me good
And you know that I need you so bad!
I wanna know what it feels like,
To run my fingers through you hair!
I wanna know what drives you wild,
Cause baby we could drive it there.
Tell me that I'm dreaming
No, I don't wanna wake up x2
U-uuuuh.
So tired of the same old things
I'ma need something new in my life.
So tired of the same old games
Think it's my time I start feeling right.
Think I'm in love
Cause you-u-u-u-u-u, got me good girl
I-i-i-i-i-i-i felt so good girl
You-u-u-u-u-u-u, got me good
And you know that I need you so bad!
cause you-u-u-u-u-u, got me good girl
I-i-i-i-i-i-i felt so good girl
You-u-u-u-u-u-u, got me good
And you know that I need you so bad!
So bad, so bad