Usher, baby
Yeah
We did it again
And this time I'mma make you scream
USHER! Yeah, man...
I see you over there, so hypnotic
Thinking 'bout what I do to that body
I get you like
ooh baby baby ooh baby baby
ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby baby
Got no drink in my hand
But I'm wasted
Getting drunk of the thought of you naked
I get you like
Ooh baby baby-ooh baby baby
ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby baby
And I ain't trying to fight it, to fight it
But you're so magnetic, magnetic
Got one life, just live it, just live it
Now relax, sing it on your back
If you wanna scream, yeah
Let me know and I'll take you there
Get you going like
Ah-ooh-ooh Baby baby ooh baby baby
Ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby
If you wanna turn right
Hope you're ready to go all night
Get you going like
ah-ooh Baby baby ooh baby baby
Ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby
If you wanna scream
Yeah, come on
Kill the lights, shut 'em off
You're electric
Devil eyes telling me come and get it
I have you like
ooh Baby baby ooh baby baby
Ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby baby
Girl tonight you're the prey
I'm the hunter
Take you here, take you there
Take you wonder
Imagine me whispering in your ear
Then I wanna, take off your clothes and put something on ya
And I ain't trying to fight it, to fight it
But you're so magnetic, magnetic
Got one life, just live it, just live it
Now relax, sing it on your back
If you wanna scream, yeah
Let me know and I'll take you there
Get you going like
oh-ooh Baby baby ooh baby baby
Ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby
If you wanna turn right
Hope you're ready to go all night
Get you going like
oh-ooh Baby baby ooh baby baby
Ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby
If you wanna scream
Out, louder, scream louder
Louder, louder, louder....
Hey, tonight I scream, I'm on need
0hhh...
If you wanna scream
YEAH
Let me know and I'll take you there
Get you going like
ooh-ooh Baby baby ooh baby baby
ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby
If you wanna turn right
Hope you're ready to go all night
Get you going like
ah-ooh Baby baby ooh baby baby
Ah-ooh baby baby ooh baby
If you wanna scream