You and I go hard, at each other like we going to war
You and I go rough, we keep throwing things and slamming the doors
You and I get sore, then dysfunctional we stuck keeping score
You and I get sick, they all know that we can't do this no more
But baby there you again, there you again making me love you
Yeah I stopped using my head, using my head let it all go
Got you stuck on my body, on my body like a tattoo
And now i'm feeling stupid, feeling stupid crawling back to you
So I cross my heart, and I hope to die,
that i'll only stay with you one more night
And I know i've said it a million times
But i'll only stay with you one more night
Trying to tell you no, but my body keeps on telling you yes
Trying to tell you stop, but your lipstick got me so out of breath
I'd be waking up, in the morning probably hating myself
And i'd be waking up, feeling sastified but guilty as hell
But baby there you again, there you again making me love you
Yeah I stopped using my head, using my head let it all go
Got you stuck on my body, on my body like a tattoo
And now i'm feeling stupid, feeling stupid crawling back to you
So I cross my heart, and I hope to die,
that i'll only stay with you one more night
And I know i've said it a million times
But i'll only stay with you one more night
Yeah baby give me one more night
But baby there you again, there you again making me love you
Yeah I stopped using my head, using my head let it all go
Got you stuck on my body, on my body like a tattoo
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
So I cross my heart, and I hope to die,
that i'll only stay with you one more night
And I know i've said it a million times
But i'll only stay with you one more night
(yeah baby give me one more night)
So I cross my heart, and I hope to die,
that i'll only stay with you one more night
And I know i've said it a million times
But i'll only stay with you one more night
(I don't know, whatever...)