Love me like
Love-love-love-love me like money
The Wonder Girls and
Akon
Love you like, love you like
Listen to me now
My heart is screamin’ out
I’m tryin’ to show you how to touch me
I’m not just a girl
I’m more precious than pearls and
I deserve all you got baby
So, if you’re gonna hold me
Baby, don’t let go of me
Give me all of you got I want everything
My heart is a treasure
One that can’t be measured
Let me teach you how to love me
Love me like money
Love me like cars
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Love me up close
Love me from a far
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Love me like money
Love me like cars
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Hold me like diamonds
Treat me like a star
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Stop listenin’ to your friends
They just want your man
Misery loves a little company
Don’t feed into them lies
Want you by my side
Why is it so hard to trust me?
Let go of ya fears girl
Promise I’ll be here girl
I won’t let ya heart skip a beat
I’ll take care of you
If you take care of me girl
Won’t ever leave you lonely?
Love you like money
Love you like cars
Love you babe, love you babe
Wherever you are
Love you up close
Love you from a far
Love you babe, love you babe
Wherever you are
Love you like money
Love you like cars
Love you babe, love you babe
Wherever you are
Hold you like diamonds
Treat you like a star
Love you babe, love you babe
Wherever you are
Look boy, I been through some things
Seen a little sunshine seen a little rain
My hearts been through some pain
And I don’t wanna go back through it again
So, I’m lettin’ you know upfront
If you plan on being in the one
Listen to my instructions
‘Cause Imma teach you how to love
(Love you like, love you like)
100 dollars bills
Brand new wheels
(Love me like, love me like)
A fresh new hair cut boy, I need you to
(Love you like, love you like)
New pair of kicks
Ice on ya risk
(Love me like, love me like)
Oh~
Love me like money
Love me like cars
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Love me up close
Love me from a far
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Love me like money
Love me like cars
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Hold me like diamonds
Treat me like a star
Love me babe, love me babe
Wherever you are
Love me babe