Get get get in line and settle down
Get in line and settle down
What's your twenty? (Do you copy?)
Where's your brain? (Do you copy?)
Checking in to check you out
Concerned about your whereabouts
Copy that (Do you copy?)
you're acting strange (Do you copy?)
So tell me what is going on
So heavy I bet
I'm fine
(and nothing's gonna knock this girl down)
I'm feeling positive for real, i'm all good no
I'm fine
(and nothing's gonna knock this girl down)
It's gotten complicated that's for sure
But you can see it my eyes,
you can read it on my lips
I'm trying to get a hold on this
I really mean it this time
And you know it's such a trip
Don't get me started
I'm trying to get a hold on this
Get get get in line, and settle down
G-G-G-Get in line, and settle down
No big deal (I can handle it)
It'll bounce off me (I can handle it)
Being around, moved block before,
doesn't matter anymore
Here we go again, (are you kiddin' me?)
Are you insane?(are you kiddin' me?)
We're underneath the avalanche so heavy again
I'm fine
(and nothing's gonna knock this girl down)
I'm feeling positive for real, i'm all good no
I'm fine
(and nothing's gonna knock this girl down)
It's gotten complicated that's for sure
But you can see it my eyes,
you can read it on my lips
I'm trying to get a hold on this
And I really mean it this time
And you know it's such a trip
Don't get me started
I'm trying to get a hold on this
Get get get in line, and settle down
Get in line, and settle down
.....
I'm a rough and tough, i'm a rough and tough
And nothing's gonna knock this girl down
But you can see it my eyes
you can read it on my lips
I'm trying to get a hold on this
And I really mean it this time
And you know it's such a trip
Don't get me started
I'm trying to get a hold on this
Gotta get a hold on this
Trying to get a hold on this
(Don't get me started)
Gotta get a hold on this
Get get get in line, and settle down
Get in line, and settle down
Get...
In line and settle down
lyrics synched by. SantiMe
Get...
Get..