Woah-oh-oh-oh
It's always a good time
Woke up on the right side of the bed
What's up with this Prince song inside my head?
Hands up if you're down to get down tonight
Cuz it's always a good time.
Slept in all my clothes like I didn't care
Hopped into a cab, take me anywhere
I'm in if you're down to get down tonight
Cuz it's always a good time
Good morning and good night
I wake up at twilight
It's gonna be alright
We don't even have to try
It's always a good time
Woah-oh-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh-oh
We don't even have to try, it's always a good time.
Feet down dropped my phone in the pool again
Checked out of my room hit the ATM
Let's hang out if you're down to get down tonight
Cuz it's always a good time
Good morning and good night
I wake up at twilight
It's gonna be alright we don't even have to try
It's always a good time.
Woah-oh-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh-oh
It's always a good time
We don't even have to try, it's always a good time.
Woah-oh-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh-oh
It's always a good time
We don't even have to try, it's always a good time.
Doesn't matter when
It's always a good time then
Doesn't matter where
It's always a good time there
Doesn't matter when,
It's always a good time then
It's always a good time
Woah-oh-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh-oh
We don't even have to try, it's always a good time
It's always a good time
Woah-oh-oh-oh Woah-oh-oh-oh
We don't even have to try, it's always a good time.
by hakz
hafizridha.com