Tonight,
Feels like we can do anything we like, oh,
I'm goin' in (Put your, put your hands up)
I'm goin' in in in in in.
Put your, put your hands up
It's 'go' time, press my button yeah blow the stage, grenade,
Oh my, tonight we gon' ring the tank, bananas,
No hold, there ain't no stopping us tonight,
I'm on my crazy, she on a crazy, we on this crazy,
We are amazing.
Tonight,
Feels like we can do anything we like, oh,
I'm goin' in (Put your, put your hands up)
I'm goin' in in in in in.
Put your, put your hands up
Take it to the head,
Take it off the edge,
Nothing but the best,
Feeling like a million,
million people everywhere,
Put it in the air,
We don't give a damn,
Feeling like a billion, billion.
No hold,
there ain't no stopping us tonight,
I'm on my crazy,
she on a crazy,
we on this crazy,
We are amazing.
Tonight,
Feels like, we can do anything we like, oh,
I'm goin' in (Put your, put your hands up)
I'm goin' in in in in in.
Put your, put your hands up
Hey you hands on the ceiling,
Nobody move, nobody get shot,
Lip pounds on me,
I love it how a mami went around on me,
So I never get enough of yelling, ven aquí,
Officer on duty, J.Lo what they call her,
Take me to jail, cause I wanna be your robber,
Put me in a cell if you really need to holler,
Put me in a cell feed down flo rida, hey,
To the sky, put your hands on rock,
Plus nobody telling please that the club is mi casa,
So they wanna freak, on the way you call papa,
Gotta make them sing high notes like Oprah,
When the ego, I got four leo,
Even the DJ, wanna rep Puerto Rico,
Got it on replay, like you just broke a needle,
Whatever that he say, better listen up people.
Tonight,
Feels like,
I'm goin' in (Put your, put your hands up)
I'm goin' in... Hey!