Oh, oh, oh
Come fill my glass up a little more
We ’bout to get hot, and burn this floor
You know we getting hotter and hotter
Sexy and hotter, let’s shut it down
Doe, what I gotta do to show these girls that I own ‘em
Some call me Nicki, and some call me Roman
Exkeeza, pleeza, I’m in a visa
….my own sneaker
Sexy, sexy that’s all I do
If you need a bad b!tch
Let me call a few
Come zoom in the middle, many skirts is up
I see some good girls, I’mma turn ‘em out
Ok bottle, sip, bottle, dozzle
I’m a bad b!tch, no mussel, hey?
Bottle, sip, bottle, dozzle
I’m a bad b!tch, no mussel, let’s go
Music...Makes Me...Hot!
Oh, oh, oh
Come fill my glass up a little more
We ’bout to get hot, and burn this floor
You know we getting hotter and hotter
Sexy and hotter, let’s shut it down
Pound the alarm!
I wanna do it for the night, night
So get me now, and knock this over
I wanna do it like you like, like
Come get me, baby we’re not getting younger
I just want you tonight, night
Baby we won’t do it for life, life
Music...Makes Me...Hot!!
Oh, oh, oh
Come fill my glass up a little more
We ’bout to get hot, and burn this floor
You know we getting hotter, and hotter
Sexy and hotter, let’s shut it down
Pound the alarm!
Oh, oh, oh
Come fill my glass up a little more
We ’bout to get hot, and burn this floor
You know we getting hotter, and hotter
Sexy and hotter, let’s shut it down
Pound the alarm!