As long as you love me
I'm under pressure,
Seven billion people in the world trying to fit in
Keep it together,
Smile on your face even though your heart is frowning
But hey now, you know girl,
We both know it's a cruel world
But I will take my chances
As long as you love me
We could be starving, we could be homeless, we could be broke
I'll be your platinum, I'll be your silver, I'll be your gold
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
I'll be your soldier
fighting every second of the day for your dreams girl
I'll be your whole world
You can be my Destiny's Child on the scene girl
So don't stress, don't cry, we don't need no wings to fly
Just take my hand
As you love me we could be starving
we could be homeless, we could be broke
As long as you love me
I'll be your platinum, I'll be your silver, I'll be your gold
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
[Big Sean]
I don't know if this makes sense, but you're my hallelujah
Give me a time and place, and I'll rendezvous, and I'll fly you to it,
I'll beat ya there
Girl you know I got you
Us, trust...
A couple of things I can't spell without you
Now we are on top of the world, 'cause that's just how we do
Used to tell me sky's the limit, now the sky's our point of view
Man now we stepping out like wow (Oh God)
Camera's pointed shoot,
Ask me what's my best side, I stand back and point at you
You, you the one that I argue with
I feel like I need a new girl to be bothered with,
But the grass ain't always greener on the other side,
It's green where you water it
So I know we got issues baby true true true
But I'd rather work on this with you
Than to go ahead and start with someone new
As long as you love me
We could be starving, we could be homeless, we could be broke
I'll be your platinum, I'll be your silver, I'll be your gold
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
love me
As long as you lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo
As long as you love me