I know it ain't fair
The only ball I drop
New Years', Times Square,
The world is mine
Sixth Sense
I see the seven signs
Now baby,
Let's get started for life
Everytime I look into your eyes
(Mr Worldwide)
I feel like I could stare in them for a lifetime
We can get started for life
Tonight
For life
We can get started for life
Tonight
For life
tonight
We can get started
You know it feels right
Big news, Pitbull
All lit up like a December night,
Tom Cruise, Mumbai
Like the 4th of July, Vanilla Sky
Thrilla in Manilla
Knockin' 'em out like Pacquiao
New Ali, new Frazier
But for now it's off to Malaysia
Two passports, three cities, two countries, one day
Now that's worldwide,
If you think it's a game let's play !Dale¡
Everytime I look into your eyes
I feel like I could stare in them for a lifetime
We can get started for life
Tonight
For life
We can get started for life
Tonight
For life
tonight
We can get started
You know it feels right
I am what they thought I'd never become,
I believed and became it,
Now I'm here to claim it
I hustle anything, you name it
I went from evictions to food stamps,
To back in work, what damn (?)
To a passport, flooded with stamps
Now slowly, everywhere I land
Two passports, three cities, two countries, one day
Now that's worldwide,
If you think it's a game let's play !Dale¡
Cause if it feels right, we shouldn't waste any more time,
Let's get it started, don't think about it
You know I'm gonna make it alright, alright
Cause if it feels right,
You know I've made up my mind
Let's get it started, don't think about it
I know that we can make it alright alright
Everytime I look into your eyes
I feel like I could stare in them for a lifetime
We can get started for life
Tonight
For life
We can get started for life
Tonight
For life
tonight
We can get started
Don't start what you can't finish
You know it feels right
Let's go
____________________
Shakira ft Pitbull