Four letter word
But I don't have the guts to say it
Smile til it hurts
Lets not make it complicated
Weve got a story
But I'm about to change the ending
You're perfect for me
You're more than just a friend so we can just stop pretending now
Gotta let you know somehow
I'll be your shelter
I'll be your storm
I'll make you shiver
I'll keep you warm
Whatever weather
Well baby I'm yours
I'll be your forever, Be your fling
Baby I will be your everything
That we would always stay together
But whos to say
We could never last forever
Girl, got a question
Could you see yourself with somebody else?
Cause I'm on a mission
I don't wanna share I want you all to myself right now
I just wanna scream it out
I'll be your shelter
I'll be your storm
I'll make you shiver
I'll keep you warm
Whatever weather
Well baby I'm yours
I'll be your forever, Be your fling
Baby I will be your everything
No matter what you do
I'll be there for you
Every time you close your eyes
I will be by your side
Want you to wear my ring Wont you tell me I'm your everything
I'll be your shelter
I'll be your storm
I'll make you shiver
I'll keep you warm
Whatever weather
Well baby I'm yours
I'll be your forever, Be your fling
Baby I will be your everything