Yeah, You could be the greatest
You can be the best
You can be the king kong banging on your chest
You could beat the world
You could beat the war
You could talk to God, go banging on his door
You can throw your hands up
You can be the clock
You can move a mountain
You can break rocks
You can be a master
Don’t wait for luck
Dedicate yourself and you can find yourself
Standing in the hall of fame
And the world’s gonna know your name
Cause you burn with the brightest flame
And you’ll be on the walls of the hall of fame
You could go the distance
You could run the mile
You could walk straight through hell with a smile
You could be the hero
You could get the gold
Breaking all the records that thought never could be broke
Do it for your people
Do it for your pride
Never gonna know if you never even try
Do it for your country
Do it for you name
Cause there’s gonna be a day
When your,
Standing in the hall of fame
And the world’s gonna know your name
Cause you burn with the brightest flame
And you’ll be on the walls of the hall of fame
Be a champion, Be a champion, Be a champion, Be a champion
On the walls of the hall of fame
Be students, Be teachers
Be politicians, Be preachers
Be believers, Be leaders
Be astronauts, Be champions
Be true seekers
Be students, Be teachers
Be politicians, Be preachers
Be believers, Be leaders
Be astronauts, Be champions
Standing in the hall of fame
And the world’s gonna know your name
Cause you burn with the brightest flame
And you’ll be on the walls of the hall of fame
You could be the greatest
You can be the best
You can be the king kong banging on your chest
You could beat the world
You could beat the war
You could talk to God, go banging on his door
You can throw your hands up
You can be the clock
You can move a mountain
You can break rocks
You can be a master
Don’t wait for luck
Dedicate yourself and you can find yourself
Standing in the hall of fame