These waters can get a little busy
But I got experience
Don't mind treking thru the storm
Long as I know that you're here with me baby
Shedding all your innocence
I see the walls are looking like they might precipitate
Until i'm in so deep, it's up to my waist
But I promise girl I ain't afraid
It's raining inside your bed
No parts are dry
Lovin makes you so wet, your legs, your thighs
And ever since we first met I knew that
I, I knew I was ready baby to take that dive
Can't help it, no
I want you to feel me
Every little bit of me baby
I don't need a life saver
Baby going deeper ain't gonna kill me
And I know they are shagging for me
I see the walls are looking like they might precipitate
Until i'm in so deep, it's up to my waist
But I promise girl I ain't afraid no no
It's raining inside your bed
No parts are dry
Lovin makes you so wet, your legs, your thighs
And ever since we first met I knew that
I, I knew I was ready baby to take that dive
I'll be inside when the tides are rolling baby
You'll be my place hide, all night all night babe
I'm not afraid to try
I knew i, don't mind playing in the rain
I was hoping that I get to take that dive
It's raining inside your bed (Its raining and I dont mind if Im fucking wet baby ohhh)
No parts are dry
Lovin makes you so wet, (so wet) your legs, your thighs
And ever since we first met I knew that
I, I knew I was ready baby to take that dive
ohhh ohhh howow hahoo that wil be baby