It's been a long time coming
since I've seen your face
And I've never went back trying to replace
Everything that I've had till my feet went numb
Praying like a fool that's been on a run
Heart's still beating but it's not working
It's like a million dollar phone
that you just can't ring
I reach out trying to love but I feel nothing
Yeah, my heart is numb
But with you
I feel again
Yeah with you
I can feel again
Yeah
Woo-hoo
Uuh.. Woo-hoo
(I Feel Again)
I'm feeling better ever
since you've known me
I was a lonely soul
but that's the old me
A long time coming since I've seen your face
I've never went back trying to replace
Everything that I broke till my feet went numb
Praying like a fool that just shot a gun
Heart's still beating but it's not working
It's like a hundred thousand voices that just can't sing
I reach out trying to love but I feel nothing
Oh my heart is numb
But with you
I feel again
Yeah with you
I can feel again
But with you
(I'm feeling better ever since you've known me)
I feel again
(I was a lonely soul but that's the old me)
Yeah with you
(I'm feeling better ever since you've known me)
I can feel again
(I was a lonely soul)
Wooooo-hoooooo
Uuh.. Woo-hoo
I'm feeling better ever since you've known me
I was a lonely soul, but that's the old me
I'm feeling better ever  since you know me
lyrics synched by. SantiMe
I'm feeling better ever since you've known me
I was a lonely soul, but that's the old me
A little wiser now but you show me
Yeah, I feel again
Feel again...