To all my friends,
The night is young
The music’s loud.
They’re playing our song
Nowhere else that I belong
Then here with you …
Oh oh oh ...
Ain’t felt this good since I remember
This night got started when you entered
I hope we can get a little closer
Maybe even get to know your name
I wanna hear the music so loud
Get some drinks inside me right now
So baby let it go
You had me at hello
Let’s raise your glass and toast
DJ plays that once more.
All my friends
This night is young
The music’s loud
They’re playing our song
Nowhere else that I belong
Then here with you …
Oh oh oh …
Gonna see the sun before you know it
If you got some money, time to blow it
Girl, way you got me feeling so sick
Dancing the night away with you,
With you , with you
Yeah nobody here is sober
Last call don’t mean it’s over, yeah
So baby let it go
You had me at hello
Let’s raise your glass and toast
All my friends
This night is young
The music’s loud
They’re playing our song
Nowhere else that I belong
Then here with you …
Oh oh oh …
I wanna hear the music so loud, yeah
(I wanna hear the music so loud)
All my friends
This night is young
The music’s loud
They’re playing our song
Nowhere else that I belong
Then here with you …