Turn around, open your eyes
Look at me now
Turn around, girl I’ve got you
We won’t fall down, yeah
We can see, forever from up here, yeah
So long as we’re together
Have no fear, no fear
So turn around, floating
So high you’re above the ground
Floating so high, turn around
Together, nothing can stop us now
Listen baby, turn around, floating
So high you’re above the ground
Floating so high, turn around
Together, nothing can stop us now
Turn around, turn around
Turn around, outa space we can go there now, yeah
Turn around, there’s no limit to what we found
Uh yeah
Music oh, I wanna feel it all, yeah
We’ll stay up, cause there’s no way for us
To fall, to fall
So turn around, floating
So high you’re above the ground
Floating so high, turn around
Together, nothing can stop us now
Listen baby, turn around, floating
So high you’re above the ground
Floating so high, turn around
Together, nothing can stop us now
Turn around, turn around
Uh baby, we’re so high now, whoa
Till our worries end our pain right now
Oh, oh, our home is the sky now
And we’re never coming down, down, down
So turn around, floating
So high you’re above the ground
Floating so high, turn around
Together, nothing can stop us now
Listen baby, turn around, floating
So high you’re above the ground
Floating so high, turn around
Together, nothing can stop us now
Turn around, turn around
nothing can stop us now