You drink more than you used to
Fell in love how could you
Trust your heart like only fools do
Go on let it bleed
You smoked ten now it's twenty
Bet you wish you never met me
To stick around you must be crazy
Go on let it bleed
I told you never to get used to me
I still awake when you fall asleep
I'm a whole lot of trouble
We're in a whole lot of trouble
I told you you should never follow me
But here we are, and you're into deep
I'm a whole lot of trouble
We're in a whole lot of trouble
You shout louder than you used to
And you hold on tighter in the bedroom
Stick around like i'mma change soon
Go on let it bleed
As you stand there trying to save me
Use your head and babe believe me
Gonna take much more than a heart to save me
Go on let it bleed
I told you never to get used to me
I still awake when you fall asleep
I'm a whole lot of trouble
We're in a whole lot of trouble
I told you you should never follow me
But here we are, and you're into deep
I'm a whole lot of trouble
We're in a whole lot of trouble