You caught me off guard, you know
Hey I'm wasting my judge
Don't know if you can hold me but,
I gotta honor it yeah
Depending on the minute and depending on the hours
I guess I got some time to waste so
We can chop away the hours, yeah
Cool so let's sing, and then let's walk
And then let's talk, and, and then, and then
Let's sing, and then less walking, and less talking
And we'll sing, yeah
Bring your car in the parking lot
And ride all night till you get a spot
Cause we ain't doing nothing
No we ain't doing nothing
Meet us in the parking lot
We're turn the speakers up
Cause we ain't doing nothing
We ain't doing nothing
Na-na-na-na-na
Le-le, ha-a-a-a-ha
Eh-eh-eh
Na-na-na-na-na
Le-le, ha-a-a-a-ha
Eh-eh-eh
I'm telling all my friends that it's pretty casual
They tryin'... what they see
Meanwhile I'm riding with you, with you
Depending on the minute and depending on the hours
Depending on the chemicals yeah we can make some power
Cool so let's sing, and then let's walk
And then let's talk, and, and then, and then
Bring your car in the parking lot
And ride all night till you get a spot
Cause we ain't doing nothing
No we ain't doing nothing
Meet us in the parking lot
We're turn the speakers up
Cause we ain't doing nothing
We ain't doing nothing
Na-na-na-na-na
Le-le, ha-a-a-a-ha
Eh-eh-eh
Na-na-na-na-na
Le-le, ha-a-a-a-ha
Eh-eh-eh
Hand in hand and arm in arm
Take me to your favorite barn
We can dance in the mud
It's slippery, show me all you buckery
Let's dance in the rain, keep dancing
Nothing unusual about it
You're just a regular guy, and there's no way around it
If you walk with me then we can talk about it
And if you want me talking let's see what we do about it
Bring your car in the parking lot
And ride all night till you get a spot
Cause we ain't doing nothing
No we ain't doing nothing
Meet us in the parking lot
We're turn the speakers up
Cause we ain't doing nothing
We ain't doing nothing