Hey girl I'm waitin on ya, I'm waitin on ya
Come on and let me sneak you out
And have a celebration, a celebration
The music up, the windows down
Yeah, we'll be doing what we do
Just pretending that we're cool
And we know it too
Yeah, we'll keep doing what we do
Just pretending that we're cool
So tonight
Let's go crazy, crazy, crazy till we see the sun
I know we only met but let's pretend its love
And never, never, never stop for anyone
Tonight let's get some
And live while we're young
Woooah wooah woooah oooh oh
Woooah wooah wooooah oooh oh
Tonight let's get some
And live while we're young
Hey girl it's now or never, it's now or never
Don't over-think just let itgo
And if we get together, g-get together
Don't let the pictures leave your phone
Yeah, we'll be doing what we do
Just pretending that we're cool
So tonight
Let's go crazy, crazy, crazy till we see the sun
I know we only met but let's pretend its love
And never, never, never stop for anyone
Tonight let's get some
And live while we're young
Woooah wooah woooah oooh oh
Woooah wooah wooooah oooh oh
Tonight let's get some
And live while we're young
And girl, you and I
We're bout to make some memories tonight
I wanna live while we're young
We wanna live while we're young
Let's go crazy, crazy, crazy till we see the sun
I know we only met but let's pretend its love
And never, never, never stop for anyone
Tonight let's get some
And live while we're young
Crazy, crazy, crazy till we see the sun
I know we only met but let's pretend its love
And never, never, never stop for anyone
Tonight let's get some
And live while we're young
Wanna live, wanna live, wanna live (while we're young)
Tonight let's get some
And live while we're young