Nhacso.net
Cause I'm so high right now...
(whoa oh...!)
I'm so high right now...
Somebody shot me
(eh!)
now I'm never gonna feel the same
it's really got me
(eh!)
and it's running off through my vein
And I can feel my heart star
beating out of time
and the room keeps
spinning in my mind
there's a smoke machine
inside my eyes
it's controlled long time ago
And all I know is that
either I'm in love or had
a little bit too much
cause I'm so high right now
either I'm in love
or you don't have to go...
Cause I'm so high right now...
(whoa oh...!)
I'm so high right now...
I'm so high right now
You make so high
so high I could fly
so good why ask why
Too much of you...
babe
I don't need another lifeline
oh! you feel so good yeah
loving you is like suicide
And I can feel my heart star
beating out of time
and the room keeps
spinning in my mind
there's a smoke machine
inside my eyes
it's controlled long time ago
And all I know is that
either I'm in love or had
a little bit too much
cause I'm so high right now
either I'm in love
or you don't have to go...
Cause I'm so high right now...
I'm so high right now
Either I'm in love or had
a little bit too much
cause I'm so high right now
either I'm in love
or you don't have to go...
Cause I'm so high right now...
(whoa oh...!)
I'm so high right now...
I'm so high right now