Nhacso.net
Yeah
Young Money
Nicki Minaj
Justin
Show you off
tonight I wanna show you off
What you got
a billion could've never bought
We gonna party like it's 3012 tonight
I wanna show you all the finer things in life
So just forget about the world, be young tonight
I'm coming for ya, i'm coming for ya
Cause all I need is a beauty and a beat
Who can make my life complete
It's all by you, when the music makes you move
Baby do it like you do
Cause...
Body rock, girl, I can feel your body rock
Take a bow, you on the hottest ticket now
We gonna party like it's 3012 tonight
I wanna show you all the finer things in life
So just forget about the world, be young tonight
I'm coming for ya, i'm coming for ya
Cause all I need is a beauty and a beat
Who can make my life complete
It's all by you, when the music makes you move
Baby do it like you do
In tongue, in lung, b-tches couldn't get on my ink crank
World tour, is mine, ten million letters, no big sign
Justin bieber, you know i'mma hit 'em with the ether
Guns out, weiner, but I gotta keep my eye out for Selena
Beauty, beauty and the beast
Beauty from the east, beauty from the precious of the priest
Beast, beauty from the streets, we don't get deceased
Everytime beauty want a beats
Body rock, girl, I can feel your body rock
Cause all I need is a beauty and a beat
Who can make my life complete
It's all by you, when the music makes you move
Baby do it like you do
Cause...