I went out last night
I'm going out tonight again
Anything to capture your attention
(your attention)
And she's a real sweet girl
And you know I got a boy
Details we both forgot to mention
(forgot to mention)
And you, I always know where you are
And you always know where I am
We're taking it way too far
But I don't want it to end
This kiss is something I can't resist
Your lips are undeniable
This kiss is something I can't risk
Your heart is unreliable
Something so sentimental
You make so detrimental
And I wish it didn't feel like this
Cause I don't wanna miss this kiss
I don't wanna miss this kiss
You know you're just my type
And your eyes are lock and key, to my heart
Tempting my confession
(my confession)
And you're a real hot thing
But you know i've got a boy somewhere
So can you feel the tension?
(Feel the tension)
And you, I'm dancing to where you are
And your dancing to where I am
We're taking it way too far
But I don't want it to end
This kiss is something I can't resist
Your lips are undeniable
This kiss is something I can't risk
Your heart is unreliable
Something so sentimental
You make so detrimental
And I wish it didn't feel like this
Cause I don't wanna miss this kiss
But if you ask me to
I couldn't, I couldn't, I
You're leaning closer and
I shouldn't, I shouldn't, I
But if you ask me to
I couldn't, I couldn't, I
I shouldn't, I shouldn't
I don't wanna miss this kiss
This kiss is something I can't resist
Your lips are undeniable
This kiss is something I can't risk
Your heart is unreliable
Something so sentimental
You make so detrimental
And I wish it didn't feel like this
Cause I don't wanna miss this kiss
I wish it didn't feel like this
I don't wanna miss this kiss