I cry many times at night
Think about you all the time
Your voice is on my mind it hurts so much inside
Even though we try and try
Break up to make up gets tired
Always mad at you, you’re mad at me, time to say goodbye
Our love ,Ain’t strong,
Couldn’t survive thru all these struggles
Couldn’t never last too many troubles
Can’t stand, the pain
You cried for me, I cried for you babe
Couldn’t believe all things we use to do
One thing stays on my mind
The look that was in your eyes
Why couldn’t I see at that time
That you loved me and you tried
Now you’re gone I ain’t mad at you
Never wanted to let you go
I wish I could hold you again
But its too late, now baby I know
Our love ,Ain’t strong,
Couldn’t survive thru all these struggles
Couldn’t never last too many troubles
Can’t stand, the pain
You cried for me, I cried for you babe
Couldn’t believe all things we use to do
Look into my eyes
What do you see?
All I see is the hatred
Isn’t that what you told me
Why am I crying bout you and I
It was all lies
All I do is cry cry cry
All you say is lie lie lie
Such a fool am I, I, I
But I’l be fine once I get you out of my mind
All I do is cry cry cry
All you say is lie lie lie
Such a fool am I, I, I
I just wanna get you out of my mind
Out of sight out of mind
I dont mind this
Sick of all the lyin and the cryin girl im dying over here
You need to stop with the wining
Glad you'd realized you and i wrong timing
Girl you know that you is no angel
Cuz it always takes two two to tango
But somehow i get i get the blame though
Look in the mirror its you throwin' the low blow
Why does it have to be this way
What happened to it will be ok
I know that i am not perfect
But i try really hard to make it worth it
You're still a diamond hope u keep shinin'
I just gotta do what i do
No more hidin' the truth
U and i we gotta let go
Cuz i dont want to hurt you no more
Our love ain’t strong
Couldn’t survive thru all these struggles
Couldn’t never last too many troubles
Can’t stand, the pain
You cried for me, I cried for you babe
Couldn’t believe all things we use to do
Our love, ain't strong
Couldn’t survive thru all these struggles
Couldn’t never last too many troubles
Can’t stand (I can't stand) the pain (Don't you know)
You cried for me, I cried for you babe
Couldn’t believe all things we use to do