Sittin' over here
Starin' in your face
With lust in my eyes
Sure don't give a damn and ya
Don't know that I've been dreamin' of ya
In my fantasy
Never once you looked at me,
Don't even realize that I'm wantin' you
To fulfill my needs
Think what you want
Let your mind free
Run free to a place that no one dares to
How many nights
I've laid in bed excited over you
I've closed my eyes
And thought of us a hundred different ways
I've gotten there so many times
I wonder how 'bout you
Day and night, day
All I've got to say is
If I was your girl...
Oh the things I'll do to you
I'd make you call out my name
I'd ask who it belongs to
If I was your woman,
The things I'd do to you
But I'm not, so I can't,
Then I won't
But, if I was your girl
How many nights
I've laid in bed excited over you
I've closed my eyes
And thought of us a hundred different ways
I've gotten there so many times
I wonder how 'bout you
Day and night, day
All I've got to say is
If I was your girl...
Oh the things I'll do to you
I'd make you call out my name
I'd ask who it belongs to
If I was your woman,
The things I'd do to you
But I'm not, so I can't,
Then I won't
But, if I was your girl
If I was your girl...
Oh the things I'll do to you
I'd make you call out my name
I'd ask who it belongs to
If I was your woman,
The things I'd do to you
But I'm not, so I can't,
Then I won't
But
If I was your girl