Once upon a time, a few mistakes ago
I was in your sights, you got me alone
You found me
You found me-e-e-e
I guess you didn't care, and I guess I like that
And when I fell hard, you took a step back
Without me,
Without me
Without me-e-e-e-e-e...
And he's long gone, when he's next to me
And I realize the blame is on me
Cause I knew you were trouble when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places I'd never been
Til you put me down
Oh I knew you were trouble when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places I'd never been
Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground
Oh, oh
Trouble, trouble, trouble
No apologizes, he'll never see you cry
Pretend he doesn't know, that he's the reason why
You're drowning, you're drowning
You're drowni-i-i-i-ng
And I heard you moved on, from whispers on the street
A new notch in your belt is all I'll ever be
And now I see
Now I see
Now I see-e-e-e-e
He was long gone when he met me
And I realize the joke is on me
I knew you were trouble when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places I'd never been
Til you put me down
Oh I knew you were trouble when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places I'd never been
Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground
Oh, oh
Trouble, trouble, trouble
And the saddest fear comes creeping in
That you never loved me or her, or anyone, or anything, yeah...
I knew you were trouble when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places I'd never been
Til you put me down
Oh I knew you were trouble when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places I'd never been
Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground
Oh, oh
Trouble, trouble, trouble
I knew you were trouble when you walked in
Dj SiRiPaLa m/