Adele
Someone Like you
Uploaded by @MarcelloElaelo
I heard
That your settled down
That you found a girl
And your married now.
I heard that your dreams came true.
Guess she gave you things
I didn't give to you.
Old friend, why are you so shy?
It ain't like you to hold back
Or hide from the lie.
I hate to turn up out of the blue uninvited,
But I couldn't stay away,
I couldn't fight it.
I hoped you'd see my face
And that you'd be reminded,
That for me, it isn't over.
Nevermind, I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you too.
Don't forget me, I beg,
I remember you said:
Sometimes it lasts in love but sometimes it hurts instead
Yeah.
You'd know how the time flies.
Only yesterday was the time of our lives.
We were born and raised in a summer haze.
Bound by the surprise of our glory days.
I hate to turn up out of the blue uninvited,
But I couldn't stay away
I couldn't fight it
I hoped you'd see my face
And that you'd be reminded,
That for me, it isn't over
Nevermind, I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you too.
Don't forget me, I beg
I remember you said
Sometimes it lasts in love but sometimes it hurts instead
Yay-e.
Nothing compares, no worries or cares.
Regret's and mistakes
They're memories made.
Who would have known how
Bittersweet this would taste?
Nevermind, I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you
Don't forget me, I beg
I remembered you said
Sometimes it lasts in love but sometimes it hurts instead
Nevermind, I'll find someone like you.
I wish nothing but the best for you too.
Don't forget me, I beg
I remembered you said
Sometimes it lasts in love but sometimes it hurts instead
Yeah.