For you I'd write a symphony,
I'd tell the violin,
It's time to sink or swim,
Watch them play for ya,
For you I'd be, (whoa oh)
Running a thousand miles,
Just to get to where you are.
Step to the beat of my heart,
I don't need a whole lot,
But for you I admit I,
I'd rather give you the world,
Or we can share mine,
I know I won't be the first one,
giving you all this attention,
Baby listen,
I just need somebody to love,
I don't need too much, just somebody to love,
Somebody to love.
I don't need nothing else,
I promise girl I swear,
I just need somebody to love.
I need somebody, I need somebody,
I need somebody, I need somebody
Every day,
I bring the sun around,
I sweep away the clouds,
Smile for me.
I would take,
Every second, every single time,
Spend it like my last dime.
Step to the beat of my heart,
I don't need a whole lot,
But for you I admit I,
I'd rather give you the world,
Or you can share mine,
I know I won't be the first one,
Givin' you all this attention,
so baby listen,
I just need somebody to love,
I don't need too much, just somebody to love,
Somebody to love.
I don't need nothing else,
I promise girl I swear,
I just need somebody to love.
I need somebody, I need somebody,
I need somebody, I need somebody
Somebody to love.
I need somebody, I need somebody,
I need somebody, I need somebody
I just need somebody to love.
And you can have it all,
Anything you want,
I can bring; give you the finer things, yeah
But what I really want,
I can't find cause,
Money can't find me,
Somebody to love (oh, oh)
Find me somebody to love (whoah ohh)
I need somebody to love,
I don't need too much, just somebody to love,
Somebody to love.
I don't need nothing else,
I promise girl I swear,
I just need somebody to love.
I need somebody, I need somebody,
I need somebody, I need somebody
Somebody to love.
I need somebody, I need somebody,
I need somebody, I need somebody
I just need somebody to love.
I need somebody, I need somebody,
I need somebody, I need somebody
I need somebody to love.
To love, to love.
Is she out there?
I just need somebody to love.