It's JB
My friends say I'm a fool to think
That you're the one for me
I guess I'm just a sucker for love (love, love)
'Cuz honestly the truth is that
You know I'm never leavin'
'Cuz you're my angel sent from above (above, above)
Baby you can do no wrong
My money is yours (Ooh)
Give you little more because I love ya,
Love ya
With me, girl, is where you belong
Just stay right here
I promise my dear I'll put nothin above yah
Above yah
(Ooh)
Love me, Love me (Hey)
Say that you love me
Fool me, Fool me (Hey)
Oh how you do me
Kiss me, Kiss me (Hey)
Say that you miss me
Tell me what I wanna hear (Oh, oh)
Tell me you love me
Love me, Love me (Hey)
Say that you love me
Fool me, Fool me (Hey)
Oh how you do me
Kiss me, Kiss me (Hey)
Say that you miss me
Tell me what I wanna hear (Oh, oh)
Tell me u love me
People try to tell me
but I still refuse to listen
'Cuz they don't get to spend time with you you you
A minute with you is worth more than
A thousand days without your love,
Oh your love
(Ooh)
And Baby you can do no wrong
My money is yours (Ooh)
Give you little more because I love ya
Love ya
With me, girl, is where you belong belong
Just stay right here
I promise my dear I'll put nothin above ya
Above ya
(Ooh)
Love me, Love me (Hey)
Say that you love me
Fool me, Fool me (Hey)
Oh how you do me
Kiss me , Kiss me (Hey)
Say that u miss me
Tell me what i wanna hear (Oh, oh)
Tell me you love me.
Love me, Love me (Hey)
Say that you love me
Fool me, Fool me (Hey)
Oh how you do me
Kiss me , kiss me (Hey)
Say that u miss me
Tell me what i wanna hear (Oh, oh)
Tell me you love me.
My heart is blind but I don't care
'Cuz when I'm with you everything
has disappeared (Oooh)
And every time I hold you near
I never wanna let you go,
(Ooh)
Love me, Love me (Hey) (Oooooooh)
Say that you love me
Fool me, Fool me (Hey)
Oh how you do me (Meee)
Kiss me , kiss me (Hey)
Say that u miss me
Tell me what i wanna hear (Ooooooh)
Tell me you love me.
Love me, Love me (Hey)
Say that you love me (Meee)
Fool me, Fool me (Hey)
Oh how you do me (Meee)
Kiss me , kiss me (Hey)
Say that u miss me (Meee)
Tell me what i wanna hear (Hey) (Oh, oh)
Tell me you love me.