Let go
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
one less lonely girl
How many I told you's and start overs
And shoulders have you cried on before
How many promises be honest girl
How many tears you let hit the floor
How many bags you packed
Just to take 'em back tell me that
How many either or but no more
If you let me inside of your world
There'd be the one less lonely girl
Ohh No
Saw so many pretty faces before I saw you you
Now all I see is you
I'm Coming for you
Ohh No
Don't need these other pretty faces
Like I need you
and when your mine in this world
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
One less lonely girl
I'm gonna put you first
I'll show you what you're worth
If you let me inside your world
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
Christmas wasn't merry, 14th of February not one of them spent with you
How many dinner dates set dinner plates and
He didn't even touch his food
How many torn photographs saw you taping back
Tell me that couldn't see an open door
But no more
If you let me inside of your world
Ohh No
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
Saw so many pretty faces before I saw you you
Now all I see is you
I'm Coming for you
No no
Don't need these other pretty faces
Like I nee you
and when your mine in this world
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
One less lonely girl
I'm gonna put you first
I'll show you what you're worth
If you let me inside of your world
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
I can fix up your broken heart
I can give you a brand new start
I can make you believe
I just wanna set one girl free to fall,
Free to fall
She's free to fall
fall in love
With me
My hearts locked and nowhere to get the key
I'll take you and leave the world with one less lonely girl
One less lonely girl
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
I'm gonna put you first
I'll show you what you're worth
If you let me inside your world
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
One less lonely girl
I'm gonna put you first
I'll show you what you're worth
If you let me inside your world
There's gonna be one less lonely girl
Only you shawty