oohhh noo, ohh noo, ohhh
they say that hate has been sent
so let loose the talk of love
before they outlaw the kiss
baby give me one last hug
theres a dream
that i've been chasing
want so badly for it to be reality
and when you hold my hand
then i understand
that its meant to be
cuz baby when you're with me
its like an angel came by, and took me to heaven
(like you took me to heaven)
cuz when i stare in your eyes
it couldnt be better
so let the music it blast
we gon' do our dance
praise the doubters on
they dont matter at all
cuz this lifes to long
and its much to strong
so baby no for sho'
ill never let you go
i got my favorite girl
not feelin' no pain
(no pain, no pain, no pain)
oh no, dont have a care in the world
why would i, when you are here
theres a moments i've been chasin
and i finally caught it out on this floor
baby, theres no hesitation,
no reservation by taking a chance and more
ohh noo, because
its like an angel came by, and took me to heaven
(like you took me to heaven)
cuz when i stare in your eyes
it couldnt be better
(i dont want to go, no no no)
so let the music it blast
we gon' do our dance
praise the doubters on
they dont matter at all
cuz this lifes to long
and this loves to strong
so baby no for sho'
ill never let you go
its like an angel came by, and took me to heaven
cuz when i stare in your eyes
it couldnt be better
(i dont want you to go, no, no, so)
take my hand, lets just dance
watch my feet, follow me
dont be scared, girl im here
if you didnt know, this is loooovee
(so let the music it blast)
(we gon' do our dance)
(praise the doubters on)
(like you took me to heaven)
(they dont matter at all)
(cuz this lifes to long)
(and its much to strong)
(so baby no for sho')
(ill never let you go)
so don't fear
dont you worry about a thing
i am here
(i here)
don't shed a tear
whenever you need me
i'll be here
ill never let you go, gooooo
ill never let you go,
(oh yeah, oh yeah)
ohhhh
ill never let you go,
ohh no, ohh noo, ohhh
ill never let you go