Never say never
Bring it on, JB,
bring it on,
See I never thought
that I could walk through fire.
I never thought
that I could take the burn.
I never had the strength
to take it higher,
Until I reached the point
of no return.
And there's
just no turning back,
When your heart's
under attack,
Gonna give everything I have,
It's my destiny.
I will never say never!
I will fight
I will fight till forever!
make it right
Whenever you
knock me down,
I will not stay on
the ground.
Pick it up,
and never say never.
And never say never
Never say never,
I never see it,
I never thought that
l could feel this power.
l could feel this free.
I'm strong enough
to climb the highest tower.
And I'm fast enough to run
across the sea.
And there's
just no turning back,
When your heart's
under attack,
Gonna give
everything I have,
Cause this is my destiny.
I will never say never!
I will fight
I will fight till forever!
make it right
Whenever you
knock me down,
I will not stay
on the ground.
Pick it up,
and never say never.
Here we go!
Guess who?
JSmith and JB!
I gotcha lil bro.
I can handle him.
Hold up, aight?
Now he's bigger than me,
Taller than me,
and he's older than me,
And stronger than me.
And his arms
a little bit longer than me.
But he ain't on
a JB song with me!
I be trying a chill
They be trying to side
with the thrill.
No pun intended,
was raised by the power of Will.
Like Luke with the force,
when push comes to shove.
Like Cobe with the 4th,
ice water with blood.
I gotta be the best,
and yes
We're the flyest,
like David and Goliath,
I conquered the giant.
So now I got the world
in my hand,
I was born
from two stars
So the moon's
where I land
I will never say never!
I will fight
I will fight till forever!
make it right
Whenever you
knock me down,
I will not stay
on the ground.
Pick it up,
and never say never.
I will never say never!
I will say never
I will fight till forever!
make it right
Whenever you
knock me down,
I will not stay
on the ground.
Pick it up,
and never say never,
And never say never,
never say it
And never say never
Never say never,
never say it,
And never say never