Everybody's laughing in my mind
Rumors spreading 'bout this other guy
Do you do what you did
When you did with me?
Does he love you the way I can?
Did you forget all the plans
That you made with me?
'Cause baby I didn't
That should be me
Holding your hand
Making you laugh
That should be me
This is so sad
Feeling your kiss
That should be me
Buying you gifts
This is so wrong
I can't go on
Till you believe
That should be me
You said you needed
A little time for my mistakes
It's funny how you use that time
To have me replaced
But did you think that
I wouldn't see you out at the movies?
Whatcha doin' to me?
You're taking him where we used to go
Now if you're trying to break my heart
It's working 'cause you know
That should be me
Holding your hand
Making you laugh
That should be me
This is so sad
Feeling your kiss
That should be me
Buying you gifts
This is so wrong
I can't go on
Till you believe
That should be me
I need to know should I fight
for our love for this long
It's getting harder to shield
This pain in my heart
That should be me
Holding your hand
Making you laugh
That should be me
This is so sad
Feeling your kiss
That should be me
Buying you gifts
This is so wrong
I can't go on
Till you believe
That should be me
Holding your hand
Oh, I making you laugh, oh baby
That should be me
(That should be me giving you flowers)
Talking by hours
That should be me
Never shoulda let you go