Ohh Ohh Ohh .. and I pray
I just can't sleep tonight
Knowing that things aint right
Its in the papers, its on the tv, its everywhere that I go
Children are crying
Soldiers are dying
Some people don't have a home
But I know there's sunshine behind that rain
I know there's good times behind that pain, hey
Can you tell me how I can make a change
I close my eyes and I can see a better day
I close my eyes....and pray
I close my eyes...and pray
I lose my appetite...
Knowing kids starve tonight
And when I sit up, cause my dinner is still on my plate
Ooo I got a vision, to make a difference
And its starting today
Cause I know there's sunshine behind that rain
I know there's good times behind that pain, hey
Haven`t tell me how I can make a change
I close my eyes and I can see a better day
I close my eyes....and pray
I close my eyesand I can see a better day
I close my eyes...and pray
For the broken-hearted
I pray for the life not started
I pray for all the ones not breathing
I pray for all the souls in need
I pray...
Can you give em one today
I just can't sleep tonight
Can someone tell how to make a change?
I close my eyes and I can see a better day
I close my eyes...and pray
I close my eyes...and I pray
I pray ..
I close my eyes and pray...