Three!
That's not luck,
that was skill
Yeah,
I'm killing you
Yo! Usher,
JB, what's up man?
I'm just playing video game
with ryan
You think that you can hold the house
till I get back?
Yeah,
l can do that
Alright,
my man
Me plus you,
I'ma tell you one time
One time,
When I met you girl
my heart went knock
Now them butterflies
in my stomach won't stop
And even though
it's a struggle love is all we got
So we gonna keep keep climbing
till the mountain top
Your world is my world
And my fight is your fight
My breath is your breath
And your heart
and now I've got
My one love,
my one heart
My one life for sure
Let me tell you one time,
girl I love you
I'ma tell you one time,
And I'll be your one guy,
you'll be my number one girl
Always makin' time
for you
I'ma tell you one time,
girl I love you
You look so deep,
you know that it humbles me
You're by my side
and troubles them don't trouble me
Many have called
but the chosen is you
Whatever you want shawty
I'll give it to you
Your world is my world
And my fight is your fight
My breath is your breath
And your heart
and now I've got
My one love,
my one heart
My one life for sure
Let me tell you one time
girl I love you
I'ma tell you one time
I'll be your one guy,
you'll be my number one girl
Always makin' time
for you
I'ma tell you one time,
girl I love you
Shawty is right there
She's got everything
l need
And I'ma tell her
one time
Give you everything
you need
Down to my last dime
She makes me happy,
l know where I'll be
Right by your side
cause she is the one
And girl
you're my one love
My one heart,
my one life for sure
Let me tell you one time
girl I love you
I'ma tell you one time
And I'll be your one guy,
you'll be my number one girl
Always makin time
for you
I'ma tell you one time
girl I love you
Me plus you,
I'ma tell you one time
One time,