1, 2, 3
Go
Ciara
Sex
Here we go
Talk to me
Your touch is
so magic to me
The strangest
things can happen
The way that
you react to me
I wanna do something
you can't imagine
Imagine if there was a million me's
talking sexy to you like that
You think
you can handle, boy
If I give you my squeeze and
I need you to push it right back
Baby, show me,
show me
What's your favorite trick
that you wanna use on me
And I'll volunteer
And I'll be flowing
and going
Till clothing disappears,
ain't nothing but shoes on me
Oh, baby
All night, show it,
just you and the crowd
Doing tricks you
never seen
And I bet that
I can make you believe
In love and sexy magic
So let me drive
my body around you
I bet you know
what I mean
Cause you know that
I can make you believe
In love
and sexy magic
Everything ain't
what it seems
I wave my hands
and I got you
And you feel
so fly assisting me
But now it's my turn
to watch you
I ain't gonna stop you
If you wanna
crowd my neck
Talk sexy to me
like that
Just do what
I taught you, girl
When I give you my heat
and I need you to push it right back
Baby, show me,
show me
What's your favorite trick
that you wanna use on me
And I'll volunteer
And I'll be flowing
and going
Till clothing disappears,
ain't nothing but shoes on me
Oh, baby
All night, show it,
just you and the crowd
Doing tricks you
never seen
And I bet that
I can make you believe
In love
and sexy magic
So let me drive
my body around you
I bet you know
what I mean
Cause you know that
I can make you believe
In love
and sexy magic
This is the part that
we fall in love..
Sugar
Let's slow it down
so we fall in love...
But don't stop
what ya doin to me
Ciara
All night, show it,
just you and the crowd
Doing tricks
you never seen
And I bet that
I can make you believe
In love
and sexy magic
So let me drive
my body around you
I bet you know
what I mean
Cause you know that
I can make you believe
In love
and sexy magic
All night, show it,
just you and the crowd
Doing tricks you
never seen
And I bet that
I can make you believe
In love
and sexy magic
So let me drive
my body around you
I bet you know
what I mean
Cause you know that
I can make you believe
In love
and sexy magic
I see you on the floor
Get it girl
In love
and sex magic
I see you on the floor
You know
what I mean
Get it girl
I bet that
I could make you believe
In love
and sex magic
I see you on the floor
Get it girl