Now if your dude ain't acting right
you tell that dude he got to go
If that dude be claiming that he broke
If he want you to stay in the house everyday
and night tell him he got to go
If he wanna run the streets then you run the streets too
And you tell him he got to go
Baby baby somebody's gonna cry tonight
Baby baby but it won't be my tears tonight
(Let's Go)
So whatcha think about that whatcha think about it
Whatcha think about that that that oh baby
Tonight we gon' switch up I'll do you you do me
Tonight you gon' stay home while I'm running the street
What do you what do you what do you
what do you think about that baby
Imma let you play my part so you can feel a broken heart
And when that you fall, make sure that
you call so I can see it
Baby baby somebody's gonna cry tonight
Baby baby but it won't be my tears tonight
So whatcha think about that whatcha think about it
Whatcha think about that that that oh baby
Tonight you gon' call me a thousand times
Tonight I'm gon' make up a thousand lies
How do you how do you how do you
how do you feel about that baby
Imma let you play my part so you can feel a broken heart
And when you just fall, make sure that
you call so I can see it
Baby baby somebody's gonna cry tonight
Baby baby but it won't be my tears tonight
So whatcha think about that whatcha think about it
Whatcha think about that that that oh baby
Okay
Hold up
Whatchu think about that
You wear the dress and I put on your slacks
Tonight I'm going out and ain't coming back
You ain't get no more pussycat
See me in the club I'm out with my girls
Do like you do when you out with them dudes
Up in the club it's just me and my girls
Play like Katy Perry kissing on girls
Now you can't eat or sleep and now
You in the house thinking 'bout me and now
I do what you do and me and now I love to see you baby
Baby baby somebody's gonna cry tonight
Baby baby but it won't be my tears tonight
So whatcha think about that whatcha think about it
Whatcha think about that that that oh baby
Now if your dude ain't acting right you
tell that dude he got to go
If that dude be claiming that he broke you
If he want you to stay in the house everyday
and night tell him he got to go
If he wanna run the streets then you run the streets too
And you tell him he got to go
Baby baby oh baby somebody's gonna cry tonight
Somebody's gonna cry tonight baby