Ladies and gentlemen
It's my pleasure to introduce to you
He's a friend of mine
Yes, yes I am
And he goes by the name...
Justin
Wowoowoooo
All the way
from Memphis, Tennessee
And he's got somethin' special
for y'all tonight
He's gonna sing a song for y'all
About this girl
Come in right here?
Yea, come on
On that sunny day
Didn't know I'd meet
Such a beautiful girl
Walking down the street
Seen those bright brown eyes
With tears coming down
She deserves a crown
But where is it now
Mamma listen
Senorita, I feel for you
You deal with things, that you don't have to
He doesn't love ya, I can tell by his charm
But you could feel this real love
If you just lay in my...
Running fast in my mind
Girl don't you slow it down
If we carry on this way
This thing might leave the ground
How would you like to fly?
That's how my queen should arrive
But you still deserve the crown
or hasn't it been found?
Mamma listen
Senorita, I feel for you
(Feel for you)
You deal with things, that you don't have to
(No, no)
He doesn't love ya, I can tell by his charm
(He don't love ya baby)
But you could feel this real love
(Feel it)
If you just lay in my...
Ah, ah, arms...
(Won't you lay in my)
(Mama lay in my)
Ah, ah, arms...
(Baby won't you lay in my)
When I look into your eyes
I see something that money can't buy
And I know if you give us a try
I'll work hard for you girl
And no longer will you ever have to cry
Senorita, I feel for you
You deal with things, that you don't have to
(Deal with things you don't have to)
He doesn't love ya, I can tell by his charm
(No, no)
But you could feel this real love
(Feel it)
If you just lay in my...
Ah, ah, arms...
(Whoa)
(My baby)
Ah, ah, arms...
(Oooh, yea)
Now listen
I wanna try somethin' right now
See they don't do this anymore
I'ma sing something
And I want the guys to sing wit' me
They go
"It feels like something's heating up,
can I leave with you?"
And then the ladies go
"I don't know what I'm thinking bout,
really leaving with you"
Guys sing
It feels like something's heating up,
can I leave with you?
And ladies
I don't know what I'm thinking bout,
really leaving with you
Feels good don't it, come on
It feels like something's heating up,
can I leave with you?
Yea, ladies
I don't know what I'm thinking bout,
really leaving with you
Show the good to me
Sing it one more time
It feels like something's heating up,
can I leave with you?
Ladies
I don't know what I'm thinking bout,
really leaving with you
Yea, yea..
It feels like something's heating up,
can I leave with you?
Ladies
I don't know what I'm thinking bout,
really leaving with you
Gentlemen, good night
Ladies, good morning
That's it