I'm bringin' sexy back
Them other boys they don't know how to act
I think it's special... what's behind your back
So turn around and and I'll pick up the slack
(Take it to the bridge)
Dirty Babe
You see these shackles baby I'm your slave
I'll let you whip me if I misbehave
It's just that no one makes me feel this way
(take it to the chorus)
Come here girl, go head be gone with it
Come to the back, go head be gone with it
VIP, go ahead be gone with it
Drinks on me, go ahead be gone with it
Lemme see what you're twerking with
go ahead be gone with it
Look at those hips, go ahead be gone with it
Make me smile, go ahead be gone with it
Go 'ahead child, go ahead be gone with it
Get your sexy on, go ahead be gone with it
I'm bringin' sexy back
Them other fuckers don't know how to act
Girl let me make up for all the things you lack
Because you're burning up I got to get it fast
(Take it to the bridge)
Dirty Babe
You see these shackles baby I'm your slave
I'll let you whip me if I misbehave
It's just that no one makes me feel this way
(take it to the chorus)
Come here girl, go ahead be gone with it
Come to the back, go ahead be gone with it
VIP, go ahead be gone with it
Drinks on me, go ahead be gone with it
Lemme see what you're twerking with
go ahead be gone with it
Look at those hips, go ahead be gone with it
Make me smile, go ahead be gone with it
Go 'ahead child, go ahead be gone with it
Get your sexy on, go ahead be gone with it
I'm bringin' sexy back
you mother fuckers watch how I attack
If that's your girl, baby watch your back
Cuz you're burning up for me and that's a fact
(take it to the chorus)
Come here girl, go ahead be gone with it
Come to the back, go ahead be gone with it
VIP, go ahead be gone with it
Drinks on me, go ahead be gone with it
Lemme see what you're twerking with
go ahead be gone with it
Look at those hips, go ahead be gone with it
Make me smile, go ahead be gone with it
Go 'ahead child, go ahead be gone with it
Get your sexy on, go ahead be gone with it