She's freaky
and she knows it
and I like it
Listen
She grabs the
yellow bottle
She likes the way
it hits her lips
She gets to
the bottom
It sends her
on a trip so right
She might be goin' home
with me tonight
She looks like a model
Except she's got
a little more ass
Don't even bother
Unless you've got
that thing she likes
I hope she's goin' home
with me tonight
Those flashing lights come
from everywhere
The way they hit her I just
stop and stare
She's got me
love stoned
Man I swear she's
bad and she knows
I think that
she knows
She's freaky
and she knows it
She's freaky,
but I like it
She shuts the room down
The way she walks
and causes a fuss
The baddest in town
She's flawless
like some uncut ice
I hope she's goin' home
with me tonight
And all she wants
is to dance
That's why you'll find
her on the floor
But you don't
have a chance
Unless you move
the way that she likes
That's why she's goin' home
with me tonight
Those flashing lights come
from everywhere
The way they hit her
I just stop and stare
She's got me love stoned
Man I swear she's bad
and she knows
I think that she knows
Those flashing lights seem
to cause a glare
The way they hit her
I just stop and stare
She's got me love stoned
from everywhere
She's bad and she knows
I think that she knows
Now dance
Little girl
You're freaky,
but I like it
Hot damn!
Let me put my funk on
this one time
Those flashing lights
come from everywhere
The way they hit her
I just stop and stare
She's got me love stoned
Man I swear she's
bad and she knows
I think that she knows
Those flashing lights seem
to cause a glare
The way they hit her
I just stop and stare
She's got me love stoned
from everywhere
She's bad and she knows
I think that she knows
Those flashing lights come
from everywhere
The way they hit her
I just stop and stare
She's got me
love stoned
I think
I'm love stoned
She's got me
love stoned
I think that she knows,
think that she knows, oh, oh
Those flashing lights come
from everywhere
I think that she knows,
think that she knows, oh, oh
Those flashing lights come
from everywhere
The way they hit her
I just stop and stare
I'm love stoned from everywhere
and she knows
Think that
she knows, oh, oh
And now I walk
around without a care
She's got me hooked
It just ain't fair, but I...
I'm love stoned
and I could swear
That she knows
Think that
she knows, oh, oh
She knows,