Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
(I'm tired of arguing girl)
Hey, hey, hey,
Hey, hey, hey
My love, hey, my love, hey
I love the way you're standing
Lips look so sweet, like cotton candy (My love)
That don't mean you gotta stop dancing
'Cause the way that you move
is so demanding (My love)
Let's put it on cruise control
Let me take you to the crib,
let me ease your soul (My love)
I gonna take it really nice and slow
But first let me, let me, let me talk to her
My love, hey, my love, hey
Walk into my great place, cozy
I'm glad you came, let's make a toast (My love)
Let me make an indecent proposal
Let me take you to the back and
do what we're suppose to (My love)
Let's take a trip to the bayou
You can be the investigator, I'm your Private I (My love)
You know I want a piece of that pie
But first let me, let me, let me talk to her
My love, hey, my love, hey
Ain't another woman that can take your spot my-
If I wrote you a symphony,
Just to say how much you mean to me
(what would you do?)
If I told you you were beautiful
Would you date me on the regular
(tell me, would you?)
Well, baby I've been around the world
But I ain't seen myself another girl (like you)
This ring here represents my heart
But there's just one thing I need from you
(say "I do")
Yeah, because
I can see us holding hands
Walking on the beach, our toes in the sand
I can see us on the countryside
Sitting on the grass, laying side by side
You could be my baby, let me make you my lady
Girl, you amaze me
Ain't gotta do nothing crazy
See, all I want you to do is be my love
(So don't give away) My love
(So don't give away)
Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love
(So don't give away) My love
(So don't give away)
Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love
Ooooh, girl
My love
Now, if I wrote you a love note
And made you smile with every word I wrote
(what would you do?)
Would that make you want to change your scene
And wanna be the one on my team
(tell me, would you?)
See, what's the point of waiting anymore?
Cause girl I've never been more sure
(that baby, it's you)
This ring here represents my heart
And everything that you've been waiting for
(just say "I do")
Yeah, because
I can see us holding hands
Walking on the beach, our toes in the sand
I can see us on the countryside
Sitting on the grass, laying side by side
You could be my baby, let me make you my lady
Girl, you amaze me
Ain't gotta do nothing crazy
See, all I want you to do is be my love
(So don't give away) My love
(So don't give away)
Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love
(So don't give away) My love
(So don't give away)
Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love
Ooooh, girl
My love
Shorty, cool as a fan
On the new once again
Still has fan from Peru to Japan
Listen baby, I don't wanna ruin your plan
If you got a man, try to lose him if you can
Cause your girls real wild through your hands up high
Wanna come kick it wit a stand up guy
You don't really wanna let the chance go by
Because you ain't been seen wit a man so fly
Friend so fly i can go fly
Private, cause I handle mine
Call me candle guy, simply because I am on fire
I hate to have to cancel my vacation so you can't deny
I'm patient, but I ain't gonna try
You don't come, I ain't gonna die
Hold up, what you mean, you can't go why?
Me and you boyfriend we ain't no tie
You say you wanna kick it with an ace so high
Baby, you decide that I ain't your guy
Ain't gon lie ,Me in your space
But forget your face, I swear I will
Same mark, same bullet anywhere I chill
Just bring wit me a pair, I will
I can see us holding hands
Walking on the beach, our toes in the sand
I can see us on the countryside
Sitting on the grass, laying side by side
You could be my baby, let me make you my lady
Girl, you amaze me
Ain't gotta do nothing crazy
See, all I want you to do is be my love
(Love) My love
(Love)
Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love
(Love) My love
(Love)
Ain't another woman that can take your spot, my love
Ooooh, girl
My love