I'm lovin' it (Badabababa)
Don't you Love it too......
Hi, I'm not here to waist your time
And No this aint'a pick up line
I Just think that your a Dime
(oooooo)Well don'tjust sit there girl
I Know that heart thats in your chest
It Carries Pain and so much stress
But you gotta let it go (go go girl)
Just Close Your Eyes ill grab your waist
Next Thing you know you'll have Your paice
But you gotta let it go (go go girl)
I Know you wan'to get down (Do you wanna get down)
You Do Deserve to get down (Do you wanna get down)
Youve Been workin hard all week (All Week)
Just Try'n to make ya money (Money)
Go Girl Now Shake ya booty (oooooo)
I'm lovin' it, I'm lovin' it
I'm lovin' it (Badabababa)
By The way whats your sign
I bet It is compatible with mine
Probly long lastin years down the line
I'm Tellin you girl your a Dime
Well don'tjust sit there girl
I Know that heart thats in your chest
It Carries Pain and so much stress
But you gotta let it go (go go girl)
Just Close Your Eyes ill grab your waist
Next Thing you know you'll have Your paice
But you gotta let it go (go go girl)
How, how'd you do all the things you do
At being you your so Profesional (Profesional)
Not to mention your the badest of your Crew
Well don'tjust sit there girl
I Know you wan'to get down
You Do Deserve to get down (Wanna get Down)
Youve Been workin hard all week (All Week)
Just Try'n to make ya money (Money)
Go Girl Now Shake ya booty (oooooo)
I'm lovin' it, I'm lovin' it
I'm lovin' it (Badabababa)
Don't you Love it too......