Don't be so quick to walk away (Dance with me)
I wanna rock your body, please stay (Dance with me)
You don't have to admit you wanna play (Dance with me)
Just let me rock you till the break of day (Dance with me)
Got time, but I don't mind
Just wanna rock you, girl
I'll have whatever you have
Come on let's give it a whirl
See, I've been watchin' you
And I like the way you move
So go head, girl, just do it
That a** shakin' thing you do
So you grab your girls and you grab a couple more
And you all could meet me in the middle of the floor
Said the air is thick, it's smellin' right
So you pass to the left, then you sail to the right
Don't be so quick to walk away (Dance with me)
I wanna rock your body, please stay (Dance with me)
You don't have to admit you wanna play (Dance with me)
Just let me rock you till the break of day (Dance with me)
I don't mean no harm
Just wanna rock you, girl
We could move, but we
Let's go, let's give it a whirl
See, it appears to me
You like the way I move
I tell you what I'm gon' do
Pull you close to share my groove
So you grab your girls and you grab a couple more
And you all could meet me in the middle of the floor
Said the air is thick, it's smellin' right
So you pass to the left, then you sail to the right
Don't be so quick to walk away (Dance with me)
I wanna rock your body, please stay (Dance with me)
You don't have to admit you wanna play (Dance with me)
Just let me rock you till the break of day (Dance with me)
Talk to me, boy No disrespect, I don't mean no harm
Talk to me, boy I can't wait to have you in my arms
Talk to me, boy Hurry up cause you're takin' too long
Talk to me, boy Bet I'll have you naked by the end of this song
So what did you come here for I came to dance with you
You don't wanna hit the floor Get some romance with you
If you should fall for evermore I'll take a chance
If love is here on the floor, girl
Yeah
Dance with me
Come on, baby
Don't be so quick to walk away (Dance with me)
I wanna rock your body, please stay (Dance with me)
You don't have to admit you wanna play (Dance with me)
Just let me rock you till the break of day (Dance with me)
Talk to me, boy No disrespect, I don't mean no harm
Talk to me, boy I can't wait to have you in my arms
Talk to me, boy Hurry up cause you're takin' too long
Talk to me, boy Bet I'll have you
naked by the end of this song
Don't be so quick to walk away (I was just thinkin' of you)
Don't be so quick to walk away (We could do somethin')
Don't be so quick to walk away (I like the way you look right now)
Don't be so quick to walk away (Come over here, baby)
Are you feelin' me
Let's do somethin'
Let's make a bet
Cause I-I bet I'll have you naked by the end of this song