Just something about you...
Way I'm lookin at you whatever
You keep lookin at me...
You gettin scared now, right?
Don't fear me baby, it's just destiny
It feel good right?...
Listen
I kind of noticed, from one night
From the club, your front face
It's kind of weird to me
Since you're so fine
If it's up to me your face will change
If you smiling that should set
the tone - just be limber
If you let go the music should groove
your bones - just remember
Sing this song with me
Ain't nobody love you like I love you
You're a good girl and that's
what makes me trust ya (hey!)
Late at night I talk to you
You will know the difference when I touch you
People are so phony
Nosy cause they're lonely
Aren't you sick of the same thing?
They say so and so was dating
Love you or they're hatin'
When it doesn't matter anyway
Cause we're here tonight
If you smiling, that should set
the tone - just be limber baby
If you let go, the music should groove
your bones - baby just remember
Sing this song with me
Ain't nobody love you like I love you
You're a good girl and that's
what makes me trust ya (hey!)
Late at night I talk to you
You will know the difference when I touch you
Yeah, you know I can make ya happy
I could change your life
If you give me that chance
To be your man
I won't let you down baby
If you give me that chance
To be your man
Here baby, put on my jacket
And then ...
Maybe we'll fly tonight (I just wanna love you baby)
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Girl ...
Ma, what chu wanna do?
I'm in front of you
Grab a friend see, I can have fun with two
Or me and you put on a stage show
In the mall kids, "that's how the chain glow"
Point to her they say, "wow, it's the same glow"
Point to me I say, "yeah, it's the same dough"
We the same type, you my air of life
You have sleepin in the same bed everynight
Go ride wit me you deservin' the best
Take a few shots let it burn in your chest
We could ride down pumpin N.E.R.D. in the deck
Funny how a few words turn into sex
Play number 3, joint called "Brain"
Ma, take a hint, make me swerve in the lane
The name Malicious and I burn every track
Clipse and J. Timberlake - now how heavy is that?
Maybe we'll fly tonight (I just wanna love you baby)
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Girl ...
Ain't nobody love you like I love you
You're a good girl and that's
what makes me trust ya (hey!)
Late at night I talk to you
You will know the difference when I touch you
Break it down
You know, I used to dream about this
when I was a little boy
I never thought it would end up this way, drums
It's kind of special right? yeah...
You know, you think about it
Sometimes people, just destined
Destined to do what they do
And that's what it is
Now everybody dance...