Guess this means you're sorry You're standing at my door
Guess this means you take back What you said before
Like how much you wanted Anyone but me
Said you'd never come back But here you are again
'Cause we belong together now, yeah
Forever united here somehow, yeah
You got a piece of me
And honestly
My life would suck without you...
Maybe I was stupid for telling you goodbye
Maybe I was wrong for tryin' to pick a fight
I know that I've got issues But you're pretty messed up too
Anyway, I found out I'm nothing without you
'Cause we belong together now, yeah
Forever united here somehow, yeah
You got a piece of me
And honestly
My life would suck without you...
Being with you is so dysfunctional
I really shouldn't miss you, but I can't let go, oh yeah
'Cause we belong together now, yeah
Forever united here somehow, yeah
You got a piece of me
And honestly
My life would suck without you...
'Cause we belong together now, yeah
Forever united here somehow, yeah
You got a piece of me
And honestly
My life would suck without you...