I hope the ring
You gave to her
Turns her finger green
I hope when you're in bed
With her
You think of me
I would never wish
Bad things
But I don't wish you well
Could you tell
By the flames
That burned your words
I never read your letter
Coz I knew what you'd say
Give me that
Sunday school answer
Try to make it all OK
Does it hurt
To know ill never be there
Bet it sucks
To see my face everywhere
It was you
Who chose to end it
Like you did
I was the last to know
You knew
Exactly what you would do
Don't say
You simply lost your way
She may believe you
But I never will
Never again
If she really knows
The truth
She deserves you
A trophy wife
Oh how cute
Ignorance is bliss
But when your day comes
And he's through with you
And he'll be through with you
You'll die together but alone
You wrote me in a letter
You couldn't say it right
To my face
Give me that
Sunday school answer
Repent your self away
Does it hurt
To know ill never be there
Bet it sucks
To see my face everywhere
It was you
Who chose to end it
Like you did
I was the last to know
You knew
Exactly what you would do
Don't say
You simply lost your way
They may believe you
But I never will
Never again
Will I hear you
Will I miss you
Never again
Will I fall to you
Never
Never again
Will I kiss you
Will I want to
Never again
Will I love you
Never
Does it hurt
To know ill never be there
Bet it sucks
To see my face everywhere
It was you
Who chose to end it
Like you did
I was the last to know
You knew
Exactly what you would do
Don't say
You simply lost your way
They may believe you
But I never will
I never Will
I never will
Never again