Oh sweetheart, put the bottle down
You've got too much talent
I see you through those bloodshot eyes
There's a cure, you've found it
Slow motion Sparks you caught that chill
Now don't deny it
But boys will be boys Oh, yes they will
They don't want to define it
Just give up the game And get into me
If you're looking for thrills
Then get cold feet
Oh no, I do not hook up, up
I go slow, so if you want me
I don't come cheap
Keep your hand on my hand
And your heart on your sleeve
Oh no, I do not hook up, up
I fall deep, cuz the more that you try
The harder I'll fight to say goodnight
I can't cook, no
But I can clean up the mess she left
Lay your head down and feel the beat
As I kiss your forehead
This may not last but this is now
So love the one you're with
You wanna chase, but you're chasing
Your tail, quick fix
Won't ever get you well
Oh no, I do not hook up, up
I go slow, so if you want me
I don't come cheap
Keep your hand on my hand
And your heart on your sleeve
Oh no, I do not hook up, up
I fall deep, cuz the more that you try
The harder I'll fight to say...
Cuz I feel the distance between us
Could be over with a snap of your fingers
Oh, no
Oh no, I do not hook up, up
I go slow, so if you want me
I don't come cheap
Keep your hand on my hand
And your heart on your sleeve
Oh no, I do not hook up, up
I fall deep, cuz the more that you try
The harder I'll fight to say,
Cuz the more that you try
The harder I'll fight to say goodnight
Oh sweetheart, put the bottle down
Cause you don't wanna miss out