Mr. Know It All
Well ya think you know it all
But ya don't know a thing at all
Ain't it something y'all
When somebody tells you something bout you
Think that they know you more than you do
So you take it down another pill to swallow
Mr. Bring me down
Well ya like to bring me down don't ya
But I ain't laying down
Baby I aint going down
Can't nobody tell me how it's gonna be
Nobody's gonna make a fool out of me
Baby you should know that I lead not follow
Oh you think that you know me
That's why I'm leaving you lonely
Cause baby you don't know a thing about me
You don't know a thing about me
You ain't got the right to tell me
When and where to go, no right to tell me
Acting like you own me lately
Yeah baby you don't know a thing about me
You don't know a thing about me
Mr. Play your games
Only got yourself to blame
When you want me back again
But I ain't fallin' back again
Cause I'm livin' my truth without your lies
Let's be clear baby this is goodbye
I ain't comin' back tomorrow
Oh you think that you know me
That's why I'm leaving you lonely
Cause baby you don't know a thing about me
You don't know a thing about me
You ain't got the right to tell me
When and where to go, no right to tell me
Acting like you own me lately
Yeah baby you don't know a thing about me
You don't know a thing about me
So what you've got the world at your feet
And you know everything about everything
But you don't
You still think I'm comin' back but baby you'll see
Oh you think that you know me
That's why I'm leaving you lonely
Cause baby you don't know a thing about me
You don't know a thing about me
You ain't got the right to tell me
When and where to go, no right to tell me
Acting like you own me lately
Yeah baby you don't know a thing about me
You don't know a thing about me
Mr. Know it all
Well ya think you know it all
But ya don't know a thing at all
Yeah baby you don't know a thing about me
You don't know a thing about me