It's over, it's over, it's over...
It seems you can't hear me
When I open my mouth you never listen
You say stay, but what does that mean
Do you think I honestly want to be reminded forever?
Don't waste your time trying to fix
What I want to erase
What I need to forget
Don't waste your time on me my friend
Friend, what does that even mean
I don't want your hand
You'll only pull me down
So save your breath
Don't waste your song on me, on me
Don't waste your time
It's not easy not answering
Every time I want to talk to you
But I can't
If you only knew the hell I put myself through
Replaying memories in my head of you and I
Every night
Don't waste your time trying to fix
What I want to erase
What I need to forget
Don't waste your time on me my friend
Friend, what does that even mean
I don't want your hand
You'll only pull me down
So save your breath
Don't waste your song on me, on me
Don't waste your time
You're calling
You're talking
You're trying
Trying to get in
But it's over, it's over
It's over, friend
Don't waste your time trying to fix it
So save your breath
Don't waste your song on me, on me
Don't waste your time
You held me
You felt me
You left me
But it's over, it's over, it's over
You touched me
You had me
But it's over, it's over
It's over, my friend
Don't waste my time