I will not make the same mistakes that you did
I will not let myself cause my heart so much misery
I will not break the way you did
You fell so hard...
I've learned the hard way
To never let it get that far
Because of you
I never stray too far from the sidewalk
I learned to play on the safe side So I don't get hurt
Because of you
I find it hard to trust Not only me
But everyone around me
Because of you
I am afraid
I lose my way
And it's not too long before you point it out
I cannot cry
Because I know that's weakness in your eyes
I'm forced to fake a smile, a laugh
Every day of my life
My heart can't possibly break
When it wasn't even whole to start with
Because of you
I never stray too far from the sidewalk
I learned to play on the safe side So I don't get hurt
Because of you
I find it hard to trust Not only me
But everyone around me
Because of you
I am afraid
I watched you die, I heard you cry
Every night in your sleep
I was so young
You should have known better than to lean on me
You never thought of anyone else You just saw your pain
And now I cry In the middle of the night
For the same damn thing
Because of you
I never stray too far from the sidewalk
I learned to play on the safe side So I don't get hurt
Because of you
I tried my hardest just to forget everything
I don't know how to let anyone else in
Because of you
I'm ashamed of my life because it's empty
I am afraid
Because of you