Everybody's talkin'
But they don't say a thing
They look at me with sad eyes
but I don't want the sympathy
It's cool you didn't want me
Sometimes you can't go back
Why'd you have to go and make a mess like that?
Well I Just have to say
Before I let go...
Have you ever been low?
Have you ever had a friend that let you down so?
When the truth came out
Were you the last to know?
Were you left out in the cold?
What you did was low
No I don't need your number
There's nothing left to say
'Cept I never thought it'd hurt this much to be safe
My friends are outside waiting
I've gotta go
Have you ever been low? (have you ever been)
Have you ever had a friend let you down so?
When the truth came out
Were you the last to know?
Were you left out in the cold?
'Cause what you did was low
What you did was low
I walk out of this darkness
With no sense of regret
And I'm going on precautious
We both know that you can't say that
This to show
For all the time I loved you so
So...
Have you ever been low? (have you ever been)
Have you ever had a friend that let you down so?
When the truth came out
Were you the last to know?
Were you left out in the cold?
'Cause what you did was low
Have you ever been low? (have you ever been)
Have you ever had a friend that let you down so?
When the truth came out
Were you the last to know?
Were you left out in the cold?
'Cause what you did was low
Have you ever been low? (have you ever been)
Have you ever had a friend that let you down so?
'Cause what you did was low...
END