You've been doing this hell
for how many years?
2 years
That's was the long
that did you give yourself
Doing this scene,
doing well?
I don't know.
I never thought
I'd be doing it for two years even
Just soot for the stars
if it feels right
Then aim for my heart
if you feel like
Take me away
and make it okay
I swear
I'll behave
You wanted control,
so we waited
I put on a show,
now I make it
You say I'm a kid,
my ego is big
I don't give
a shit
And it
goes like this
Take me by the tongue
and I'll know you
Kiss me 'til you're drunk
and I'll show you
All
the moves like Jagger
I've got
I don't need to try
to control you
Look into my eyes
and I'll own you
With them
moves like Jagger
I've got
the moves like Jagger
Maybe it's hard
when you feel like
You're broken
and scarred
Nothing feels right
But
when you're with me,
I'll
make you believe
That
I've got the key
So get in the car,
we can ride it
Wherever you want,
get inside it
And you wanna steer,
but I'm shifting gears
I'll take it
from here
And it
goes like this
Take me by the tongue
and I'll know you
Kiss me 'til you're drunk
and I'll show you
All
the moves like Jagger
I've got
I don't need to try
to control you
Look into my eyes
and I'll own you
With them
moves like Jagger
I've got
the moves like Jagger
You wanna know
how to make me smile
Take control,
own me just for the night
And if I share my secret,
you're gonna have to keep it
Nobody else
can see this
So watch and learn,
I won't show you twice
Head to toe,
baby rub me right
If I share my secret,
you're gonna have to keep it
Nobody else
can see this
And it
goes like this
Take me by the tongue
and I'll know you
Kiss me 'til you're drunk
and I'll show you
All
the moves like Jagger
I've got
I don't need to try
to control you
Look into my eyes
and I'll own you
With them
moves like Jagger
I've got
the moves like Jagger
I think
we're pretty much set up
For at least
another year