I'm outta time and all I got is 4 minutes
4 minutes eh
Breakdown come on
Come on
Come on boy I've been waiting for
somebody to pick up my stroll
Now don't waste time, give me desire,
tell me how you wanna roll
I want somebody to speed it up for me
then take it down slow
There's enough room for both
Girl I can hit you back just gotta
show me where it's at
Are you ready to go? (Are you ready to go?)
If you want it
You've already got it
If you thought it
It better be what you want
If you feel it
It must be real just
Say the word and
I'ma give you what you want
Time is waiting
We only got four minutes to save the world
No hesitating
Grab a boy
Go grab your girl
Time is waiting
We only got four minutes to save the world
No hesitating
We only got four minutes huh four minutes
So keep it up keep it up
Don't be afraid
Madonna
You gotta get em a heart
Tick tock tick tock tick tock
That's right keep it up keep it up
Don't be afraid
Madonna
You gotta get em a heart
Tick tock tick tock tick tock
Sometimes I think what I need is a you intervention
Yeah
And I know I can tell that you like it and that it's good
By the way that you move
Oh hey
The road to heaven is paved with good intentions
Yeah
But if I die tonight at least I can say
I did what I wanted to do
Tell me how 'bout you?
If you want it
You've already got it
If you thought it
It better be what you want
If you feel it
It must be real just
Say the word and
I'ma give you what you want
Time is waiting
We only got four minutes to save the world
No hesitating
Grab a boy
Go grab your girl
Time is waiting
We only got four minutes to save the world
No hesitating
We only got four minutes huh four minutes
So keep it up keep it up
Don't be afraid
Madonna
You gotta get em a heart
Tick tock tick tock tick tock
Breakdown
Yeah
Tick tock tick tock tick tock
I've only got four minutes to save the world