Come here
Let me take you on a trip
Leaving in the name of love
Silence and emptiness
You're among a billion stars
Please don't say a single word
All around the galaxy
Silence and emptiness
Let's go into space
Heading for Venus
Fly around the Sun
Playmate to Jesus
Everywhere I go, I pray
For universal love
High above the sky
Closer to Heaven
Here among the stars
All is forgiven
Everywhere I go, I pray
For universal love
I'm hearing nothing - is it me or is it you?
I keep on trying but you're just not coming through
I see your signal but I keep on losing it
I'll find your frequency bit by bit
Forgive me
Please, forgive the things I've done
Every little matters here
Life keeps moving on
Everlasting energy
Shining all over me
Falling into gravity
Silence and emptiness
Let's go into space
Heading for Venus
Fly around the Sun
Playmate to Jesus
Everywhere I go, I pray
For universal love
High above the sky
Closer to Heaven
Here among the stars
All is forgiven
Everywhere I go, I pray
For universal love
(Can you hear me?) I'm hearing nothing - is it me or is it you?
(Can you hear me?) I keep on trying but you're just not coming through
(Can you hear me?) I see your signal but I keep on losing it
(Can you hear me?) I'll find your frequency bit by bit
Love spreads love - forevermore
Fear spreads fear - the Devil's core
Take my hand and follow me
It's magical
This moment's gonna change my life
(Can you hear me?) Love spreads love - forevermore
(Can you hear me?) Fear spreads fear - the Devil's core
(Can you hear me?) Take my hand and follow me
(Can you hear me?) It's magical - so here we go
Let's go into space
Heading for Venus
Fly around the Sun
Playmate to Jesus
Everywhere I go, I pray
For universal love
High above the sky
Closer to Heaven
Here among the stars
All is forgiven
Everywhere I go, I pray
For universal love
(Can you hear me?) I'm hearing nothing - is it me or is it you?
(Can you hear me?) I keep on trying but you're just not coming through
(Can you hear me?) I see your signal but I keep on losing it
(Can you hear me?) I'll find your frequency bit by bit
Life keeps moving on (Love) (Love)
Life keeps moving on (Love)