Back in the Ronald Reagan days
When we put sattelites in space
When boys wore skinny leather ties
Like Don Johnson from Miami Vice
When M&M was just a snack
And Michael Jacksons skin was black
Back when the coolest thing in store
Was a Commodore 64
Back to the 80's
Back to Soap
Back to Rocky and Cherry Coke
Those were the days
And we go
Back to the 80's
And hey there Mr.T
To Twisted Sisters on MTV, yeah
Those were the days
I come back
To Iron Maiden and 7UP (I come back)
Bananarama and Breakfast Club
Come Back, Yeah
I Come Back
When Huey Lewis was the news
When we went flying with Tom Cruise
When shoulderpads and looking tough
Lost a dare to David Hasselhof
To many men with heavy makeup on
To many poodles with guitars
Thanks for all the joy you've given us
You will always be our superstars
Back to the 80's
Back to Soap
Back to Rocky and Cherry Coke
Those were the days
And we go
Back to the 80's
And hey there Mr.T
To Twisted Sisters on MTV, yeah
Those were the days
I come back
To Iron Maiden and 7UP (I come back)
Bananarama and Breakfast Club
Come Back, Yeah
I Come Back
Hooray for Cosby and Rubicks Cube
Hooray for Dynasty and Moon Boots
Hooray for Devo and Barber Curls
Hooray for Poltergeist and Barbie Girls
Back to the 80's
Back to Soap
Back to Rocky and Cherry Coke
Those were the days
Lets go back
Back to the 80's
To Mr.T
To Twisted Sisters on MTV, yeah
Those were the days
I come back
To Iron Maiden and 7UP (I come back)
Bananarama and Breakfast Club
Come Back, Yeah
Lets go back