How r u doing?
Party
It's time do it
It's time to tell us how to queue it
We're gonna pop what's in the bottle
Gonna rock what's in the shuttle
All the love, we're gonna spread it
(spread it)
How r u doing?
Hey girls, let's get it on,
let's get it on till we got it
Gotta lose the distance
that we got until we rock it
Tonight we're gonna share
a secret invitation
Love generation, love generation
We wanna know now
if you're feeling alive
are you ready tonight?
It's time to party
'cause the feeling is right
We wanna know now
are you ready to go-oh-oh-oh?
How R U doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Wanna get to know you,
tell us how r u doing?
How R U doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Let's bring it all together,
how r u doing tonight?
First step is taken when you say it
(say it, say it)
It's time to show what's in the pocket
Gonna shake what's in the rocket
All our love will turn to magic
(magic, come closer)
How r u doing?
It's time to pick it up
to put it down in words, yeah
Gotta stop believing that
no one's gonna hurt ya
Tonight we'll get it out
with best, best intentions
Love generation, love generation
We wanna know now
if you're feeling alive
are you ready tonight?
It's time to party
'cause the feeling is right
We wanna know now
are you ready to go-oh-oh-oh?
How r u doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Wanna get to know you,
tell us how r u doing?
How r u doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Wanna bring it all together,
how r u doin?
How r u doing?
How r u doing? Love
How r u doing? Love generation
Are you ready to go-oh-oh,
go-oh-oh, go-oh-oh-oh?
How r u doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Wanna get to know you,
tell us how r u doing?
How r u doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Let's bring it all together,
how r u doing?
We wanna know now
if you're feeling alive
are you ready tonight?
It's time to party
'cause the feeling is right
We wanna know now
are you ready to go-oh-oh-oh?
How r u doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Wanna get to know you,
tell us how r u doing?
How r u doing girl?
How r u doing boy?
Let's bring it all together
How r u doing?