I've been walking
In the same way as I did
Missing out
The cracks in the pavement
And tutting my heel
And strutting my feet
Is there anything
I can do for you dear?
Is there anyone I could call?
No and thank you, please Madam
I ain't lost, just wandering
Round my hometown
Memories are fresh
Ooh, the people I've met
Are the wonders of my world
Are the wonders of this world
I like it in the city
When the air
Is so thick and opaque
I love to see everybody
In short skirts
Shorts and shades
I like it in the city
When two worlds collide
You get the people
And the government
Everybody taking
Different sides
Shows that
We ain't gonna stand shit
Shows
That we are united
That we ain't gonna take it
Shows
That we ain't gonna stand shit
Shows that we are united
Round my hometown
Memories are fresh
Ooh the people I've met
Are the wonders of my world
Are the wonders of this world