Have a baby by me,
Baby! Be a millionaire
Be a millionaire,
Have a baby by me,
Baby! Be a millionaire
Be a millionaire,
Imma play no games,
When I'm
in that thang
Come show
what I mean
Come see what I mean,
you see what I mean
I said Lil' Mama put me on,
baby put me on
Bet I'm gon
have you gone
See what I mean
First is her neck,
yea then her back
Yeah I'm a freak,
I get in all that
Girl I perform for you,
like a pornostar
'Til you had enough,
I just needed a little bit more
New music,
new mood, new position
New erotic sounds,
it's going down now listen
I could hear
your heart beat
Your sweatin
I could paint a perfect picture
I get deeper and deeper,
I told cha I'd get chya
I'd work that,
murk that,
Just the way
you like it baby
Turn a quickie
into an all nighter maybe
Your sexdrive it
match my sexdrive
Then we movin'
as fast as a nascar rides
Switch gears slow down,
go down, whoa now
You could feel every inch of it
when we intimate
I'd use my toungue baby,
a little sprung maybe
I had your head spinnin'
sayin' 50 so crazy
Imma play no games,
when I'm
in that thang
Come show
what I mean
Come see what I mean,
you see what I mean
I said Lil' Mama put me on,
baby put me on
Bet I'm gon
have you gone,
See what I mean
Have a baby by me,
Baby! Be a millionaire
Be a millionaire,
Have a baby by me,
Baby! Be a millionaire
Be a millionaire,
Girl I want you to give me,
what you got and gimme more?
Baby you could start
on top or on fours
You know I like it,
when you get in to it
Don't nobody do it,
uh like I do it
Feel a rush
from my touch
Get intoxicated,
drunk off my love
Call it
hennessy thug
Passion you laughin',
I make you smilin' on the regular
Tell me what you want shawty
thats what imma get you
I need you to be
what I need more than liquor and weed
I need you to make,
me a seed
I need you to give me
a reason to breath
I need you I'm tellin'
this so u know what I need
I'd be a part time,
a full time lover,
A signifcant other
Don't matter which way it go,
I'm, oh ,so gutta
Girl you could get it
however you want, get it,
I'm feeling you still feelin you
right now, get it
Imma play no games,
When I'm
in that thang
Come show
what I mean
Come see what I mean,
you see what I mean
I said Lil' Mama put me on,
baby put me on
Bet I'm gon
have you gone
See what I mean
Have a baby by me,
Baby! Be a millionaire
Be a millionaire,
Have a baby by me,
Baby! Be a millionaire
Be a millionaire,
Have a baby by me,
Baby! Be a millionaire
Be a millionaire,