Somebody gimme a bass line
Yeah that's tight
Jay drop the drums right here
Think we missin' something dog, I got it
Put some horns right here
Ooooohhhh that's right
Give her what she wants ooooohhhh ha
Give her what she wants oh give her what she wants
I see you looking, at what you see
Boy, now don't be shy ain't nothin' but facin' opportunity
She's right you know, (uh, hah) She's right (ahh)
(Man) She's right you know, (uh, hah)She's right(owwww!)
You stand there looking at me (at me)
I stand here looking at you girl (at you boy)
You know exactly what's on my mind (yeah yeah)
It's just the way that i see
You came here looking for me
But I don't do this type of thing all the time
(you want me to) come here boy
I got a little something for ya
Got a liitle bit, can't i get a little bit (yeah yeah)
And i don't know-oo, what it is but I just wanna get to know ya,
(alright, alright, yeah yeah)
I need you to dance... all night
Tilt ya head back, take it down now
Bring it back up slowly
I need you to dance... all night
Tilt ya head back, take it down now
Bring it back up slowly
Now situations, girl they often change
Listen to me
Sometimes for the good and sometimes for the bad
But who's to blame?
He's right you know, (uh, hah) He's right (ahh)
(Baby girl) He's right you know, (uh, hah) He's right (oww!)
You stand there looking at me (at me)
I stand here looking at you girl (at you boy)
You know exactly what's on my mind (yeah yeah)
It's just the way that I see
You came here looking for me
But i don't do this type of thing all the time (yeah)
(you want me to) come here boy
I got a little something for ya
Got a little bit, can't I get a little bit (yeah yeah)
And I don't know-oo, what it is but I just wanna get to know ya,
(alright, alright, yeah yeah)
I need you to dance... all night
Tilt ya head back, take it down now
Bring it back up slowly
I need you to dance... all night
Tilt ya head back, take it down now
Bring it back up slowly
Hustle for me, (hustle, hustle)
Hustle for me, Yeah.....
You've got some nerve,
Thinkin your so--
I got a little bit of that, a little bit of this
Little bit of rap, with a little bit of bitch
You stand there looking at me (at me)
I stand here looking at you girl (at you boy)
You know exactly what's on my mind (yeah yeah)
It's just the way that I see
You came here looking for me
But I don't do this type of thing all the time
(you want me to) come here boy
I got a little something for ya
Got a little bit, can't I get a little bit (yeah yeah)
And I don't know-oo, what it is but I just wanna get to know ya,
(alright, alright, yeah yeah)
I need you to dance... all night
Tilt ya head back, take it down now
Bring it back up slowly
I need you to dance... all night
Tilt ya head back, take it down now
Bring it back up slowly
Nelly, Nelly you make me so sweaty baby