Where's all mah soul sistas
Lemme hear ya'll flow sistas
Hey sista, go sista, soul sista, flow sista
Hey sista, go sista, soul sista, go sista
He met Marmalade down IN old Moulin Rouge
Struttin' her stuff on the street
She said, Hello, hey Jo, you wanna give it a go? Oh! uh huh
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya dada (Hey hey hey)
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya here (here)
Mocha Chocalata ya ya (oh yea)
Creole lady Marmalade
What What, What what
ooh oh
Voulez vous coucher avec moi ce soir
Voulez vous coucher avec moi
Lil' Kim: yea yea yea yea
Pink: He sat in her boudoir while she freshened up
Boy drank all that Magnolia wine
All her black satin sheets, suede's, dark greens
yeah
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya dada (da-da-da)
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya here (here ohooh yea yeah)
Mocha Choca lata ya ya (yea)
Creole lady Marmalade
Voulez vous coucher avec moi ce soir (ce soir, what what what)
Voulez vous coucher avec moi
yea yea uh
He come through with the money and the garter bags
I let him know we bout that cake straight up the gate uh
We independent women, some mistake us for whores
I'm sayin¡, why spend mine when I can spend yours
Disagree? Well that's you and I'm sorry
Imma keep playing these cats out like Atari
Wear ideal shoes get love from the dudes
4 bad ass chicks from the Moulin Rouge
hey sistas, soul sistas, betta get that dough sistas
We drink wine with diamonds in the glass
bottle case the meaning of expensive taste
if you wanna Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya
Mocha Chocalate-a what?
Real Lady Marmalade
One more time C'mon now
Marmalade... Lady Marmalade... Marmalade...
hey Hey Hey!
Touch of her skin feeling silky smooth
color of cafe au lait alright
Made the savage beast inside roar until he cried,
More-more-more
Now he's back home doin' 9 to 5
Sleepin' the grey flannel life
But when he turns off to sleep memories creep,
More-more-more
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya dada (da daeaea yea)
Giuchie, Giuchie, ya ya here (ooh)
Mocha Choca lata ya ya (yea)
Creole lady Marmalade
Voulez vous coucher avec moi ce soir (ce soir)
Voulez vous coucher avec moi (all my sistas yea)
Voulez vous coucher avec moi (C¡®Mon! uh)
Christina...(oh Leaeaa Oh)
Pink... (Lady Marmalade)
Lil' Kim...(hey Hey! uh uh uh uh...)
Mya...(Oh Oh oooo)
Rot wailer baby...(baby)
Moulin Rouge... (0h)
Misdemeanor here...
Creole Lady Marmalade Yes-ah......