I've got trouble trouble trouble, always knockin at my door.
Yes I'm a whole lot of trouble baby,
like a kid in a candy store.
I've got nothin but trouble babe,
not since the day that I was born.
(Do your thang honey)
I could feel it from the start
Couldn't stand to be apart
Somethin bout ya caught my eye
Somethin moved me deep inside
I don't know what you did boy but you had it
And I've been hooked ever since
I told my mother, my brother, my sister and my friends
Told the others, my lovers from past and present tense
That every time I see you everything starts making sense
(Do your thang honey)
Ain't no other man can stand up next to you
Ain't no other man on the planet does what you do
You're the kinda guy a girl finds in a blue moon
You got soul, you got class,
you got style with your bad ass
Ain't no other man, it's true
Ain't no other man but you
Never thought I'd be alright, no no no
Til you came and changed my life, yeah yeah yeah
What was cloudy now is clear, yeah yeah
You're the light that I needed
You got what I want boy and I want it
So keep on givin' it up
So tell your mother, your brother,
your sister and your friends
And the others, your lovers, better not be present tense
Cause I want everyone to know that
you are mine and no one else's
Ain't no other man can stand up next to you
Ain't no other man on the planet does what you do
You're the kinda guy a girl finds in a blue moon
You got soul, you got class,
you got style with your bad ass
Ain't no other man, it's true
Ain't no other man but you
(Break it down now)
Ain't no other, ain't, ain't no other other
Ain't no other, ain't, ain't no other lover
Ain't no other, I-I-I need no other
Ain't no other man but you
You are there when I'm a mess
Talk me down from every ledge
Give me strength, boy you're the best
You're the only one who's ever passed every test
WwW.Farsi-Lyrics.Ir
Ain't no other man can stand up next to you
Ain't no other man on the planet does what you do
You're the kinda guy a girl finds in a blue moon
You got soul, you got class, you got style with your bad ass
Ain't no other man, it's true
Ain't no other man but you
And now im telling you said aint no other man but you
Ain't no other man can stand up next to you
Ain't no other man on the planet does what you do
You're the kinda guy a girl finds in a blue moon
You got soul, you got class, you got style with your bad ass
Ain't no other man, it's true
Ain't no other man but you
I've got trouble trouble trouble, always knockin at my door.
Yes I'm a whole lot of trouble baby,
like a kid in a candy store.
I've got nothin but trouble babe,
not since the day that I was born.