Oh Sometimes I get a good feeling yeah
Oh I get a feeling that I never, never, never never had before no, no
And I just wanna tell you right now
I believe, I really do believe that
Something's got a hold on me
(Oh, it must be love)
Something's got a hold on me right now child
(Yeah, it must be love)
Let me tell you now
I got a feeling, I feel so strange
Everything about me seems tu have changed
Step by step, I got a brand new walk
I even sound sweeter when I walk
I said, Oh (Oh) Oh (Oh)
Oh (Oh) Oh (Oh)
I say baby, oh, it must be love
(You know it must be love)
Let me tell you now
Something's got a hold on me, yeah
(Oh, it must be love)
Something's got a hold on me right now child
Let me tell you now
I've never felt like this before
Something's got a hold on me that won´t let go
I believe I'd die if I only could
I feel so strange, but I sure feel good
I said, Oh (Oh) Oh (Oh)
Oh (Oh) Oh (Oh)
I say baby, oh, it must be love
(You know it must be love)
Let me tell you now
My heart feels over, my feet feel light
I shake all over, but I feel alright
I never felt like this befoer
Something's got a hold on me that won't let go
I never thought it could happen to me
Got me heavy when I'm in misery
i never thought it could be this way
Love's sure gonna put a hurting on me
I said, oh (Oh), oh (Oh) , oh (OH) , oh (Oh)
I say baby it must be love
(You know it must be love)
Yeah you know it walks like love
He talk like love
(You know he talks like love)
Make me feel alright
(Make me feel alright)
In the middle of the night
(In the middle of the night)
La, la, la
(La, la, la)