when i'm lost
in the rain
in your eyes i know
i'll find the light
to light my way
when i'm scared
losing ground
when my world is going crazy
you can turn it all around
and when i'm down you're there
pushing me to the top
you're always there
giving me all you've got
for a shield
from the storm
for a friend
for a love
to keep me safe and warm
i turn to you
for the strength
to be strong
for the will to carry on
for everything you do
for everything that's true
i turn to you
when i lose
the will to win
i just reach for you and
i can reach the sky again
i can do
anything
cause your love is so amazing
cause your love inspires me
and when i need a friend
you're always on my side
giving me faith
that gets me through the night
for a shield
from the storm
for a friend
for a love
to keep me safe and warm
i turn to you
for the strength
to be strong
for the will to carry on
for everything you do
i turn to you
for the arms to be my shelter
through all the rain
for truth that
will never change
for someone to lean on
for a heart i can
rely on through anything
for that one who
i can run to
for a shield
from the storm
for a friend
for a love
to keep me safe and warm
i turn to you
for the strength
to be strong
for the will to carry on
for everything you do
for everything that's true
i turn to you