come on, come on
oh,ooh,ohh...
a century I've been in solitude
trapped wanting to escape
dreaming that someone
releases me
you blow me a kiss
i want to love you
but there's a price
you'll have to pay
for me to give myself away
oh oh oh oh oh
my body says i want to
but my soul is afraid
if you want me next to you
rub right and you will see
like a released genie
i will make your dreams reality
if you want me next to you
to win my heart
three wishes i will grant you (oh yeah)
if you swear your love to me
like a trapped genie i wait
to be free with your sincere love
come, come, to remove me from here
dancing the passion dominates us
our impulses out of control
it's so difficult to contain ourselves
you think today it might happen
but i know that nothing will happen
you have to love me (you have to love me)
oh oh oh oh oh
my body says i want to
but my soul is afraid
if you want me next to you
rub right and you will see
like a released genie
i will make your dreams reality
if you want me next to you
to win my heart
three wishes i will grant you (oh yeah)
if you swear your love to me
like a trapped genie i wait
to be free with your sincere love
come, come, to remove me from here
like a trapped genie i wait
to be free with your sincere love
(if you want me next to you)
like a trapped genie i wait
come, come, to remove me from here
oh oh oh oh oh
my body says i want to
but my soul is afraid
if you want me next to you
rub my lamp right
like a released genie
(i'm a trapped genie)
i will make your dreams reality
if you want me next to you(ooh)
to win my heart
three wishes i will grant you
if you swear your love to me
(if you swear your love to me)
if you want me next to you
(if you want me next to you)
rub right and you will see
like a released genie
(ohhh,yeah ohh, love)
i will make your dreams reality
if you want me next to you
(trapped baby)
to win my heart
three wishes i will grant you
if you swear your love to me
like a trapped genie i wait
come, come, to remove me from here