Come On over, come on over baby
Hey boy, don't you know
I got something going on
I got an invitation
Don't you keep me waiting all night long
I know, you know
So baby don't
Pretend you won't
Keep me guessing with ya
You will, or you won't
Don't wanna play the game with you, baby
So listen to me....
All I want is you
Come over here baby
You know you make me go crazy
All I want is you
Now baby don't be shy
You better cross the line
I'm gonna love you right
'cause all I want is you...
Come on over, come on over baby
Come On over, come on over baby
I'm not just talking
About your sexuality
But I can't help myself
When you put your hands on me
It's paradise
When you and I
Get close, skin tight
When I wanna I wanna
Go on all night
I wanna play that game with ya baby
Listen to me...
All I want is you
Come over here baby
You know you make me go crazy
All I want is you
Now baby don't be shy
You better cross the line
I'm gonna love you right
'cause all I want is you...
Come on over, come on over baby
Come on over, come on over
Don't ya wanna be the one tonight?
We can do exactly what you like
Don't ya wanna be just you and me?
We can do what comes naturally
I got a thing for you
Got my mind made up
And I'm serious
Never been more baby
Don't show it but it's real (so sure)
And it' right here
Come on, Come on, Come on, over
You give me
What a girl feels
What a girl likes
What a girl needs
What a girl wants
All I
All I want is you
Come over here baby
You know you make me go crazy
All I want is you
Now baby don't be shy
You better cross the line
I'm gonna love you right
'cause all I want is you...
All I want is you
You make me go crazy
Now baby don't be shy
You better cross the line
I'm gonna love you right
'cause all I want is you...