Yeah come on
I wanna thank you
for giving me time to breathe
Like a rock you waited so patiently
While I got it together
While I figured it out
I only looked but I never touched
'Cause in my heart
was a picture of us
Holdin' hands, makin' plans
and it's lucky for me you understand
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Whatever makes me happy sets you free
And I'm thanking you
for knowing exactly
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Whatever keeps me in your arms
And I'm thanking you
for giving it to me
What I want is what you got
And what you got is what I want
There was a time I was blind
I was so confused
Run away just to hide it all from you
But baby you knew me better,
than I knew myself
They say if you love something
let it go
If it comes back it's yours
That's how you know
It's for keeps, yeah,
it's for sure
And you're ready and willin'
To give me more than
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Whatever makes me happy sets you free
And I'm thanking you
for knowin' exactly
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Whatever keeps me in your arms
And I'm thanking you
for givin' to me
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Somebody sensitive,
crazy, sexy, cool like you
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
(It's all right)
(It's okay)
You let a girl know
how much you care about her
I swear you're the one who always knew
You knew
Ooh, oh I'm thanking you
for being there for me
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Whatever keeps me in your arms
is what I need
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Whatever makes me happy sets you free
And I'm thanking you for knowin' exactly
What a girl wants
What a girl needs
Whatever keeps me in your arms
And I'm thanking you for givin' it
Oh baby, oh darlin'
Thank you, thank you for giving me
What I want
And what I need