You know,
Tonight I'm feeling a little out of control
Is this me? You want to get crazy?
'Cause I don't give a (Ow)
I'm out of character, I'm in rare form
And if you really knew me
You'd know it's not the norm
Cause I'm doing things that I normally won't do
The old me's gone, I feel brand new
And if you don't like it, fuck you
The music's on and I'm dancing
I'm normally in the corner just standing
I'm feeling unusual
I don't care 'cause this is my night
I'm not myself tonight
Tonight I'm not the same girl, same girl
I'm dancing a lot and I'm taking shots
And I'm feeling fine
I'm kissing all the boys and the girls
Someone call the doctor 'cause I lost my mind
Cause I'm doing things that I normally won't do
The old me's gone, I feel brand new
And if you don't like it, fuck you
The music's on and I'm dancing
I'm normally in the corner just standing
I'm feeling unusual
I don't care 'cause this is my night
I'm not myself tonight
Tonight I'm not the same girl, same girl
Tonight I'm not the same girl
(One, two, three, four)
In the morning, when I wake up
I go back to the girl I used to be
But baby, not tonight
I'm not myself tonight
Tonight I'm not the same girl, same girl
That feels good, I needed that
Get crazy, let's go
That's right, come on
Give it to me now
Don't stop