English Subtitle: But I Remember You
Now that my life is normal
Now that I got someone in home
how dreams with me coming
Now I can say that I am ok.
Now that I am good.
Now with the time I could get over
That love that almost kill me
Now there is no pain
Now at last It is my again
But I remember you
And again i loose my peace
And my hart destroys.
But I remember you
And my smiles erases
And my world destroys.
Ooh, oh, hey
Now that my future begins to shine
Now that got my security back
Now there is no more pain
Now at last its me again
But I remember you
And again i loose my peace
And my hart destroys.
But I remember you
And my smiles erases
And my world destroys.
Oh, oh, whoa
But I remember you
Oh no, no
And my hart destroys.
But I remember you
my smiles erases
my world destroys.
But I remember you
Ooh
But I... but I... but I... but I...
But I remember you
Oh, whoa
But I remember you...