I feel like I've been locked up tight
For a century of lonely nights
Waiting for someone to release me
You're licking your lips
And blowing kisses my way
But that don't mean I'm gonna give it away
Baby baby baby (baby baby baby)
Ooooh
My body's saying lets go
But my heart is saying no
If you wanna be with me
Baby there's a price to pay
I'm a genie in a bottle
You gotta rub me the right way
If you wanna be with me
I can make your wish come true
You gotta make a big impression
I gotta like what you do
I'm a genie in a bottle baby
Gotta rub me the right way honey
Come, come, come on and let me out
The music's playing
The light's down low
Just one more dance
And then we're good to go
Waiting for someone
Who needs me
Hormones racing at the speed of light
But that don't mean its gotta be tonight
Baby, baby, baby (baby, baby, baby)
Ooooh
My body's saying lets go
But my heart is saying no
If you wanna be with me
Baby there's a price to pay
I'm a genie in a bottle (I'm a genie in a bottle)
You gotta rub me the right way
If you wanna be with me (Ooh)
I can make your wish come true
(Wish come true, woah...)
Just come and set me free
And I'll be with you
I'm a genie in a bottle baby
You gotta rub me the right way honey
Come, come, come on and let me out
I'm a genie in a bottle baby
Gotta rub me the right way honey
(If you wanna be with me)
I'm a genie in a bottle baby
Come, come, come on and let me out
Ooooh
My body's saying let's go
But my heart is saying no
If you wanna be with me
Baby there's a price to pay
I'm a genie in a bottle
You gotta rub me the right way
If you wanna be with me
I can make your wish come true (Ooh)
You gotta make a big impression
I gotta like what you do (Oh yeah)
If you wanna be with me
Baby there's a price to pay
I'm a genie in a bottle
You gotta rub me the right way
(you gotta rub me the right way)
If you wanna be with me
I can make your wish come true
Just come and set me free baby
And I'll be with you
I'm a genie in a bottle baby
Come, come, come on in