Are you aware of
what you make me feel, baby?
Right now I feel
invisible to you
Like I'm not real
Didn't you feel me
lock my arms around you?
Why'd you
turn away?
Here's what
I have to say
I was left
to cry there
Waiting
outside there
Grinning with
the lost stare
That's
when I decided
Why should
I care?
'Cause you
weren't there
When I was scared
I was so alone
You, you need
to listen
I'm starting
to trip
I'm losing
my grip
And I'm in this
thing alone
Am I just some chick
you place beside you
to take
somebody's place?
When you turn around
can you recognize my face?
You used
to love me
to hug me
But that
wasn't the case
Everything
wasn't ok
I was left
to cry there
Waiting
outside there
Grinning
with the lost stare
That's
when I decided
Why should
I care?
'Cause you
weren't there
When I was scared
I was so alone
You, you need
to listen
I'm starting
to trip
I'm losing
my grip
And I'm in this
thing alone
Crying out loud
I'm crying out loud
Open your eyes
Open up wide
Why should
I care?
'Cause you
weren't there
When
I was scared
I was so alone
Why should
I care?
'Cause you
weren't there
When
I was scared
I was so alone
Why should
I care?
If you
don't care
Then I
We're not
going anywhere
Why should
I care?
'Cause you
weren't there
When
I was scared
I was so alone
Why should
I care?
If you
don't care
Then I
We're not
going anywhere
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo