You're so good to me, baby, baby
I wanna lock you up in my closet
When no one's around
I wanna put your hand in my pocket
Because you're allowed
I wanna drive you into the corner
And kiss you without a sound
I wanna stay this way forever
I'll say it loud
Now you're in and you can't get out
You make me so hot
Make me wanna drop
You're so ridiculous
I can barely stop
I can hardly breathe
You make me wanna scream
You're so fabulous \Nyou're so good to me, baby, baby
You're so good to me, baby, baby
I can make you feel all better
Just take it in
And I can show you all the places
You've never been
And I can make you say everything
That you never said
And I will let you do anything
Again and again
Now you're in and you can't get out
You make me so hot
Make me wanna drop
You're so ridiculous
I can barely stop
I can hardly breathe
You make me wanna scream
You're so fabulous \Nyou're so good to me, baby, baby
You're so good to me, baby, baby
Kiss me gently, always I know
Hold me, love me
Don't ever go, oh oh oh
Yeah!
You make me so hot
Make me wanna drop
You're so ridiculous
I can barely stop
I can hardly breathe
You make me wanna scream
You're so fabulous \Nyou're so good to me
You make me so hot
Make me wanna drop
You're so ridiculous
I can barely stop
I can hardly breathe
You make me wanna scream
You're so fabulous \Nyou're so good to me, baby, baby
You're so good to me, baby, baby
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo