You held my hand and
walked me home,
I know
While you gave me that kiss,
it was something like this,
It made me go
You wiped my tears,
got rid of all my fears,
why did you
have to go?
Guess it wasn't enough
to take up some of my love
Guys are
so hard to trust
Did I not tell you
that I'm not like that
Girl the one
who gives it all away
Did you think that I was gonna
give it up to you,
This time?
Did you think that it was something
I was gonna tell
And cry?
Don't try to
tell me what to do,
tell me what to say,
You're better
off that way
Don't think that you're charming
the fact that your arm
Is now
around my neck
Will get you in my pants
I'll have to kick your ass
And make you
never forget
I'm gonna ask you to stop.
Thought I liked you a lot,
but I'm really upset
Really upset
So get out of my head,
get off of my bed
yeah that's
what I said
Did I not tell you
that I'm not like that
Girl the one
who throws it all away?
Did you think that I was gonna
give it up to you,
this time?
Did you think that it was something
I was gonna tell
And cry?
Don't try to
tell me what to do,
tell me what to say,
You're better
off that way
This guilt trip that
you put me on won't
Mess me up
I've done no wrong
Any thoughts of you and me
have gone away
Did you think that I was gonna
give it up to you,
this time?
Did you think that it was something
I was gonna tell
and cry?
Don't try to
tell me what to do,
tell me what to say,
You're better
off that way
Better off that way
I'm better
off alone anyway
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo