Tripping out
Spinning around
I'm underground
I fell down,
Yeah,
I fell down
I'm freaking out
Where am I now?
Upside down
And
I can't stop it now
It can't stop me now
I'll get by,
I'll survive,
When the world's
crashing down
When I fall
and hit the ground
I will turn
myself around
Don't you try
to stop me
I won't cry
I found myself
in wonderland
Get back on
my feet again
Is this real?
Is this pretend?
I'll take a stand
until the end
I'll get by,
I'll survive,
When the world's
crashing down
When I fall
and hit the ground
I will turn
myself around
Don't you try
to stop me
I won't cry
I'll get by,
I'll survive,
When the world's
crashing down
When I fall
and hit the ground
I will turn
myself around
Don't you try
to stop me
I won't cry
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo