Oh oh , oh oh...
So much for my happy ending.
Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh...
Let's talk this over
It's not like we're dead
Was it something I did?
Was it something You said?
Don't leave me hanging
In a city so dead
Held up so high
On such a breakable thread
You were all the things
I thought I knew
And I thought we could be
You were everything,
everything that I wanted
We were meant to be,
supposed to be, but we lost it.
And all the memories,
so close to me,
just fade away
All this time you
were pretending
So much for
my happy ending.
Oh oh, oh oh...
So much for
my happy ending.
Oh oh, oh oh...
You've got
your dumb friends
I know what they say
They tell you I'm difficult
But so are they
But they don't know me
Do they even know you?
All the things
you hide from me
All the shit that you do
You were all the things
I thought I knew
And I thought
we could be
You were everything,
everything that I wanted.
We were meant to be,
supposed to be,
but we lost it.
And all the memories,
so close to me,
just fade away
All this time
you were pretending
So much for
my happy ending.
It's nice to know
you were there
Thanks for acting
like you cared
And making me feel like
I was the only one.
It's nice to know
we had it all
Thanks for
watching as I fall
And letting me know
we were done.
You were everything,
everything that I wanted
We were meant to be,
supposed to be,
but we lost it
And all the memories,
so close to me,
just fade away
All this time
you were pretending
So much for
my happy ending.
You were everything,
everything that I wanted
We were meant to be,
supposed to be,
but we lost it
And all the memories,
so close to me,
just fade away
All this time
you were pretending
So much for
my happy ending.
Oh oh , oh oh...
So much for
my happy ending.
Oh oh , oh oh...
So much for
my happy ending.
Oh oh , oh oh...
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo