There's not much
going on today
I'm really bored,
it's getting late
What happened
to my Saturday?
Saturday
Monday's coming,
the day I hate
Sit on the bed alone,
staring at the phone
He wasn't what I wanted,
what I thought, no
He wouldn't even
open up the door
He never made me feel
like I was special
He isn't really what
I'm looking for
Hey Hey Hey
This is when I start
to bite my nails
And clean my room
when all else fails
I think it's time
for me to bail
This point of view
is getting stale
Sit on the bed alone,
staring at the phone
He wasn't what I wanted,
what I thought, no
He wouldn't even
open up the door
He never made me feel
like I was special
He isn't really what
I'm looking for
Hey hey hey hey
Na na na na na,
we've all got choices
Na na na na,
we've all got voices
Na na na na na,
stand up make some noise
Na na na na,
Sit on the bed alone,
staring at the phone
He wasn't what I wanted,
what I thought, no
He wouldn't even
open up the door
He never made me feel
like I was special
He isn't really what
I'm looking for
He wasn't what I wanted,
what I thought, no
He wouldn't even
open up the door
He never made me
feel like I was special
Like I was special,
cause I was special
Na na na na
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo