Let me hear
you say hey hey hey
Alright, now let me hear
you say hey hey ho
I hate it when a guy
doesn't get the door
Even though I told him yesterday
and the day before
I hate it when a guy
doesn't get the tab
And I have to pull my money out
and that looks bad
Where are the hopes,
where are the dreams
My Cinderella story scene
When do you think
they'll finally see
That you're not, not, not
gonna get any better
You won't, won't, won't
you won't get rid of me never
Like it or not even though
she's a lot like me
We're not the same
And yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm a lot to handle
You don't know trouble
but I'm a hell of a scandal
Me I'm a scene
I'm a drama queen
I'm the best damn thing
that your eyes have ever seen
Alright, alright,
Yeah
I hate it when a guy
doesn't understand
Why a certain time of month
I don't want to hold his hand
I hate it when they go out
and we stay in
And they come home smelling
like their ex-girlfriend
But I found my hopes
I found my dreams
My Cinderella story scene
Now everybody's gonna see
That you're not, not, not
gonna get any better
You won't, won't, won't
you won't get rid of me never
Like it or not even though
she's a lot like me
We're not the same
And yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm a lot to handle
You don't know trouble
but I'm a hell of a scandal
Me I'm a scene
I'm a drama queen
I'm the best damn thing
that your eyes have ever seen
Give me an A,
always give me what I want
Give me a V,
be very, very good to me
R, are you gonna
treat me right
I, I can put up a fight
Give me an L,
let me hear you scream loud
Let me hear you scream loud
One, two,
three, four
Where are the hopes,
where are the dreams
My Cinderella story scene
When do you think
they'll finally see
That you're not, not, not
gonna get any better
You won't, won't, won't
you won't get rid of me never
Like it or not even though
she's a lot like me
We're not the same
And yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm a lot to handle
You don't know trouble
but I'm a hell of a scandal
Me I'm a scene
I'm a drama queen
I'm the best damn thing
that your eyes have ever seen
Let me hear
you say hey hey hey
Alright, now let me hear
you say hey hey ho
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo
I'm the best damn thing
that your eyes have ever seen