Life's like this
That's the way it is
Cause life's like this
Chill out
whatcha yelling' for?
Lay back it's all
been done before
And if you could only let it be
you will see
I like you the
way you are
When we're
drivin' in your car
And you're talking
to me one on one
But you've become
Somebody else
Round everyone else
You're watching your back
like you can't relax
You're tryin' to be cool
you look like a fool to me
Tell me
Why you have to go and
make things so complicated?
I see the way you're
Acting like you're somebody else
gets me frustrated
Life's like this
you...
And you fall and
you crawl and you break
And you take what you get
and you turn it into
Honesty
and promise me
I'm never gonna
find you fake it
No,
no, no
You come over
unannounced
Dressed up like
you're somethin' else
Where you are and
where it's at you see
You're making me
Laugh out when you
strike your pose
Take off all your
preppy clothes
You know you're not
fooling anyone
when you've become
Somebody else
Round everyone else
Watching your back,
like you can't relax
Trying to be cool you look
like a fool to me
Tell me
Why you have to go and
make things so complicated?
I see the way you're
Acting like you're somebody else
gets me frustrated
Life's like this
you...
And you fall and
you crawl and you break
And you take what you get
and you turn it into
Honesty
and promise me
I'm never gonna
find you fake it
No, no
no, no
No,
No
Chill out whatcha
yelling for?
Lay back, it's all
been done before
And if you could only let it be
You will see
Somebody else
round everyone else
You're watching your back,
like you can't relax
You're trying to be cool,
you look like a fool to me
Tell me
Why you have to go and
make things so complicated?
I see the way you're
Acting like you're somebody else
gets me frustrated
Life's like this
you...
And you fall and
you crawl and you break
And you take what you get
and you turn it into
Honesty
and promise me
I'm never gonna
find you fake it
No,
no,
Why you have to go and
make things so complicated?
I see the way you're
Acting like you're somebody else
gets me frustrated
Life's like this
you...
And you fall and
you crawl and you break
And you take what you get
and you turn it into
Honesty
and promise me
I'm never gonna
find you fake it
No,
no, no
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo