I always needed time
on my own
I never thought I'd need
you there when I cry
And the days feel like
years when I'm alone
And the bed where you lie
Is made up on your side
When you walk away
I count the steps that you take
Do you see how much
I need you right now?
When you're gone
The pieces of my heart
are missing you
When you're gone
The face I came to know
is missing too
When you're gone
All words I need to hear
to always get me
through the day
And make it ok
I miss you
I've never felt this
way before
Everything that I do
Reminds me of you
And the clothes you left,
they lie on the floor
And they smell just like you
I love the things that you do
When you walk away
I count the steps that you take
Do you see how much
I need you right now?
When you're gone
The pieces of my heart
are missing you
When you're gone
The face I came to know
is missing too
When you're gone
All words I need to hear
to always get me
through the day
And make it ok
I miss you
We were made
for each other
I'll keep it forever
I know we were
Yeah, yeah
And all I ever wanted
was for you to know
Everything I do I give
my heart and soul
I can hardly breathe
I need to feel you
here with me
Yeah...
When you're gone
The pieces of my heart
are missing you
When you're gone
The face I came to know
is missing too
When you're gone
All words I need to hear
to always get me
through the day
And make it ok
I miss you
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo