He was a boy
She was a girl
Can I make it
anymore obvious?
He was a punk
She did ballet
What more can I say?
He wanted her
She'd never tell
Secretly she wanted
him as well
But all of her friends
Stuck up their nose
They had a problem
with his baggy clothes
He was
a skater boy
She said see
you later boy
He wasn't good
enough for her
She had
a pretty face
But her head
was up in space
She needed to come
back down to earth
Five years from now
She sits at home
Feeding the baby
She's all alone
She turns on tv
Guess who she sees?
Skater boy rockin' up MTV.
She calls up
her friends
They already know
And they've all got
tickets to see his show
She tags along
Stands in the crowd
Looks up at the man
that she turned down
He was
a skater boy
She said see
you later boy
He wasn't good
enough for her
Now he's a superstar
Slammin' on his guitar
Does your pretty face
see what he's worth?
He was
a skater boy
She said
see you later boy
He wasn't good
enough for her
Now he's a superstar
Slammin' on his guitar
Does your pretty face
see what he's worth?
Sorry girl
but you missed out
Well, tough luck,
that boy's mine now
We are more than
just good friends
This is how
the story ends
Too bad that
you couldn't see
See the man
that boy could be
There is more
than meets the eye
I see the soul that has in inside
He's just
a boy
And I'm just
a girl
Can I make it
anymore obvious?
We are in love
Haven't you heard
How we rock
each others world?
I'm with the
skater boy
I said see you
later boy
I'll be backstage
after the show
I'll be at
the studio
Singing the
song we wrote
About the girl
you used to know
I'm with the
skater boy
I said see you
later boy
I'll be backstage
after the show
I'll be at the studio
Singing the
song we wrote
About the girl
you used to know.
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo