Lil Mama and Avril Lavigne REMIX
Lil Mama and Avril Lavigne
Hey hey you you I don't like your girlfriend
No way no way I think you need a new one
Hey hey you you I could be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Hey hey you you I know that you like me
No way no way you know it's no a secret
Hey hey you you I want to be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Don't get it twisted Lil Mama got my paper on
That means I'm a paper chaser I chase my paper on
And I know we chasing paper that you be chasing on
I just deliver the lyrics that people focus on
Hands and a boob and a chopped up song
Put it in a store and they go cops on
Everybody know that it's no combo
You better lay low like popo
Case you ain't know better already know
I go in like project so
So get it biggie mama b-r-double o-k-lyn drama
Hey hey you you I don't like your girlfriend
No way no way I think you need a new one
Hey hey you you I could be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Hey hey you you I know that you like me
No way no way you know it's no a secret
Hey hey you you I want to be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Please ain't party stop
All I knows sixteen to pop
Told you you all better act on top
Been doing this since hop more pop
Ah tell the brother can't stop
For all the mans I'm cracked on rocks
For all the mans they love my mass
Style so I gotta go hard
der than I did before
her style is crossover
pee wee curling Lil Mama
miss stuff is going in
so when you see me in the drop top shades
in the summer time blazing you wanna be my boyfriend.
Hey hey you you I don't like your girlfriend
No way no way I think you need a new one
Hey hey you you I could be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Hey hey you you I know that you like me
No way no way you know it's no a secret
Hey hey you you I want to be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Oh in a second you'll be wrapped around my finger
'Cause I can, 'cause I can do it better
There's no other
So when's it gonna sink in?
She's so stupid what the hell were you thinking?
Oh in a second you'll be wrapped around my finger
'Cause I can, 'cause I can do it better
There's no other
So when's it gonna sink in?
She's so stupid what the hell were you thinking?
You wave goodbye
Your girls a bird
You're by my side
Make it work
You and her that sounds absurd
Me and you go better you heard?
You ain't hear any dumb girls laugh in the back
that's 'cause I speak crack on the track
I'm gonna keep it real boy
Let me know if you down with that
Me and yo girlfriend we ain't no tie
You better ask T.I.
I'm telling you like Jennifer Hudson
I got plastic elastic in the back
Of the Jaguar sure 'cause that's what's popping
Tiger purses bank is filled
I'm mad 'cause this is nothing
Hey hey you you I don't like your girlfriend
No way no way I think you need a new one
Hey hey you you I could be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Hey hey you you I know that you like me
No way no way you know it's no a secret
Hey hey you you I want to be your girlfriend
I could be your girl Lil Mama be your girlfriend
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo