I need you boo,
I gotta see you boo
and the hearts
all over the world tonight,
said the hearts
all over the world tonight
I need you boo, (ooh)
I gotta see you boo (hey)
and the hearts
all over the world tonight,
said the hearts
all over the world tonight
hey! little mama, ooh, you a stunna
hot..lil
figure, yes, you a winner and
I'm so glad to be yours,
youre a class all your own and...
ooh, little
cutie when..you talk to me
I swear..the whole world stops
youre..my sweetheart
and I'm so glad that you are mine
you are one of a kind and...
you mean to me
what I mean to you and...
together baby,
there is nothing we wont do
cos if I gotchu,
I dont need money,
I dont need cars,
girl, youre my all...
and...
oh! I'm into you, and girl,
no..one else would do,
cuz with every kiss and every hug,
you make me fall in love,
and now i..know
I cant be the only one,
I bet his hearts
all over the world tonight,
with the love of his life who feel...
wat I feel when im
with you, with you, with
you, with you, with you, girl..
you, with you, with you,ohh ...
with you, with you, with
you, with you, with you, girl..
you, with you, with you,ohh ...
oh girl!...
I dont want nobody else,
without you, theres no one left then,
youre like jordans on saturday,
I gotta have you
and I cannot wait now,
hey! little
shawty, say..you care for me,
you know..I care for you,
you know...that ill be true,
you know..that I wont lie,
you know..that I would try,
to be your everything..yeah...
cuz if I got chu,
I dont need money,
I dont need cars,
girl, youre my all...
oh! I'm into you, and girl,
no..one else would do,
cuz with every kiss and every hug,
you make me fall in love,
and now i..know
I cant be the only one,
I bet his hearts
all over the world tonight,
with the love of his life who feel...
wat I feel when im
with you, with you, with
you, with you, with you, ohh...
you, with you, with you, yeah heh..
and i... will never try to
deny, cuz you are my whole light,
cuz if you ever
let me do,I would die...
so I wont find, i
dont need another woman,
I just need your all and nothing,
cos if I got
that, and ill be straight
baby, youre the best part of my ??
I need you boo,
I gotta see you boo
and the hearts
all over the world tonight,
said the hearts
all over the world tonight
woo ooohh.. yeah they need it boo,
they gotta see their boo,
said the hearts
all over the world tonight,
hearts all over the world tonight
oh! I'm into you, and girl,
no..one else would do,
cuz with every kiss and every hug,
you make me fall in love,
and now i..know
I cant be the only one,
I bet his hearts
all over the world tonight,
with the love of his life who feel...
with you, with you, with
you, with you, with you, girl..
you, with you, with you, ooh...
with you, with you, with you,
with you, with you, only with you..
with you, with you,
with you, with you, yeeeah