Yo this is Nappy Boy radio live
Wit' ya boy T-Pain, we love rap music
Listen, uh we got a caller on line one
Caller what's your problem?
Hello, I'm on the radio with T-Pain
(How's it goin, yea)
It aint goin good
My girl aint doin her thang she used to do...
Well, I got just what you need
Brand new Chris Brown, T-Pain
You heard it hear first Nappy Boy Radio
We love ya... hey...
She want that lovey dovey (lovey dovey)
kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Her mind she fantasize bout' gettin' wit' me
They hatin' on me (hatin' on me)
They only diss diss (diss diss)
Cause' she mine, and so fine
and thick as can be
She want that lovey dovey (lovey dovey)
Kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Her mind she fantasize bout' gettin' wit' me
They hatin on me (hatin' on me)
They only diss diss (diss diss)
Cause' she's mine, and so fine
and thick as can be
I'm a country boy from Tappahannock (aaooo)
VA is where I reside
So shawty understand it (aaooo)
And u know I just turned 18
Can get a little manish
And you see this bandana hangin
That means I'm like a bandit
Like-like a bandit-bandit
(Aawwww, ruff)
I got paper girl (ruff)
The Lamborghini (ruff)
With the spider seats (ruff)
You've neva seen it (aaooo)
So get it shawty
We parking' lot pimpin' in my dome
And I know what you want
She want that lovey dovey (lovey dovey)
Kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Her mind she fantasize bout gettin wit' me
They hatin' on me (hatin' on me)
They wanna diss diss (diss diss)
Cause' she mine, and so fine
and thick as can be
She want that lovey dovey (lovey dovey)
Kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Cause mind she fantasize bout' gettin' wit' me
They hatin' on me (hatin' on me)
They only diss diss (kiss kiss)
Cause she's mine, and so fine
and thick as can be
I'm the epitamy of this demonstration
I got the remedy
Ya feelin' me
So why is you hatin' on my anatomy
It's bird like (yeah)
You heard right
Girl I'm the king so that means that I'm black (ruff)
If you wit it girl (ruff)
Get it poppin (ruff)
roll wit me (ruff)
Aint no stoppin (aaooo)
So get it shawty
We parking lot pimpin in my dome
and I know what you want... hey...
She want that lovey dovey (lovey dovey)
Kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Her mind she fantasize bout' gettin' wit' me
They hatin' on me (hatin' on me)
They only diss diss (diss diss)
Cause' she mine, and so fine
and thick as can be... hey...
She want that lovey dovey (lovey dovey)
Kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Her mind she fantasize bout gettin wit' me
They hatin' on me (hatin' on me)
They only diss diss (diss diss)
Cause' she's mine, and so fine
and thick as can be
Shawty lemme holla at you
You so hot hot hot hot
You ain't got me hollin' if you not not not not
I'm king of the town you can take a look around
Teddy bend her ass down in the spot spot spot spot
(YEAAH) I got money on me
(YEAAH) baby girl no problem
(YEAAH) see me rollin' shawty?
(YEAAH) let's hit McDonalds (ruff)
It's TP and CB
I'ma nappy boy
uh-er-oh-uh-uh
OOOOOOWWEEEEEEE!!!!
She want that lovey dovey, oh (lovey dovey)
That kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Her mind she fantasize bout' gettin' wit' me
They hatin' on me (hatin' on me)
They wanna diss diss (kiss kiss)
Cause' she's mine, and so fine
and thick as can be
She want that lovey dovey (lovey dovey)
Kiss kiss (kiss kiss)
Her mind she fantasize bout' gettin' wit' me
They hatin' on me (hatin' on me)
They only diss diss (diss diss)
Cause' she's mine, and so fine
and thick as can be
Yeahhh
We are live back on nappy
boy radio live ( Ok, yeahh)
This is your boy DJ-pain
I gotta get outta hurr man
I just wanna leave wit
If you ain't got it by now then
you just ain't gettin'it... we love ya
Nappy boy (AAAA) and Pretty boy (AAAA)
Nap Nap Nap Nap, n' pretty boy! (AAAA)
Five, Four, Three, Zero, Yeah!