Go, hey Lil Mama,
I can transform ya
No, I can't dance,
but I can dance on ya
Swiss on the beats,
Chris move ya feet
And baby I can transform ya,
him to a me
I can change you life,
make it so new
Make you never want to go back
to the old you
Ciroc and lime,
give it a lil time
And she can transform
like Optimus Prime
Need a ride
I can Range you up,
Money I can
change you up
You can ride your own,
no longer be the passenger
Swag low,
I build you up
Knees we can
stand you up
Red lips, red dress,
like em like a fire truck
What you need?
you can have that
My black card,
they won’t decline that
See potential in ya,
Let me mould that
I can transform ya,
Anything ya want I got,
I can get it for ya
Your my baby girl,
shoulda know I did it for ya
I can trans, I can trans,
I can transform ya
Shoes,
you got it,
Bags,
Cars,
you got it,
Money,
still got it,
I can transform ya,
Anything ya want,
I can get it for ya
See me in the video,
you can have it really all
Iced out everything,
like an eskimo,
Wanna fly, we can go,
anywhere you wanna go
Jimmy Choos in Italy,
Louie V in Tokyo
Something
like Pinnochio,
If you lie down
imma grow
Wanna see me
do it big
I can show you
how it goes
Take you from an amateur,
to being professional
I can have you
swag surfing
What you need?
you can have that
My black card
they won’t decline that
See potential in ya,
Let me mould that
I can transform ya,
Anything ya want I got,
I can get it for ya
Your my baby girl,
shoulda know I did it for ya
I can trans, I can trans,
I can transform ya
Shoes,
you got it,
Bags,
Cars,
you got it,
Money,
still got it,
I can transform ya,
I can transform ya
Anything you want,
I can get it for ya
I can transform ya
like a transformer
I can turn you
from a human to a Carter
Take you off the bench,
and turn ya to a starter
Then take you home
and put you on a charger
Then my cars
transforms to a charter
And we can fly to
wherever you ever thought of
I take you
to wherever its warmer
Then I gotta rip off
your dress like a warm up
But I'm just
getting warmed up
So tell your man
he better get his voltron up
I transform
her to a Ducati
Then I transform me
to a Bugatti
'cos her form
puts me in a trance
I transform smaller
and she puts me in her pants
Swizz on the Beat,
Chris move ya feet
And we can transform
a good girl to a freak
I can transform ya,
Anything ya want I got,
I can get it for ya,
Your my baby girl,
shoulda know I did it for ya
I can trans, I can trans,
I can transform ya
Shoes,
you got it,
Bags,
Cars,
you got it,
Money,
still got it,
I can transform ya,
I can transform ya
Anything you want
I can get it for ya
Chris