1,2,3,4
Hey
Forever
It’s you,
And me
Moving at
the speed of light
Into eternity
Tonight
Is the night
To join me in
the middle of ecstasy
Feel the melody and the rhythm
of the music around you
Around you
Imma take you there
So don’t be scared
Im right
here baby
We can go anywhere,
go anywhere
But first,
it’s your chance
Take my hand
come with me
It’s like I waited
my whole life
For this one night
Its gonna be me, you,
and the dance floor
Cause we only
got one night
Double your pleasure
Double your fun
And dance
forever, ever, ever
Forever
ever, ever
Forever on
the dance floor
Sounds like
we’re on another level
Feels like our
love’s intertwined
We can be
two rebels
Breakin the rules
Me and you,
you and I
All you gotta
do is watch me
Look what I can do
with my feet
Baby,
feel the beat inside
I’m driving you
take the front seat
I just need
you to trust me
It’s like I...
It’s like I waited
my whole life
For this one night
Its gonna be me, you,
and the dance floor
Cause we only
got one night
Double your pleasure
Double your fun
Dance forever
ever, ever
Forever
Forever on
the dance floor
It’s a
long way now
So high off
the ground
Sending for an angel
Bring me your heart
Girl, where
did you come from
Got me so undone
Gaze in your eyes got me saying
“What a beautiful lady!”
No ifs,
and, or maybes
I’m releasing
my heart
Its feeling amazing
No one else
that matter
You love me
And I won’t let you fall girl,
let you fall girl
Oh, oh,
yea, yea
I won’t let you fall, let you fall,
let you fall
Oh, oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
It’s like I...
It’s like I waited
my whole life
For this
one night
Its gonna be me, you,
and the dance floor
Cause we only
got one night
Double your pleasure
Double your fun
Dance forever
ever, ever
Forever
Forever on
the dance floor
Forever
ever, ever
Forever...