Everybody, yeah
Rock your body, yeah
Rock your body right
Backstreet's back, alright
Hey, yeah
Oh my God, we're back again
Brothers, sisters, everybody sing
Gonna bring the flavor, show you how
Gotta question for you better answer now, yeah
Am I original?
Yeah
Am I the only one?
Am I sexual?
Yeah
Am I everything you need?
You better rock your body now
Everybody
Yeah
Rock your body
Everybody
Rock your body right
Backstreet's back, alright
Alright
Now throw your hands up in the air
Wave them around like you just don't care
If you wanna party let me hear you yell
Cuz we got it goin' on again
Yeah
Am I original?
Am I the only one?
Yeah
Am I sexual?
Am I everything you need?
You better rock your body now
Everybody
Yeah
Rock your body
Everybody
Rock your body right
Backstreet's back, alright
Alright
Everybody, yeah
Rock your body, yeah
Everybody
Rock your body right (rock your body right)
Backstreet's back
Everybody (everybody)
Yeah (rock your body)
Yeah (everybody rock your body)
Everybody (everybody, rock your body)
Rock your body right (everybody)
Backstreet's back, alright