I can see that you've been crying
You can't hide it with a lie
What's the use in you denying
That what you have is wrong
I heard him promise you forever
But forevers come and gone
Baby he would say whatever
It takes to keep you blind
To the truth between the lines
Oh I will love you more than that
I won't say those words, \Nthen take them back
Don't give loneliness a chance
Baby listen to me when I say
I will love you more than that
Baby you deserve much better
What's the use in holding on
Don't you see it's now or never
Coz I just can't be friends
Baby knowing in the end
That I will love you more than that
I won't say those words, \Nthen take them back
Don't give loneliness a chance
Baby listen to me when I say
There's not a day that passes by
I don't wonder why we haven't tried
It's not too late to change your mind
So take my hand, don't say goodbye
I will love you more than that
I won't say those words, \Nthen take them back
Oh I will love you more than that
I won't say those words,\N then take them back
Don't give loneliness a chance
Baby listen to me when I say
I will love you, oh
I will love you more than that
I won't say those words, \Nthen take them back
Don't give loneliness a chance
Baby listen to me when I say
I will love you more than that