Baby, I know you are hurting
Right now you feel like you could never love again
Now all I ask is for a chance
To prove that I love you
From the first day that I saw your smiling face
Honey, I knew that we would be together forever
Ooh, when I asked you out, you said, "No"
But I found out darling that you'd been hurt
You felt that you'd never love again
I deserve a try honey just once
Give me a chance and I'll prove this all wrong
You walked in, you were so quick to judge
But honey, he's nothing like me
I'll never break your heart
I'll never make you cry
I'd rather die than live without you
I'll give you all of me
Honey, that's no lie
I'll never break your heart
I'll never make you cry
I'd rather die than live without you
I'll give you all of me
Honey, that's no lie
As time goes by you will get to know me
A little more better, girl, that's the way love goes, baby baby
And I know you're afraid to let your feelings show
And I understand but girl, it's time to let go
I deserve a try, honey, just once
Give me chance and I'll prove this all wrong
You walked in, you were so quick to judge
But honey, he's nothing like me
Darling, why can't you see?
I'll never break your heart
I'll never make you cry
I'd rather die than live without you
I'll give you all of me
Honey, that's no lie
I'll never break your heart
I'll never make you cry
I'd rather die than live without you
I'll give you all of me
Honey, that's no lie
No way, no how
I swear
I
I'll never break your heart
I'll never make you cry
I'd rather die than live without you
I'll give you all of me
Honey, that's no lie