Girl:] "Hello?"
[AJ:]"Hi it's me what's up baby? I'm \Nsorry listen I'm gonna be late tonight \Nso don't stay up and wait for me ok?"
[Girl:] "Where are you?"
[AJ:] "Wait wait say that again?"
[Girl:] "Hello?"
[AJ:] "You're really dropping out \NI think my battery must be low. \NListen if you
can hear me \Nwe're goin' to a place nearby, alright? Gotta go"
Let me tell you the story about \Nthe call that changed my destiny
Me and my boys went out,\N just to end up in misery
I was about to go home \Nand there she was standing in front of me
Said 'Hi, I got a little place nearby
Wanna go?', I should have said 'No'
Someone's waiting for me
But I called my girl up and said
Listen Baby I'm sorry
Just wanna tell you don't worry
I will be late don't stay up and wait for me
I'll say again you're dropping out my battery is low
So you know we're goin' to a place nearby
I gotta go
Now two years gone, nothing's been won
I can't take it back what's done is done
One of her friends found out
That she wasn't my only one
And it eats me from inside,\N that she's not by my side
Just because I made that call and lied
Listen Baby I'm sorry
Just wanna tell you don't worry
I will be late don't stay up and wait for me
I'll say again you're dropping out my battery is low
So you know we're goin to a place nearby
I gotta go
"Baby baby I'm sorry, and "Hello?"
Let me tell you the story about \Nthe call that changed my destiny
Me and my boys went out, \Njust to end up in misery
I was about to go home \Nand there she was standing in front of me
Said I, I got a little place nearby
Gotta go
Listen Baby I'm sorry
Just wanna tell you don't worry
I will be late don't stay up and wait for me
I'll say again you're dropping out my battery is low
So you know we're goin to a place nearby
Gotta go
Listen Baby I'm sorry
Just wanna tell you don't worry
I will be late don't stay up and wait for me
I'll say again you're dropping out my battery is low
So you know we're goin to a place nearby
We're goin to a place nearby
Gotta go