As long as you love me
Although loneliness \Nhas always been a friend of mine
I'm leavin' my life in your hands
People say I'm crazy and that I am blind
Risking it all in a glance
And how you got me blind is still a mystery
I can't get you out of my head
Don't care what is written in your history
As long as you're here with me
I don't care who you are
Where you're from
What you did
As long as you love me
Who you are
Where you're from
Don't care what you did
As long as you love me
Every little thing \Nthat you have said and done
Feels like it's deep within me
Doesn't really matter if you're on the run
It seems like we're meant to be
I don't care who you are
Where you're from
What you did
As long as you love me \N (I don't know)
Who you are
Where you're from
Don't care what you did
As long as you love me (yeah)
I've tried to hide it so that no one knows
But I guess it shows
When you look into my eyes
What you did and where you're comin from
I don't care, as long as you love me, baby
I don't care who you are
Where you're from
What you did
As long as you love me
Who you are
Where you're from
Don't care what you did (yeah)
As long as you love me
Who you are
Where you're from
What you did
As long as you love me
Who you are
Where you're from
As long as you love me
Who you are
What you did \N(I don't care)