Everybody grove to the music
Everybody jam
Oh, hey
We've been waiting so long
Just can't hold it back no more
Creepin' up and down now
It's time for me to let it go
If you really wanna see
What we can do for you
Send the crazy wildin' static
Sing it
Jam on cuz Backstreet's got it
Come on now everybody
We've got it goin' on for years
Jam on cuz Backstreet's got it
Come on now everybody
We've got it goin' on for years
Well I'm creepin' up on your left
Straight up funky when I get with you
Keep it ruthless when I get wet
Keep the party packed in my corner
Tough like granite to keep the crowd hype
Get up on this just to get right
What you want it what you gonna get
Backstreet's got the special effects, uh
If you really wanna see
What we can do for you, oh
I'll send the crazy wildin' static
Sing it
Jam on cuz Backstreet's got it
Come on now everybody
We've got it goin' on for years
Jam on cuz Backstreet's got it
Come on now everybody
We've got it goin' on for years
We've been waiting so long
Just can't hold it back no more
(just can't hold it back no more)
Creepin' up and down now
It's time for me to let it go
Jam on, jam on
Everybody groove to the music
Everybody jam
Jam on cuz Backstreet's got it
Come on now everybody
We've got it goin' on for years
We've got it goin' on