She keeps the secrets in her eyes
She wraps the truth inside her lies
And just when i can't take what she's done to me
She comes to me
And leads me back to paradise
She's so hard to hold But I can't let go
I'm a house of cards in a hurricane
A reckless ride in the pouring rain
She cuts me and the pain is all I wanna feel
She danced away just like a child
She drives me crazy drives me wild
But I'm helpless when she smiles
Oh.. when she smiles
she smile
Maybe I'd fight it if I could
It hurts so bad, but feels so good
She opens up just like a rose to me
When she's close to me
Anything she asked me to, I would
It's out of control But I can't let go...
I'm a house of cards in a hurricane
A reckless ride in the pouring rain
She cuts me and the pain is all I wanna feel
She danced away just like a child
She drives me crazy drives me wild
But I'm helpless when she smiles
Oh.. when she smiles
When she looks at me
I.. get so weak
I'm a house of cards in a hurricane
A reckless ride in the pouring rain
She cuts me and the pain is all I wanna feel
She danced away just like a child
She drives me crazy drives me wild
But I'm helpless when she smiles
Oh.. when she smiles
when she smiles
She smiles