I don't know what he does to make you cry
But I'll be there to make you smile
I don't have a fancy car
To get to you I'd walk a thousand miles
I don't care if he buys you nice things
Does his gifts come from the heart?
I don't know
But if you were my girl
I'd make it so we'd never be apart
But my love is all I have to give
Without you I don't think I could live
I wish I could give the world to you
But love is all I have to give
When you talk (when you talk) \Ndoes it seem like he's not
Even listening to a word you say?
That's okay babe, \njust tell me your problems
I'll try my best to kiss them all away
Does he leave (does he leave) \Nwhen you need him the most?
Does his friends get all your time?
Baby please
I'm on my knees
Praying for the day that you'll be mine
But my love is all I have to give
Without you I don't think I could live
I wish I could give the world to you
But love is all I have to give
To you... (hey girl) hey girl,\N I don't want you to cry no more inside
All the money in the world \Ncould never add up to all the love
I have inside...
Without you I don't think I could live
I wish I could give the world to you
But love is all I have to give
But my love is all I have to give
Without you I don't think I could live
I wish I could give the world to you
But love is all I have to give
But my love is all I have to give
Without you I don't think I can live
I wish I could give the world to you
But love is all I have to give... to you