Looking at your picture
from when we first met
You gave me a smile that I could never forget
And nothing I could do could protect me from you that night
Wrapped around your finger
Always in my mind
The days they blend 'cause we stayed up all night
Yeah, you and I were everything,
everything to me
I just want you to know
that I've been fighting to let you go
Some days I make it through,
and then there's nights that never end
I wish that I could believe
that there's a day you'll come back to me
But still I have to say
I would do it all again,
just want you to know
All the doors are closing
I'm trying to move ahead
And deep inside I wish it's me instead
My dreams are empty from the day
The day you slipped away
I just want you to know
that I've been fighting to let you go
Some days I make it through,
and then there's nights that never end
I wish that I could believe
that there's a day you'll come back to me
But still I have to say
I would do it all again,
just want you to know
That since I lost you,
I lost myself
No, I can't fake it,
there's no one else
I just want you to know
that I've been fighting to let you go
Some days I make it through,
and then there's nights that never end
I wish that I could believe
that there's a day you'll come back to me
But still I have to say
I would do it all again,
just want you to know