Ever Try To Reach For Something
But Its Someone Else's Dream
Every Step That You Take Forward
It Takes You Right Back Where You Been
And Then When You Least Expect It
And You Tried About Everything
Somebody Hears Your Opinions
Somebody Cares What You See
You Woke Me Up
No Longer Tired
With You I Feel Inspired
You Help Me Find My Fire
You're The New Classic
You're The New PYT
Stands For Pay Young
Taking On The World From The Driver's Seat
You Look So Classic
Fantastic
When You're On That Floor
Bring The Beat Back Once More
Let Me See You Do That
Oh Trying To Do It Right
No Rehearsals
It's Your Life
If Your Doing This Crazy Dance
Cause Your Making These Crazy Friends
It's Just This Is Not a Test
You Put In Work To Be The Best (ohhh)
(ohhh) It's A Classic Take
On A Brand New Game
Before The Needle Drops
They're Gonna Know Your Name
When It Gets Old Don't Lose The Light
You're Cold I'll Warm You Up
(You Up) Your Fire Is Hot Enough (enough) Enough (enough)
You're The New Classic
You're The New PYT
Stands For Pay Young And
Trying Everything Just To Touch Your Dreams
You Look So Classic Fantastic
When You're On That Floor
Bring The Beat Back Once More (bring it back) (once more)
Let Me See You Do That
It's Become So Hard
For Me To Be Surprised
You're Bringing Back The Real Me
No Judgment In Your Eyes
Cause When I Dance With You
It's How I Speak The Truth
Just Classic When Me Met
Now You Make Me New
You're The New Classic
You're The New PYT
Cause You're Pay Young And
Taking On The World From The Drivers Seat
You Look So Classic
Fantastic
When You On That Floor
Bring The Beat Back Once More (bring the beat back once more)
You're The New Classic
You're The New PYT
Cause You're Pay Young And
Taking On The World From The Driver's Seat
You Look So Classic
Fantastic
When You're On That Floor
Bring The Beat Back Once More
(bring it back) (bring it back)
Let Me See You Do That
Your The New Classic
Your The New PYT
Cause Your Pay Young
Isn't Take A Chance To Believe In Me
You're The New Classic
Fantastic
When You're On That Floor (when you're on that floor)
Bring The Beat Back Once More (bring it back once more)
Let Me See You Do That