You walk and talk like your some new sensation
You move in circles you don't need an invitation
You spend you money You can't get no satisfaction
You play it right so you can get the right reaction
It won't be long my darling
Pick up the phone nobodies on it
Where are your friends now baby?
How are the ones supposed to be there for you
You
When your falling down, the worlds not spinning around you
When your falling down, the worlds not all about you
You
When your falling down, you know I'll be around
When your falling down, falling down
Without a place when you look into the mirror
Which is blurry but the lies are getting clearer
Your eyes are fixed
Your smile is an elastic
You gave me roses but their all just made of plastic
It won't be long my darling
Pick up the phone nobodies on it
Where are your friends now baby?
How are the ones supposed to be there for you
You
When your falling down, the world not spinning around you
When your falling down, the worlds not all about you
You
When your falling down, you know I'll be around
When your falling down, falling down
Smile for the camera everybody's looking at you
Smile for the camera 'cause there all about to trash you
Smile for the camera, camera, camera
Smile for the camera, who's gonna catch ya
You, You
You
When your falling down, the worlds not spinning around you
When your falling down, the worlds not all about you
You
When your falling down, you know I'll be around
When falling down, Falling down
Smile for the camera everybody's looking at you
Smile for the camera 'cause there all about to trash you