Everybody tells me,
That it's so hard to make it,
Yet so hard to break it,
And there's no way to fake it,
Everybody tells me that it's wrong what I'm feeling,
I shouldn't believe in,
The dreams that I'm dreaming,
I hear it everyday,
I hear it all the time,
I'm never gunna amount to much,
But they're never gunna change my mind.
Oh!
Tell me, tell me, tell me,
Something I don't know,
Something I don't know.
How many inches in a mile,
What it takes to make you smile.
Getcha not to treat me like a child, baby.
Tell me, tell me, tell me,
Something I don't know,
Something I don't know.
Tell me, tell me something I don't know,
Tell me, tell me something I don't know.
Everybody tells me I don't know what I'm doing,
This life I'm pursuing,
The odds of me loosing.
Everybody tells me that it's one in a million,
More like one in a billion,
Or one in a zillion.
I hear it everyday,
I hear it all the time,
I'm never gunna amount to much,
But they're never gunna change my mind.
Oh!
Tell me, tell me, tell me,
Something I don't know,
Something I don't know.
How many inches in a mile,
What it takes to make you smile,
Getcha not to treat me like a child, baby.
Tell me, tell me, tell me,
Something I don't know,
Are you ready for it?
Yeah I'm ready for it.
Really ready for it?
I'm on my way,
I know I'm gonna get there someday,
It doesn't help when you say,
It won't be easy.
Tell me, tell me, tell me,
Something I don't know,
Something I don't know.
How many inches in a mile,
What it takes to make you smile,
Getcha not to treat me like a child, baby.
Tell me, tell me, tell me,
something I don't know,