Watch all the flowers
Dance with the wind
Listen to snowflakes
Whisper your name
Feel all the wonder
Lifting your dreams
You can fly
(Fly)
Fly to who you are
Climb upon your star
You believe you'll find your wings
Fly
To Your Heart
Touch every rainbow
Painting the sky
Look at the magic
Glide through your life
A sprinkle of pixie dust circles the night you can fly
Fly to who you are
Climb upon your star
You believe you'll find your wings
Fly
Everywhere you go
So we'll find a home
You'll be free to spread your wings
Fly
You can fly
To your heart
Rise to the heights of all you can be
(Fly, Fly)
Soar on the hope of marvelous things
Fly to who you are
Climb upon your star
You believe you'll find your wings
Fly
Everwhere you go
So we'll find a home
You'll be free to spread your wings
Fly
You can fly
To your heart