I wouldn't wanna be anybody else, hey
You made my insecure
To me I wasn't good enough
But who are you to judge
When you're diamond in the rough
I'm sure you got some things
You like to change about yourself
But when it comes to me
I wouldn't want to be anybody else
Na na na na, na na na na, na na na na na
I'm no beauty queen, I'm just beautiful me
You got every right to a beautiful life
Come on!
Who says
Who says you're not perfect
Who says you're not worth it
Who says you're the only one that's hurting
Trust me that's the price of beauty
Who says you're not pretty
Who says you're not beautiful
Who says
It's such a funny thing
How nothing's funny when it's you
You tell me what you need
But they can widen out the the truth
It's like a work of art
But never gets to see the lights
Keep you beneath the stars
While I can touch the sky
Na na na na, na na na na, na na na na na
I'm no beauty queen, I'm just beautiful me
You got every right to a beautiful life
Come on!
Who says
Who says you're not perfect
Who says you're not worth it
Who says you're the only one that's hurting
Trust me that's the price of beauty
Who says you're not pretty
Who says you're not beautiful
Who says
Who say you're not star potential
Who says you're presidential
Who says you can't be in movies
Listen to me, listen to me
Who says you don't pass a test
Who says you can't be the best
Who said, who said
Would you tell me who said that, yeah
Who says
Who says you're not perfect
Who says you're not worth it
Who says you're the only one that's hurting
Trust me that's the price of beauty
Who says you're not pretty
Who says you're not beautiful
Who says
Who says you're not perfect
Who says you're not worth it
Who says you're the only one that's hurting
Trust me that's the price of beauty
Who says you're not pretty
Who says you're not beautiful
Who says