Round and Round (x4)
You see me standing there
And act like you dont know me
But last night you were calling me
Saying you want me
Oh why you always make me feel
Like I'm the one thats crazy
You feel my heart racing
My-my heart racing
Boy, I need you here with me
We can't go on this way
I'm falling hard for you
And all I can say
We're going round and round
We're never gonna stop
Going round and round
We'll never get where
We are going
Round and round
Well your gonna miss me
Cause im getting dizzy
Going round and round
Round and round
You tried to pull me close
And whisper in my ear
You always told me lies
I cried out all my tears
I pushed my feelings to the side
But then you bring them back
B-bring them back
Now you got me singing
Boy,I need you here with me
We cant go on this way
I'm falling hard for you
And all I can say
We're going round and round
We're never gonna stop
Going round and round
We'll never get where
We are going
Round and round
Well your gonna miss me
Cause im getting dizzy
Going round and round
Round and round
Love me or Love me not
Im starring at the clock
I take them flower petals off
And then I watch them drop
Love me or Love me not
Im starring at the clock
I take them flower petals off
And then I watch them drop
Boy,I need you here with me
We cant go on this way
I'm falling hard for you
And all I can say
We're going round and round
We're never gonna stop
Going round and round
We'll never get where
We are going
Round and round
Well your gonna miss me
Cause im getting dizzy
Going round and round
Round and round