How you choose to express yourself
Its all your own and I can tell
It comes naturally,
it comes naturally
You follow what you feel inside,
It's intuitive, you don't have to try,
It comes naturally,
It comes naturally
And it takes my breath away
You are the thunder and I am the lightning,
And I love the way you know who you are,
And to me it's exciting,
When you know it's meant to be,
Everything comes naturally,
It comes naturally,
When you're with me baby,
Everything comes naturally,
It comes naturally,
(Ba-Ba-Baby)
You have a way of moving me,
A force of nature, your energy,
It comes naturally, (You know it does,)
It comes naturally, (Oh yeah)
And it takes my breath away (Everytime)
What you do, so naturally
You are the thunder and I am the lightning,
And I love the way you know who you are,
And to me it's exciting,
When you know it's meant to be,
Everything comes naturally,
It comes naturally,
When you're with me baby,
Everything comes naturally,
It comes naturally,
(Ba-Ba-Baby)
When we collide, sparks fly
When you look in my eyes,
it takes my breath away
(You are) You are the thunder and I am the lightening
And I love the way you know who you are
And to me it's exciting
When you know it's meant to be
Everything comes naturally,
it comes naturally
When youre with me, baby
Everything comes naturally,
it comes naturally
Ba-Ba-baby
Naturally (Naturally)
Everything comes naturally, aturally (Naturally)
Ba-Ba-baby