And I don't wanna see no more
Oh Oh (And I don't wanna see no more)
It was Saturday when I got that call
Far away from feeling tall
I know, I know, I know what the truth is
Yeah
I try to look away from what you did
Heartache became my friend
You walked away from me baby
I would've never done the same
You made me feel like our love was not real
You threw it all away, so
I don’t wanna wait for you
I don’t wanna wake up thinking, hoping
You will get it right this time
‘Cause you know that you’re so cold
I don’t wanna see no more
And I can’t get away from you
It’s one of the reasons why
That I just can’t get you out my mind
And all I keep seeing is your picture
I don’t wanna see no more
It was so easy to trust you baby
Guess I was so stupid baby
Oh, I didn’t ever think that this would come
You’re running right to another one, oh
You walked away from me baby
You threw it all away, so
I don’t wanna wait for you, no, no
I don’t wanna wake up thinking, hoping
You will get it right this time
‘Cause you know that you’re so cold
I don’t wanna see no more
And I can’t get away from you
It’s one of the reasons why
That I just can’t get you out my mind
And all I keep seeing is your picture
I don’t wanna see no more (no more)
I don’t wanna see no more
I used to be afraid of letting go
The fragile part of me, I’m here right now
I need you to set me free
I can see it in your eyes
That you won’t blame it on me this time
No, never
You might want me back but I won’t look back, no
I don’t wanna wait for you
I don’t wanna wake up thinking, hoping
You will get it right this time
‘Cause you know that you’re so cold
I don’t wanna see no more
And I can’t get away from you
It’s one of the reasons why
That I just can’t get you out my mind
And all I keep seeing is your picture
I don't wanna see no more.