[Snoop Dog]
Greetings loved ones
Let's take a journey
[Katy Perry]
I know a place
Where the grass is really greener
Warm, wet and wild
There must be something in the water
Sippin' gin and juice
Laying underneath the palm trees
(Undone)
The boys break their necks
Tryin' to creep a little sneak peek
(At us)
You could travel the world
But nothing comes close
to the Golden Coast
Once you party with us
You'll be falling in love
(Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh)
California gurls,
we're unforgettable
Daisy dukes,
bikinis on top
Sun-kissed skin, so hot,
will melt your popsicle
(Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh)
(Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh)
California gurls, we're undeniable
Fine, fresh, fierce, we got it on lock
West Coast represent,
now put your hands up
(Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh)
(Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh)
Sex on a beach
We get sand in out stilettos
We freak, in my jeep
Snoop Doggy Dogg is on the stereo
(Oh-oh)
You could travel the world
But nothing comes close
to the Golden Coast
Once you party with us
You'll be falling in love
Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh)
California gurls, we're unforgettable
Daisy dukes, bikinis on top
Sun-kissed skin, so hot,
will melt your popsicle
(Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh)
(Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh)
California gurls, we're undeniable
Fine, fresh, fierce, we got it on lock
West Coast represent,
now put your hands up
(Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh)
(Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh)
[Snoop Dogg]
Tone Tan, Fit and ready
Turn it up cause its gettin' heavy
Wild wild west coast
These are the girls I love the most
I mean the ones
I mean like shes the one
Kiss her
Touch her
Squeeze her
The girls a freak
She drives a jeep
The men on the beach
I'm okay, I wont play
I love the bait Just like I love LA
Venice beach
And Palm Springs
Summer time is everything
Come on boys
Hanging out
All that a-s
Bikinis, tankinis, martinis
No weenies
Just to get
In betweeny
Katy my lady
(Yeah)
You looking here baby
(uh huh)
Im all up on you
Cause you representing California
[Katy Perry]
California girls, We're unforgettable
Daisy Dukes, Bikinis on top
Sun-kissed skin, So hot
Will melt your popsicle
Oooooh Oh Oooooh
California girls, We're undeniable
Fine, fresh, fierce
We got it on lock
West coast represent
Now put your hands up
Oooooh Oh Oooooh
(Californiaaaa)
California girls man
I really wish
You all could be California girls