fridaayyyyy
hey, oh
what happened
listen
i just wanna thank you
for the best party eve of all times
it was absolutely incredible
i dont care what anyone say about you
you are actually really cool
best party ever, wooooo
There's a stranger in my bed
There's a pounding in my head
Glitter all over the room
Pink flamingos in the pool
I smell like a minibar
DJ's passed out in the yard
Barbie's on the barbeque
There's a hickie or a bruise
Pictures of last night
Eended up online
I'm screwed
Oh well
It's a black top blur
But I'm pretty sure it ruled
Last Friday night
Yeah we danced on tabletops
And we took too many shots
Think we kissed but I forgot
Last Friday night
Yeah we maxed our credit cards
And got kicked out of the bar
So we hit the boulevard
Last Friday night
We went streaking in the park
Skinny dipping in the dark
Then had a menage a trois
Last Friday night
Yeah I think we broke the law
Always say we're gonna stop-op
Whoa-oh-oah
This Friday night
Do it all again
Trying to connect the dots
Don't know what to tell my boss
Think the city towed my car
Chandelier is on the floor
With my favorite party dress
Warrants out for my arrest
Think I need a ginger ale
That was such an epic fail
Pictures of last night
Ended up online
I'm screwed
Oh well
It's a blacked out blur
But I'm pretty sure it ruled
Damn
Last Friday night
Yeah we danced on table tops
And we took too many shots
Think we kissed but I forgot
Last Friday night
Yeah we maxed our credits card
And got kicked out of the bars
So we hit the boulevards
Last Friday night
We went streaking in the park
Skinny dipping int he dark
Then had a menage a trois
last friday night
Yeah I think we broke the law
Always say we're gonna stop-op
Oh whoa oh
This Friday night
Do it all again
T.G.I.F.
Last Friday night
Yeah we danced on table tops
And we took too many shots
Think we kissed but I forgot
Last Friday night
Yeah we maxed our credit cards
And got kicked out of the bar
So we hit the boulevard
Last Friday night
We went streaking in the park
Skinny dipping in the dark
Then had a menage a trois
Last Friday night
Yeah I think we broke the law
Always say we're gonna stop
Oh-whoa-oh
This Friday night
Do it all again
what is doing this egg on the floor
katy beth perry what happend
to your room
oh no mam, dad
and why there are some lost boy in your bed
i dont know anything
i just woke up
and my soalr system was off the post
my godness, so you're respossible
and what uncle kenny is doing on the coach
i didn't do it
it was rebecca
she had a party
rebecca black is a nice girl
i dont think she would start this
why you come back so early from convention
i get a crazy text from uncle kenny
that said he want to play...
we got to get home right away
to see what was that all about
cant let that happen
i love you guy's
but uncle kenny told me you used to be fun on fridays
kitty cat we invented fridays
i need to sleep off