I hopped off
the plane at LAX.
With my dreams
in the cart again.
Welcome to
the land of fame XX.
Am I gonna fit in?
Jumped in the cab.
Here I am for
the first time.
Look to the right and
I see the hollywood sign.
This is all
so crazy.
Everybody
seems so famous.
My tummys turnin'
and I'm feelin' kinda home sick.
Too much pressure
and I'm nervous.
'Cause when the taxi man
turned on the radio.
And a Jay Z's song was on.
So I put my hands up.
There playing my song.
And the butterflys
fly away.
Noddin'
my head like yeah.
Movin' my hips
like yeah.
I got my hands up
there playing my song.
I know
I'm gonna be okay.
It's a
party in the USA.
Get to the club
in my taxi cab.
Everybodys
lookin' at me now.
Like "whos that chick,
thats rockin' kicks".
"She gotta be
from out of town".
So hard with my girls
not around me.
It's definatel
not a Nashville party.
'Cause' all
I see are stilletos.
I guess
I never got the memo.
My tummys turnin'
and I'm feelin' kinda home sick.
Too much pressure
and I'm nervous.
And the D.J.
dropped my favorite tune.
And a Britney's song was on.
So I put my hands up.
There playing my song.
And the butterflys
fly away.
Noddin'
my head like yeah.
Movin' my hips
like yeah.
I got my hands up
there playing my song.
I know
I'm gonna be okay.
It's a
party in the USA.
Feel like
I wanna fly
Back to
my hometown tonight
Something
stops me everytime
The D.J. plays my song
and I feel alright
So I put my hands up.
There playing my song.
And the butterflys
fly away.
Noddin'
my head like yeah.
Movin' my hips
like yeah.
I got my hands up
there playing my song.
I know
I'm gonna be okay.
It's a
party in the USA.
So I put my hands up.
There playing my song.
And the butterflys
fly away.
Noddin'
my head like yeah.
Movin' my hips
like yeah.
I got my hands up
there playing my song.
I know
I'm gonna be okay.
It's a
party in the USA.