R -
O -
C -
K -
Mafia
Creation shows me what to do
I'm dancing on the floor with you And when you touch my hand
I go crazy, yeah
The music tells me what to feel
I like you now
But is it real by the time we say goodnight
I don't know if this is right
And I feel you (you) coming through my veins.
Am I into you (you) or is it music to blaime?
Who owns my heart
Is it love or is it art
'Cause the way you got your body movin' got me confusin'
And I can't tell if it's the beat or sparks
Who owns my heart
Is it love or is it art
You know I wanna believe that we're a masterpiece
But sometimes it's hard to tell in the dark
Who owns my heart
The room is full
But all I see is the way
Your eyes just blaze through me
Like fire in the dark
We're like living art
And it hits me
Like a ... of wave
Are you feeling me
Or is the music to blame
Who owns my heart
Is it love or is it art
'Cause the way you got your body movin' got me confusin'
And I can't tell if it's the beat or sparks
Who owns my heart
Is it love or is it art
You know I wanna believe that we're a masterpiece
But sometimes it's hard to tell in the dark
Who owns my heart
So come on, baby
Keep on bumping me
Keep on rubbing me
Like a rodeo
Baby, hold me close
Come on
Here we go,Here we go,Here we go
And it hits me
Like a ... of wave
Are you feeling me
Or is the music to blame
Who owns my heart
Is it love or is it art
'Cause the way you got your body movin' got me confusin'
And I can't tell if it's the beat or sparks
Who owns my heart
Is it love or is it art
You know I wanna believe that we're a masterpiece
But sometimes it's hard to tell in the dark
Who owns my heart