Can you wait to get home
Baby dial your number
Can you pick up the phone
Cause I wanna holla
Daydreamin about you all day
in school cant concentrate
Wanna have your voice in my ear till
mama come and say its too late
Cause the lights are on outside
Wish there was somewhere to hide
Cause I just don't want to say goodbye
Cause you are my baby baby
Nothing really matters
I don't really care what nobody tell me
I'm gonna be here
It's a matter of extreme importance
my first teenage love affair
Another secret meeting
on the 5th floor staircase
i'm gonna give you this letter
of all the things i can't say
want u to be my first my last
my ending and beginning
i write your name in my book your last name
my first i'm your mrs
Cause the lights are on outside
Wish there was somewhere to hide
I just don't want to say goodbye
Cause you are my baby baby
Nothing really matters
I don't really care what nobody tell me
I'm gonna be here
Its a matter of extreme importance
my first teenage love affair
hey boy
you know i really like being with you
just hanging out is fine
so maybe we can go to first base
because I feel you
second base
want you to feel me too boy
third base
betta pump the brakes and baby slow down
i gotta go home now
Cause the lights are on outside
Wish there was somewhere to hide
Cause I just don't want to say goodbye
Cause you are my baby baby
Nothing really matters
I don't really care what nobody tell me
I'm gonna be here
Its a matter of extreme importance
my first teenage love affair
my baby baby
nothing really matters
i don't really care
what nobody tell me
i'm gonna be here
it's a matter of extreme importance
my first teenage love affair