If I had no more time
No more time left to be here
Would you cherish what we have
Cause I'm everything that you were looking for
If I couldn't feel your touch
And no longer were you with me
I'll be wishing you were here
To be everything that I've been looking for
I don't want to forget the present is a gift
And I don't want to take for granted the time you may have here with me
Cause Lord only knows another day is not really guaranteed, so
Everytime you hold me
Hold me like this is the last time
Everytime you kiss me
Kiss me like you'll never see me again
Everytime you touch me
Touch me like this is the last time
Promise that you'll love me
Love me like you'll never see me again
How many really know what love is
Now you never will
Do you know until you lose it
That it's everything that we are looking for
When I wake up in the morning
With you beside me
I'm so thankful that I found
Everything that I've been looking for
I don't want to forget the present is a gift
And I don't want to take for granted the time you may have here with me
Cause Lord only knows another day is not really guaranteed, so
Everytime you hold me
Hold me like this is the last time
Everytime you kiss me
Kiss me like you'll never see me again
Everytime you touch me
Touch me like this is the last time
Promise that you'll love me
Love me like you'll never see me again