Moment of honesty
Someone's gotta take the lead tonight
Who's it gonna be?
I'm gonna sit right here
And tell u all that comes to me
And if you have something to say
You should say right now
You give me a feeling that I never felt before
And I deserve it, I know I deserve it
It's becoming something that's impossible to ignore
And I can't take it
I was wondering maybe
Could I make you my baby
If we do the Un-thinkable
Would it make us look crazy
If you ask me I'm ready
I know you were sent to me
This is exactly how it should feel
When it's meant to be
Time is only wasting
So why wait for eventually
If we gonna do something about it
We should do right now
You give me a feeling that I never felt before
And I deserve it, I know I deserve it
It's becoming something that's impossible to ignore
It is what we make it
I was wondering maybe
Could I make you my baby
If we do the Un-thinkable
Would it make us look crazy
Or would it be so beautiful
Either way I'm saying
If you ask me I'm ready
Yeah
Say
Why give up before we try
Feel the lows before the highs
Clip our wings before we fly away
I can't say I came prepared
I'm suspended in the air
Won't you come be in the sky with me
I was wondering maybe
Could I make you my baby
If we do the Un-thinkable
Would it make us look crazy
Or would it be so beautiful
Either way I'm saying
If you ask me I'm ready