Baby, baby, baby
From the day I saw you
I really really want to catch your eye
There's something special 'bout you
I must really like you
Cause not a lotta guys are worth my time
Ooo baby, baby, baby
It's gettin kind of crazy
Cause you are takin over my mind
And it feels like oooooo
But you don't know my name
And I swear it feels like
ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo
You don't know my name
(round and round and round we go,
will you ever know)
Oh baby baby baby
I see us on our first date
You're doin everything
that makes me smile
And when we had our first kiss
It happened on a Thursday
Ooooo it set my soul on fire
Ooo baby baby baby
I can't wait for the first time
My imagination's runnin wild
It feels like ooooo
You don't know my name
And I swear it baby, it feels like
oooo ooooo ooooo ooooo
You don't know my name
(round and round and round we go,
will you ever know)
"I'm sayin, he don't even know
what he's doin' to me
Got me feelin' all crazy inside
I'm feelin like"
Owww! Ooooo Oooooo
Doin more than I've ever done
for anyone's attention
Take notice of what's in front of you
Cause did I mention you're 'bout
to miss a good thing
And you'll never know how good it feels
to have all of my affection
And you'll never get a chance
to experience my lovin'
Cause my lovin' feels like ooooooo
You don't know my name
(round and round and round we go,
will you ever know
And I swear it feels like
oooo ooooo ooooo ooooo
You don't know my name
(round and round and round we go,
will you ever know)
Ohhh
Will you ever know it, no no no no no
Will you ever know it?
"I'm gonna have to just go ahead
and call this boy.
Hello? Can I speak to -- to Michael?
Oh hey, how you doin?
Uh, I feel kinda silly doin' this,
But um, this is the waitress from
the coffee house on 39th and Lennox
You know, the one with the braids?
Yeah, well I see you on Wednesdays all the time
You come in every Wednesday
on your lunch break, I think
And you always order the special,
with the hot chocolate
And my manager be tripping and stuff
Talking bout we gotta use water
But I always use some milk
and cream for you
Cause I think you're kinda sweet.
Anyway you always got
on some fly blue suit
'n your cufflinks are shining all bright
So, whatchu do? Oh, word?
Yeah, that's interesting
Look man, I mean
I don't wanna waste your time but
I know girls don't usually do this,
But I was wondering if maybe
we could get together
Outside the restaurant one day
Cause I do look a lot different
outside my work clothes
I mean we could just go across
the street to the park right here
Wait, hold up, my cell phone's breakin up,
hold up
Can you hear me now? Yeah
So, what day did you say?
Oh yeah, Thursday's perfect, man:."
And it feels like oooo
You don't know my name
(round and round and round we go,
will you ever know)
Baby Baby I swear it's like oooooo
You don't know my name, no no no
(round and round and round we go,
will you ever know)
And it feels like oooo
You don't know my name
And I swear on my mother
and father it feels like
Oooo ooo oooo ooo ooo ooo