Used to dream of being a millionaire, without a care
But if I'm seeing my dreams and you aren't there
'cause it's over
bet just wont be fair
darling,
gonna be a poor woman living on the street,
no food to eat,
cause i don't want no pie if i have to cry.
cause it's over
when you said goodbye!
all at once...
i had it all
but it doesn't mean anything
now that you're gone
from above seems i had it all
but it doesn't mean anything
since you're gone
now i see myself through different eyes,
it's no surprise!
being alone will make you realise
when it's over!
all in love is fair
I shoulda been there, I shoulda been there, I shoulda shoulda love is fair.
all at once...
i had it all
but it doesn't mean anything
now that you're gone
from above seems i had it all
but it doesn't mean anything
since you're gone
I know I pushed you away
What can I do that would save our love
Take these material things
They don't mean nothing
Its you that I want
All at once...
I had it all
But it doesn't mean anything
Now that you're gone
From above,
Seems I had it all
But it doesn't mean anything
Since you're gone
all at once...
i had it all
but it doesn't mean anything
now that you're gone
from above seems i had it all
but it doesn't mean anything