Alicia Keys - No One
from the album "As I Am"
I just want you close
Where you can stay forever
You can be sure
That it will only get better
You and me together
Through the days and nights
I don't worry 'cause
Everything's gonna be alright
People keep talking
They can say what they like
But all I know is
Everything's gonna be alright
No one, no one, no one
Can get in the way of what I'm feeling
Can get in the way of what I feel for you
You, you
When the rain is pouring down
And my heart is hurting
You will always be around
Yes, I know, for certain
You and me together
Through the days and nights
I don't worry 'cause
Everything's gonna be alright
People keep talking
They can say what they like
But all I know is
Everything's gonna be alright
No one, no one, no one
Can get in the way of what I'm feeling
Can get in the way of what I feel for you
You, you
Can get in the way of what I feel
I know, some people search the world
to find something like what we have
I know, people will try, try to divide
something so real
so 'till the end of time
I'm telling you that
No one, no one
Can get in the way of what I'm feeling
No one, no one, no one
Can get in the way of what I feel for you
Oh oh oh oh ooh, oh oh oh oh ooh,
oh oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh oooh