I keep your picture beside my bed,
And I still remember everything you said,
I always thought our love was so right
I guess I was wrong.
Always thought you'll be by my side papa now you gone.
(And I'm not tryna hear that shit)
All I wanna know baby..
If what we had was good..
How come you don't call me..
anymore?
Still light the fire on a rainy night,
I still like it better when you holdin' me tight,
Everbody said..
Everybody said that we should never part, en...
Tell me baby,baby,baby,Why..
Why you wanna go and break my heart?
All I wanna know baby,
If what we had was good..
How come you don't call me(call me)
anymore?
Oh oooooooooooo hey eeeeeee
Sometimes it feels like I'm gonna die..
If you don't call me papa
ooooh you got to try..
Gone get down on my knees hopin' you please..
Please oh ooooh
Woo want you call me sometime papa?
(don't you call me more oh)
Why on earth can't you just pick-up the phone,
You know I don't like to be alone!
How come you don't call me-(Why must you torture me?)
How come you don't call me-