Weren't you the one who said that
you don't want me anymore
and how you need your space,
and give the keys back to your door
and how I cried and tried and tried
to make you stay with me
but still you said the love was gone
and that I had to leave
(Now you)
talking 'bout a family,
sayin' I complete your dream
(Now you)
sayin' I'm your everything
you're confusing me what you say to me
don't play with me, don't play with me
Cause what goes around comes around
what goes up must come down
Now who's cryin', desirin' to come back to me
what goes around comes around
what goes up must come down
Now who's cryin', desirin' to come back
I remember when I was sitting home alone
waiting for you 'til 3 o'clock in the morn
and when you came home
you'd always have some sorry exscuse
and explainin' to me, like I'm just some kinda fool
I sacrifie the things I want to just to do things for you
and when it's time to do for me
you never come through
(Now you)
want to be a bond of me (eyy)
have so much to say to me (heyy)
(Now you)
want to make time for me
What you do to me
You're confusin' me
Don't play with me, don't play with me
Cause what goes around comes around
what goes up must come down
Now who's crying desiring to come back to me
what goes around comes around
what goes up must come down
Now who's cryin', desirin' to come back
I remember when I was sittin' home alone
waitin' for you 'til 3 o'clock in the morn
night after night knowin' somthing goin' on
wasn't long before I be gawa gawa gone
lord knows it wasn't easy, believe me
never thought you'd be the one that would decieve me
and never do what you're supposed to do
no need to hose me fool, 'cause I'm over you
Cause what goes around comes around
what goes up must come down
Now who's crying desiring to come back to me
what goes around comes around
what goes up must come down
Gotta stop tryin' to come back to me
it's called karma baby and it goes around
Now who's cryin', desirin' to come back to me