Some people live for the fortune
Some people live just for the fame
Some people live for the power,yeah
Some people live to play the game
Some people think that the physical things
Define what's within
And I've been there before that life's a bore
So full of the superficial
Some people want it all
But I don't want nothing at all
If it ain't you baby
If I ain't got you baby
Some people want diamond rings
Some just want everything
But everything means nothing
If I ain't got you,yeah
Some people search for a fountain
That promises forever young
Some people need three dozen roses
And that's the only way to prove you love them
Hand me the world on a silver plater
And what good would it be
With no one to share
With no one who truly cares for me
Some people want it all
But I don't want nothing at all
If it ain't you baby
If I ain't got you baby
Some people want diamond rings
Some just want everything
But everything means nothing
If I ain't got you,you,you
Some people want it all
But I don't want nothing at all
If it ain't you baby
If I ain't got you baby
Some people want diamond rings
Some just want everything
But everything means nothing
If I ain't got you,yeah
If I ain't got you with me baby
ohh,so nothing in this whole wide world don't mean a thing