Standing at this liquor store,
Whisky coming through my pores,
Feeling like I run this whole block.
Lotto tickets and cheap beer
That's why you can catch me here,
Tryna scratch my way up to the top.
Because my job got me going nowhere,
So I ain't got a thing to lose.
Take me to a place where I don't care,
This is me and my liquor store blues.
I'll take one shot for my pain,
One drag for my sorrow.
Get messed up today,
I'll be ok tomorrow.
One shot for my pain,
One drag for my sorrow.
Get messed up today,
I'll be ok tomorrow.
Me and my guitar tonight,
Singing to the city lights,
Tryna live on more than what I got.
Cause '68 Citrus ain't gonna pay the rent,
So I'll be out here til they call the cops.
Because my job got me going nowhere,
So I ain't got a thing to lose.
Take me to a place where I don't care,
This is me and my liquor store blues.
I'll take one shot for my pain,
One drag for my sorrow.
Get messed up today,
I'll be ok tomorrow.
One shot for my pain,
One drag for my sorrow.
Get messed up today,
I'll be ok tomorrow.
Here come Junior Gong
I'm flying high like superman
And thinking that I run the whole block
I dunno if it's just because
Pineapple kush between my jaws
Has got me feeling like I'm on top
Feeling like i would stand up to de cops
And stand up to de bigga heads
becaw de whole ah de ah saps
All de talk dem a talk
And dem fly make nah drop
Nuff ghetto youth cannot escape de trap
Give me this one shot for my pain,
One drag for my sorrow.
Get messed up today,
I'll be ok tomorrow.
One shot for my pain,
One drag for my sorrow.
Get messed up today,
I'll be ok tomorrow.