Beautiful girls all over the world
i could be chasing but my time would be wasted
they got nothing on you baby
nothing on you baby
not not nothing on you
i know you feel where i'm coming from
regardless of the things in my past that i've done
most of really was for the hell of the fun
on the carousel so around i spun (spun)
with no directions just tryna get some (some)
tryna chase skirts, living in the summer sun (sun)
this is how i lost more than i had ever won
and honestly i ended up with none
there's no much nonsense
it's on my conscience
i'm thinking baby i should get it out
and i don't wanna sound redundant
but i was wondering if there was something that you wanna know
(that you wanna know)
but never mind that we should let it go (we should let it go)
cos we don't wanna be a t.v episode (t.v episode)
and all the bad thoughts just let them go (go, go, go)
beautiful girls all over the world
i could be chasing but my time would be wasted
they got nothing on you baby
nothing on you baby
they might say hi and i might say hey
but you shouldn't worry about what they say
cos they got nothing on you baby
nothing on you baby
hands down there will never be another one
i been around and i never seen another one
look at your style they ain't really got nothing on
and you out and you ain't got nothing on
baby you the whole package plus you pay your taxes
and you keep it real while them other stay plastic
you're my wonder women call me mr. fantastic
stop.. now think about it
i've been to london, i've been to paris
even went out there to tokyo
back home down in georgia to new orleans
but you always still to show (still to show)
and just like that girl you got me fro (got me fro)
like a nintendo 64 (64)
if you never knew well now you know (know, know, know)
beautiful girls all over the world
i could be chasing but my time would be wasted
they got nothing on you baby
nothing on you baby
they might say hi and i might say hey
but you shouldn't worry about what they say
cos they got nothing on you baby
nothing on you baby
everywhere i go i'm always hearing your name (name, name)
and no matter where i'm at girl you make me wanna sing (sing)
weather a bus or a plane or a car or a train
no other girls in my brain and you the one to blame
beautiful girls all over the world
i could be chasing but my time would be wasted
they got nothing on you baby
nothing on you baby
they might say hi and i might say hey
but you shouldn't worry about what they say