Easy come, easy go
That's just how you live
Oh, take it all but you never give
Should've known you was trouble from the first kiss
Had your eyes wide open
Why were they open
Gave you all I had and you tossed it in the trash
You tossed it in the trash, you did
To give me all your love is all I ever ask
Cause what you don't understand is
I'd catch a grenade for ya
Throw my hand on a blade for ya
I'd jump in front of a train for ya
You know I'd do anything for ya
Oh, whoa
I would go through all this pain
Take a bullet straight through my brain
Yes, I would die for you baby
But you won't do the same
No,
Black and blue
Beat me till I'm numb
Tell the devil I said hey
When you get back to where you're from
Mad woman, bad woman
That's just what you are
Yeah, you smile in my face
Then rip the breaks out my car
Gave you all I had and you tossed it in the trash
You tossed it in the trash, yes, you did
To give me all your love is all I ever ask
Cause what you don't understand is
I'd catch a grenade for ya
Throw my hand on a blade for ya
I'd jump in front of a train for ya
You know I'd do anything for ya
Oh, whoa
I would go through all this pain
Take a bullet straight through my brain
Yes, I would die for you baby
But you won't do the same
If my body was on fire
Ooh, you'd watch me burn down in flames
You said you love me, you're a liar
Cause you never ever, ever did baby
But darling I'd catch a grenade for ya
Throw my hand on a blade for ya
I'd jump in front of a train for ya
You know I'd do anything for ya
Oh, whoa
I would go through all this pain
Take a bullet straight through my brain
Yes, I would die for you baby
But you won't do the same
No you won't do the same
You wouldn't do the same
You'd never do the same
No,