Today I don't feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like pickin up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
'Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything
I'm gonna kick my feet up, then stare at the fan
Turn the TV on, throw my hand in my pants
Nobody's gonna tell me I can't
Nah!
I'll be lounging on a couch, just chillin in my snuggie
Click to MTV so they can teach me how to Douggie,
'Cause in my castle I'm the freakin man
Yes, I said it
I said it, 'cause I can!
Today I don't feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like pickin up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
'Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything
Nothing at all
Tomorrow I wake up do some P90x
Meet a really nice girl
Have some really nice sex
And she's gonna scream out this is great
Oh my God, this is great
Yeah!
I might mess around and get my college degree,
I bet my old man will be so pround of me.
But sorry paps you'll just have to wait
Yes, I said it
I said it, 'cause I can!
Today I don't feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like pickin up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
'Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything
No, I ain't gonna comb my hair
'Cause I ain't going anywhere
No,
I'll just strut in my birthday suit,
And let everything hang loose
Yeah,
Today I don't feel like doing anything
I just wanna lay in my bed
Don't feel like pickin up my phone
So leave a message at the tone
'Cause today I swear I'm not doing anything
Nothing at all,
Nothing at all.