Hey
Slow it down
Whataya want from me?
Yeah
I'm afraid
Whataya want from me?
There might have been a time
When I would give myself away
Oh ,once upon a time
I didn't give a damn
But now
Here we are
So ,whataya want from me?
Whataya want from me?
Just don't give up
I'm working it out
Please don't give in
I won't let you down
It messed me up
Need a second to breathe
Just keep coming around
Hey!
Whataya want from me?
There
It's plain to see
That baby you're beautiful
And there's nothing wrong with you
It's me
I'm a freak
But thanks for loving me,
'cause you're doing it perfectly
And there might have been a time
When I would have let you slip away
I wouldn't even try
But I think you could save my life
Just don't give up
I'm working it out
Please don't give in
I won't let you down
It messed me up
Need a second to breathe
Just keep coming around
Hey!
Whataya want from me?
Just don't give up on me
I won't let you down
No, I won't ya let ya down
So wait!
Just don't give up
I'm working it out
Please don't give in
I won't let you down
It messed me up
Need a second to breathe
Just keep coming around
Hey!
Whataya want from me?
Just don't give up
I'm working it out
Please don't give in
I won't let you down
It messed me up
Need a second to breathe
Just keep coming around
Hey!
Whataya want from me?
Whataya want from me.....?