Adam Lambert - For Your Entertainment
So hot out the box
Can we pick up the pace?
Turn it up Heat it up I need to be entertained
Push the limit are you with it baby don't be afraid
I'ma hurt you real good
Let's go, it's my show
Baby do what I say
Don't trip off the bits that I'm gonna display
I told you I'ma hold you down until you're amazed
Give it to you till you're screaming my name
No escaping when I start
Once I'm in I own your heart
There's no way to ring the alarm
So hold on until it's over
Oh, do you know what you got into?
Can you handle what I'm about to do?
Cause it's about to get rough for you
I'm here for your entertainment
Oh, I bet you thought I was awfully sweet
You thought an angel swept you off your feet
But I'm about to turn up the heat
I'm here for your entertainment
It's all right, you'll be fine,
Baby I'm in control
Take the pain, take the pleasure
I'm the master of both
Close your eyes, not your mind
Let me into your soul
I'ma work you till you turn me around
No escaping when I start
Once I'm in I own your heart
There's no way to ring the alarm
So hold on until it's over
Oh, do you know what you got into?
Can you handle what I'm about to do?
Cause it's about to get rough for you
I'm here for your entertainment
Oh, I bet you thought I was awfully sweet
You thought an angel swept you off your feet
But I'm about to turn up the heat
I'm here for your entertainment
Do you like what you see?
Let me entertain you till you scream
Oh, do you know what you got into?
Can you handle what I'm about to do?
Cause it's about to get rough for you
I'm here for your entertainment
Oh, I bet you thought I was awfully sweet
You thought an angel swept you off your feet
But I'm about to turn up the heat
I'm here for your entertainment