Baby, you're lookin' fire hot.
I'll have you open all night like an IHOP
I take you home baby let you keep me company
You gimme some of you, I give you some of me
You look good, baby must taste heavenly
I'm pretty sure that you got your own recipe
So pick it up, pick it up, yeah I like you
I just can't get enough I got to drive through
Cause is me, you, you, me, me, you all night
Have it your way, foreplay
Before I feed you appetite
Let me get my ticket baby, let me get it line
I can tell the way you like it, baby, supersized
Hold on, you got yours, let me get mine
I ain't leavin' till they turn over the closed sign. Check it!
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body until you hear me out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out.
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body till it's lights out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out
Number one, I take two number three's
That's a whole lot of you and a side of me.
Now is it full of myself to want you full of me?
And if there's room for dessert then I want a piece
Baby get my order right, no errors.
Imma touch you in all the right areas
I could feed you, you could feed me.
Girl, deliver that to me, come see me
Cause is me, you, you, me, me, you all night
Have it your way, foreplay. Before I feed you appetite
Do you like it well done, cause I do it well
Cause I'm well seasoned if you couldn't tell
Now let me walk into your body until you hear me out
And turn me on, my baby, dont you cut me out, Say
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body until you hear me out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body till it's lights out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out
Turn me on, my baby dont you. Cut me out
What's your name? What's your number?
I'm glad I came. Can you take my order?
What's your name? Girl, what's your number?
Come over here. what's your name?
Come closer. what's your number?
I'm over here. I'm glad I came.
A little closer. can you take my order?
Come over here. what's your name?
Come closer. what's your number?
I'm over here. I'm glad I came.
A little closer. Can you take my order?
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body until you hear me out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body till it's lights out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body until you hear me out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out
Take my order cause your body like a carry out
Let me walk into your body till it's lights out
Turn me on, my baby dont you cut me out