On behalf of the very Museum
thank you all for being here for such a monumental event
Now, this is the first edition from a series of seven
that we featured within the museum
and will be on display throughout the next four months.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you...
What is somebody like
you doin' in a place like this?
Say did you come alone or
did you bring all your friends?
Say whats your name?
What you drinking?
I think I know what are you thinking
Baby whats your sign,
tell me yours and ill tell you mine
Say What is someone like
you doin' in a place like this?
I'll never be the same
If we ever meet again
Won't let you get away
This free fall's got me me so
kiss me all night,
don't ever let me go
Ill never be the same
if we ever meet again
Do you come here much?
I swear I've seen your face before
You don't see me blush
but I cant help to want you more more
Baby tel me whats youre story?
I ain't shy, don't you worry
I'm flirting with my eyes
I wanna leave with you tonight
do you come here much?
I've gotta see your face some more
(some more Cause baby I)
I'll never be the same
If we ever meet again
Won't let you get away
This free fall's got me me so
kiss me all night,
don't ever let me go
I'll never be the same
If we ever meet again
If we ever meet again,
I'll have so much more to say
(Say if we ever meet again)
If we ever meet again, again
I wont let you go away
(Say if we ever meet again)
If we ever, ever meet again
I'll have so much more to say

(Say if we ever meet again)
If we ever, ever meet again
I wont let you go away!
I'll never be the same
If we ever meet again
Won't let you get away
This free fall's got me me so
kiss me all night,
don't ever let me go
I'll never be the same
If we ever meet again
Won't let you get away
This free fall's got me me so
kiss me all night,
don't ever let me go
I'll never be the same
If we ever meet again
Just when the night can't get no less
Pornstars struttin' while they dis'
Vixens fighting for their shirts
My buddy like Justin West, yes
You gonna finish, dear
And your body so superb
Me and you, dance with her
But your girl, face of the year
Face of the year