Is it going is it going is
it going is it going?
I don't know
what you're looking for
Let´s go
I'm the type of girl that'll
look you dead in the eye
I'm real as they come if
you don't know
why im fly-y-y-y-y
Seen ya try to switch it up
but girl you ain't that dope
I'm the wonderwoman
let me go get my robe
I'm a supermodel and mami,
si mami
Amnesty international got
bangkok to montauk on lock
You love my ass
and my abs
and the video for promiscuous
My style is ridiculous-s-s-s-s
If you see us in the club
we'll be acting real nice
If you see us on the floor
you'll be watchin all night
We ain't here to hurt nobody
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
Wanna see you work your body
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
When timbo is in the party
everbody put up their hands
I get a half a mill for my beats
you get a couple grand-d-d-d-d
Never gonna see the day that
i ain't got the upper hand
I'm respected from californ.i.a.
way down to japan
I'm a real producer
and you just the piano man
Your songs don't top the charts,
i heard em
I'm a real producer
and you just the piano man
Your songs don't top the charts,
i heard em
i'm not a fan-n-n-n
Niggaz talkin greasy im the one
that gave them they chance
Somebody need to tell em
that they can't do it like I can
If you see us in the club
we'll be acting real nice
If you see us on the floor
you'll be watchin all night
We ain't here to hurt nobody
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
Wanna see you work your body
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
Could you speak up and
stop the mumbling
I don't think you came in clear
Sitting on the top it's hard to hear
you from way up here
I saw you tryin to act cute on tv
just let me clear the air
We missed you on the
charts last week
Damn that's right,
you wasn't there
If sexy never left, then
why's everybody on my shi it it?
Don't hate on me just because
you didn't come up with it
So if you see us in the club go
on and walk the other way
'cause our run will never be over;
not at least until we say
If you see us in the club
we'll be acting real nice
If you see us on the floor
you'll be watchin all night
We ain't here to hurt nobody
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
Wanna see you work your body
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
If you see us in the club
we'll be acting real nice
If you see us on the floor
you'll be watchin all night
We ain't here to hurt nobody
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
Wanna see you work your body
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
If you see us in the club
we'll be acting real nice
If you see us on the floor
you'll be watchin all night
We ain't here to hurt nobody
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me
Wanna see you work your body
So give it to me give it
to me give it to me