Jennifer Lopez -  Papi Album: Love (2011)
Lisa,
Here I go,
You want your mail?
Yes, please
How are you doin'?
Ok!
He not back yet?
Not yet,
Wait, one second
Eat this cookie
And your love will come back
Just one small bite
It's most stronger than you think
No, no, no
Dear I said a small bite, small bite
It broke and...
Let all the heat pour down
I'm good as long as he's around
He lets me wear the crown
I do my best to make him proud
Now all my super ladies
I got my baby, if you got your baby,
Move your body, dance for your papi
Rock your body, dance for your papi
Put your hands up in the air
Dance for your man if you care
Put your hands up in the air,
Move your body, dance for your papi
Rock your body, dance for your papi
Got that fruit?
Are you sure?
My rock is shinin' bright
Even if he ain't by my side
He makes sure that I glow
I make sure everybody knows
Now all my super ladies
I got my baby, if you got your baby,
Move your body, dance for your papi
Rock your body, dance for your papi
Put your hands up in the air
Dance for your man if you care
Put your hands up in the air,
Move your body, dance for your papi
Rock your body, dance for your papi
Put your hands up in the air
Dance for your man if you care
Put your hands up in the air,
Step up, let your hair down
Pop, drop, and lock it go all out
If he rocks tear up the crowd
Dance for your papi
Llegale, llegale
Sueltate el pelo
Levantate, cai, aseguralo
Llegale, llegale
Sueltate el pelo
Levantate, cai, aseguralo
Ve por todas,
Si el es lo maximo
Asota baldosa
Baila para tu papi
Stop!
Hold on a second
Now all my super ladies
I got my baby, if you got your baby,
Move your body, dance for your papi
Rock your body, dance for your papi
Put your hands up in the air
Dance for your man if you care
Put your hands up in the air,
Move your body, dance for your papi
Rock your body, dance for your papi
Put your hands up in the air
Dance for your man if you care
Put your hands up in the air,
Papi!
The were crazy did you see?