I'm a, a diva
I'm a, I'm a, a diva
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
Stop the track
Let me stay fax
Told you gimme a minute
and I'll be right back
Fifty Millions
around the world
And then say
that I couldn't get
And I got so stickin' filthy
with Benj's I can't spin
How you gon' be
talking shit?
You act like
I just got a fit
Been the number one diva
in this game for a minute
I know you're ought to pay
for the one that
they call the queen
Every radio ‘round the world know me ‘
cause this way I be
I'm a, a diva
I'm a, I'm a, a diva
I'm a, I'm a,..
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
When he pull up
Home to pop my hood up
Bet he betta have
a six pack in the coola
Gettin' money,
diva's gettin' money
If you ain't gettin' money
Then you ain't
got nothin' for me
Tell me somethin'
(Tell me somethin')
Where yo boss at?
(Where yo boss at?)
When my ladies up in here
they like to talk like
I wanna see ya
(I'd like to see her)
I'd like to meet ya
(I'd like to meet her)
What you say
(Not to me)
She ain't no diva
(She ain't no diva)
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
Six fifteen in my stilettos,
They struttin' in this game
What's yo age?
What's the question
They ask
when I hit the stage
I'm a diva, best believe
You see her she getting' paid
She ain't calling him
to greet her
She don't need him
her best man
This is a stick-up,
stick-up
I need ‘em bags,
all dat money
A stick-up,
stick-up
You see them ask
Where the money
All my ladies,
get it up
I see you,
I do the same
Take you to another level
No passengers on my plane
I'm a, a diva,
I'm a, I'm a, a diva
This is a stick-up,
stick-up
I need ‘em bags,
all dat money
Stick-up,
stick-up
You see them ask
Where the money
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
Diva is the female
version of the hustla
Of the hustla,
of the, of the hustla
I'm  a diva
I'm a, I'm a, a diva
Them hustlers
keep on talking
They like the way
Im walkin
Your sayin that
you want me...