Girls, we run this motha (yeah!)
GIRLS!
Who run the world? Girls!
We run this motha? Girls!
Some of them men think they freak this like we do
But no they don't
Make your cheques come at they neck,
Disrespect us no they won't
Boy don't even try to take us
Boy this beat is crazy
This is how they made me
Used to take this baby
This goes out to all my girls
That's in the club rocking the latest
Who will buy it for themselves and get more money later
I think I need a barber
None of these hoes can fade me
I'm so good with this,
I remind you I'm so hood with this
Boy I'm just playing, come here baby
Hope you still like me, If you hate me
My persuasion can build a nation
In this hour, our love we can devour
You'll do anything for me
Who run the world? Girls!
We run this motha? Girls!
It's hot up in here
DJ don't be scared to run this, run this back
I'm repping for the girls who taking over the world
Have me raise a glass for the college grads
Anyone rolling I'll let you know what time it is
You can't hold me
I broke my 9 to 5 and copped my cheque
This goes out to all the women getting it in,
Get on your grind
To the other men that respect what I do
Please accept my shine
Boy you know you love it
How we're smart enough to make these millions
Strong enough to bare the children
Then get back to business
See, you better not play me
Don't come here baby
Hope you still like me
If you hate me!
My persuasion can build a nation
In this hour
Our love we can devour
You'll do anything for me
Who run the world? Girls!
We run this motha? Girls!
Who are we? What's we want? The world.
Who run the world? Girls!