Damn that was so good I wanna buy him a short set
I'ma be like a jolly rancher that you get from the corner store
I'ma be like a waffle cone that's dripping down to the floor
The way you do if for me I can't lie
About to be up in the mall all night
Whatever I get you putting it on
Don't give me no lip let mama do it all
Let me be, I wants to be, gots to be
Your suga give mama some suga mama
Suga ma-ma-mama
I'm your suga mama, suga mama
Let me be, I wants to be, gots to be
New whip, new heavy on the wrist
Cause I'm a suga ma-ma-mama
I'm your suga mama, suga mama
Sit on mama lap
Come sit on mama lap
It's so good to the point that I'd
Do anything to keep you home
Baby what you want me to buy
My accountant's waiting on the phone
Just the thought of making love to you
Dropping everything that's what I'll do
Whatever I get you putting it on
Now take it off while I watch you perform
Let me be, I wants to be, gots to be
Your suga give mama some suga mama
Suga ma-ma-mama
I'm your suga mama, suga mama
Let me be, I wants to be, gots to be
New whip, new heavy on the wrist
Cause I'm a suga ma-ma-mama
I'm your suga mama, suga mama
Sit on mama lap
Come sit on mama lap
And I've always been the type to take care of mine
I know just what I'm doing
Don't you worry it's cool and everything is steady
Puttin' you on my taxes already, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I promise I won't let no bills get behind
Cause every touch, every kiss and hug
You 'bes believe it'll be on time
Suga mama mama mama yeah yeah yeah
Let me be, I wants to be, gots to be
Your suga give mama some suga mama
Suga ma-ma-mama
I'm your suga mama, suga mama
Let me be, I wants to be, gots to be
New whip, new heavy on the wrist
Cause I'm a suga ma-ma-mama
I'm your suga mama, suga mama
Sit on mama lap
Come sit on mama lap