Give it to mama
Give it give it
Give it to mama mama (oh)
Give it
Give it to mama mama
For some strange reason (huh)
You done pleasin me like it's ok (Oh oh ooooh)
Like a perm that's been left too long
It's like a burn
The result is it just won't take (Oh oh ooooh)
I can see
Now it's all coming so clear to me now
Misinterpreted all of my naiveness
Was just thinking if I had no you
Than I can't do
My stock just went up over 2 million
So if you want to
You got the green light
So if you want to (want to, want to)
So if you want to
You got the green light
Give it to mama
Go go go goooo
Go go RED LIGHT (ah) GREEN LIGHT!
Some sillies say I should be trophied
Cuz it gets no stronger (Oh oh ooooh)
Ladies ya'll know (yea girl ya'll know)
This pimp ish gets no older
Is that a threat (what's another threat)
Yep! (that's another threat)
From you, you can get no colder
You got the green light (whoa)
And you can't ride (whoa)
You holdin up traffic
Green means go!!
Go go go goooo
Go go RED LIGHT
(I said you're holdin up traffic green means go!!) GREEN LIGHT!
So if you want to
You got the green light (you got the green light babe!)
So if you want to (go!)
You got the green light (ooh!)
So if you want to (want to, want to)
You got the green light
So if you want to
Give it to mama
(Sung over go's)
Oh no problem you can go
I'm gon' find somebody else
So why not move along
You want a green light...so you can...GO!! (go, go, go)
Go go go goooo
Go go RED LIGHT (ah) GREEN LIGHT!
I gave all I could give
My love, my heart (my heart)
Now we're facing the end (the end) of what you did from the start
My love
Instrument Solo
(You're holdin up traffic, GREEN MEANS GO!!)
So if you want to (WHOA oh oh!)
You got the green light (WHOA oh oh!)
So if you want to (WHOA oh!)
So if you want to (Go!) (want to, want to)
You got the green light (Go go go go!)
So if you want to
You got the green light
Give it to mama
(Sung over go's)
Oh no problem you can go
I will find somebody else
So why not move along
You want a green light...so you can...GO!! (go, go, go)
Go go go goooo