(Turn The Lights On)
Every night I rush to my bed
With hopes that maybe I'll get a chance to see you
When i close my eyes
I'm going out of my head
Lost in a fairytale
Can you hold my hands and be my guide
Clouds filled with stars cover your skies
And I hope it rains
You're the perfect lullaby
What kinda dream am is this?
You could be a sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Either way I, don't wanna wake up from you (Turn The Lights On)
Sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Somebody pinch me, your love's too good to be true (Turn The Lights On)
My guilty pleasure I ain't going no where
Baby long as you're here
I'll be floating on air cause you're my
You can be a sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Either way I, don't wanna wake up from you (Turn The Lights On)
I mention you when I say my prayers
I wrap you around around all of my thoughts
Boy you're my temporary high
I wish that when I wake up you're there
To wrap your arms around me for real
And tell me you'll stay by side
Clouds filled with stars cover your skies
And I hope it rains
You're the perfect lullaby
What kinda dream is this
You can be a sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Either way I, don't wanna wake up from you (Turn The Lights On)
Sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Somebody pinch me, your love's too good to be true (Turn The Lights On)
My guilty pleasure I ain't going no where,
Baby long as you're here
I'll be floating on air cause you're my
You can be a sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Either way I, don't wanna wake up from you (Turn The Lights On)
Tattoo your name across my heart
So it will remain
Not even death can make us part
What kind of dream is this?
You can be a sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Either way I, don't wanna wake up from you (Turn The Lights On)
Sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Somebody pinch me, your love's too good to be true (Turn The Lights On)
My guilty pleasure I ain't going no where
Baby long as you're here
I'll be floating on air cause you're my,
You can be a sweet dream or a beautiful nightmare
Either way I, don't wanna wake up from you (Turn The Lights On)