I'm a train wreck in the morning
I'm a bitch in the afternoon
Every now and then without warning
I can be really mean towards you
I'm a puzzle yes indeed
Ever-complex in every way
And all the pieces aren't even in the box
And yet, you see the picture clear as day
I don't know why you love me
And that's why I love you
You catch me when I fall
Accept me flaws and all
And that's why I love you
And that's why I love (hmm)
I neglect you when I'm working (ha ha ha uhn)
When I need attention
I tend to nag (oh oh ha uhn)
I'm a host of imperfection (ha ha ha uhn)
And you see past all that (hm hm uhn uhhhh uhn)
I'm a peasant by some standards (ha ha ha ha uhn)
But in your eyes I'm a queen (oh oh ha uhn)
You see potential in all my flaws (ha ha ha uh uh)
And that's exactly what I need
I don't know why you love me
And that's why I love you
You catch me when I fall
Accept me flaws and all
And that's why I love you
And that's why I love you (ah)
I don't know why you love me
And that's why I love you
You catch me when I fall
Accept me flaws and all
And that's why I love you
And that's why I love you (ah)