Hey baby how you doing?
You know Im gonna cut right to the chase.
Some women were made,
but me, myself.
I like to think I was created,
for a special purpose.
I mean, whats more special than you, you feel me?
Its a long way but lets get lost.
You dont need to call into work, cuz you're the boss.
For real want you to show me how you feel,
I consider myself lucky thats a big deal.
I well you got the key to my heart,
but you aint gonna need it.
I'd rather you open up my body.
And show me secrets.
You didnt know was inside,
No need for me to lie.
It's too big,
It's too wide,
It's too strong,
It wont fit,
It's too much,
It's too tough,
He talks like this,
Cuz he can back it up.
He got a big ego,
Such a huge ego,
I love his big ego,
It's too much,
He walks like this,
cuz he can back it up.
Usually I'm humble,
but right now I dont choose.
You can leave with me,
or you could have the blues.
Some call it arrogant.
I call it confidant.
You decide when you find,
on what I'm working with.
Damn I know, I'm killing you with them legs.
Better yet them thighs.
Matter a fact its my smile,
or maybe my eyes.
Boy you a site to see,
kind of something like me.
It's too big,
It's too wide,
It's too strong,
It wont fit,
It's too much,
It's too tough,
I talk like this,
cuz I can back it up.
I got a big ego,
Such a huge ego,
but he love my big ego,
It's too much.
I walk like this,
cuz I can back it up.
I talk like this,
I can back it up.
I walk like this,
cuz I can back it up.
It's too big,
It's too wide,
It's too strong,
It wont fit,
It's too much,
It's too tough,
He talks like this,
Cuz he can back it up.
He got a big ego,
Such a huge ego,
I love his big ego,
It's too much,
He walks like this,
cuz he can back it up.
Ego so big.
You must admit.
I got every reason to feel like Im that bitch.
Ego so strong, if you dont know.
I dont need no beat, I can sing it with piano.