To be or not to be
Not
Hold Up, bring the beat back
Stop, I ain't ready yet
Wait, let me fix my hair (yes, yes)
Yes mam (yes mam) Yes
I think I'm ready
Been locked up in the house way too long,
It's time to get it,
Cause once again he's out doing wrong,
And my girls are so real,
Said it's been a minute since I had some
He's been acting up, but he won't be the only one
(Oh) Cause when he acts up (Oh) that's when you put it on,
(Oh) Been on him up tight (Oh) this is your song
(Oh) Hold out your back (Oh) time to impress
(Oh) Pull out your freakum dress
Oooh put your freakum dress on Oooh put your freakum dress on
Oooh Every woman got one Oooh Shut it down when the time's come
Oooh Pull out the big gun Oooh and put your freakum dress on
Soon as you saw me, turned on by how the dress was fitting right
Short and backless (backless, backless)
See my silhouette in the moonlight
Such an attraction, keep telling me how my outfit's so nice
Little did he know, Ha my man gonna take it off tonight
(Oh) Cause when he act up (Oh) that's when you put it on,
(Oh) Been on him up tight (Oh) this is your song
(Oh) Hold out your back (Oh) time to impress
(Oh) Pull out your freakum dress
Oooh put your freakum dress on Oooh put your freakum dress on
Oooh Every woman got one Oooh Shut it down when the time's come
Oooh Pull out the big gun Oooh and put your freakum dress on
All the ladies (oh) you with this and you're dressed up in your dresses,
and ur bestest with no reason?
Get ready to freakum dress em
When you put it on it's an invitation,
When they play your the song you go up and shake it,
Work it out on your man you don't have to waste it,
Spin it all around then take it to the ground and
When you put it on it's an invitation,
When they play your the song you go up and shake it,
Work it out on your man you don't have to waste it,
Spin it all around then take it to the ground and
(Oh) Cause when he acts up (Oh) that's when you put it on,
(Oh) Been on him up tight (Oh) this is your song
(Oh) Hold out your back (Oh) time to impress
(Oh) Pull out your freakum dress
Oooh put your freakum dress on Oooh put your freakum dress on
Oooh Every woman got one Oooh Shut it down when the time's come
Oooh Pull out the big gun Oooh and put your freakum dress on
Ladies look here, when you been with your man for a long time (oh)
Every time and then you gotta go back in the closet and pull out that freakum dress (oh) uh,
I got my freakum dress on, I got my freakum dress on (oh) I got my freakum dress on, I got my freakum dress on (oh)