All the single ladies
Now put your hands up
Up in the club, we just broke up
I'm doing my own little thing
you decided to dip but now you wanna trip
Cuz another brother noticed me
I'm up on him, he up on me
dont pay him any attention
cuz i cried my tears, GAVE three good years
Ya can't be mad at me
Cuz if you liked it then you should have put a ring on it
If you liked it then you shoulda put a ring on it
Don't be mad once you see that he want it
wo oh ooh oh oh ooh oh oh ooh oh oh oh x2
Cuz if you liked it then you should have put a ring on it
If you liked it then you shoulda put a ring on it
Don't be mad once you see that he want it
I got gloss on my lips, a man on my hips
hold me tighter than my Dereon jeans
acting up, drink in my cup
I couldnt care less what you think
I need no permission, did I mention
Dont pay him any attention
Cuz you had your turn
But now you gonna learn
What it really feels like to miss me
Cuz if you liked it then you should have put a ring on it
If you liked it then you shoulda put a ring on it
Don't be mad once you see that he want it
wo oh ooh oh oh ooh oh oh ooh oh oh oh x2
Cuz if you liked it then you should have put a ring on it
If you liked it then you shoulda put a ring on it
Don't be mad once you see that he want it
wo oh ooh oh oh ooh oh oh ooh oh oh oh x2
Don't treat me to the things of this world
I'm not that kind of girl
Your love is what I prefer, what I deserve
Is a man that makes me, then takes me
And delivers me to a destiny, to infinity and beyond
Pull me into your arms
Say I'm the one you WANT
If you don't, you'll be alone
And like a ghost I'll be gone
All the single ladies
Now put your hands up
woo oh ooh oh oh ooh oh oh ooh
oh oh oh 2x
Cuz if you liked it then you should have put a ring on it
If you liked it then you shoulda put a ring on it
Don't be mad once you see that he want it
Cuz if you liked it then you should have put a ring on it
If you liked it then you shoulda put a ring on it
Don't be mad once you see that he want it