Now, now, now, honey,
You better sit down and look around,
Cause you must've bumped yo' head.
And I love you enough to talk some sense back into you, baby,
I'd hate to see you come home, me the kids,
And the dog is gone,
Check my credentials...
I give you everything you want, everything you need,
Even your friends say I'm a good woman.
All I need to know is why?
Why don't you love me? (Love me)
Tell me, baby, why don't you love me, (Love me)
When I make me so damn easy to love? (To love)
And why don't you need me? (Need me)
Tell me, baby, why don't you need me, (Why don't you need me)
When I make me so damn easy to need? (To need, To need)
I got beauty, I got class,
I got style, and I got ass,
And you don't even care to care.
Looka here...
I even put money in the bank account,
Don't have to ask no one to help me out,
You don't even notice that.
Why don't you love me? (Love me)
Tell me, baby, why don't you love me, (Love me)
When I make me so damn easy to love? (Easy, to love me, love me, love me)
Why don't you need me?
Tell me, baby, why don't you need me,
When I make me so damn easy to need?
I got beauty, I got heart,
Keep my head in them books, I'm sharp,
But you don't care to know I'm smart.
Now, now, now, now, now, now, now...
I got moves in your bedroom,
Keep you happy with the nasty things I do,
But you don't seem to be in tune.
Why don't you love me? (Love me)
Tell me, baby, why don't you love me, (Love me)
When I make me so damn easy to love? (Easy, to love me, lo-lo-love me, love me)
Why don't you need me?
Tell me, baby, why don't you need me,
When I make me so damn easy to need?
Why don't you love me? (Love me)
Tell me, baby, why don't you love me, (Love me)
When I make me so damn easy to love? (Easy, to love me, lo-lo-love me, love me)
Why don't you need me?
Tell me, baby, why don't you need me,
When I make me so damn easy to need?
(There's nothing not to love about me) There's nothing not to love about me,
No, no, there's nothing not to love about me. (Nothing not to love about me)
I'm lovely...
There's nothing not to need about me.
(There's nothing not to need about me)
No, no, there's nothing not to need about me.
Maybe you're just not the one,
Or maybe you're just plain...
Dumb!