If I ain't got nothing,
I got you
If I ain't got something I don't give a damn,
cause I got it with you
I don't know much about algebra,
but I know one plus one equals two
And it's me and you,
thats all we'll have when the world is thru
Cause baby we ain't got nothing without love
Darling you got enough for the both of us
So come on baby,
make love to me
When my days look low,
pull me in close and don't let me go.
Make love to me.
So that when the worlds at war,
that our love heal us all
Right now baby make love to me
ooh ooh make love to me.
Hey! I don't know much about guns
but I...I've been shot by you
Hey! And I don't know when I'm gon die,
but I hope that I'm gon die by you
Hey! And I don't know much about fighting,
but I, I know I will fight for you
Hey! Just when I ball up my first I realize that
I'm laying right next to you
Baby we ain't nothing but love,
and darling you got enough for the both of us
ohhh Make love to me...
when my days look low,
pull me in close and don't let me go.
Make love to me...so that when the worlds at war,
that our love heal us all
Help me let down my guard,
make love to me
ooh ooh ooh make love to me