How you doin' honey baby
You know I don't ask for much but
For a girl spending time alone
Can be pretty rough
But I get a knock on my door
You know it's yours for sure
We can't wait for the bedroom
So we just hit the floor
(Sing it girl)
Is ya'll all right
I don't know but I know what's happened to me girl
Uh, break it down now
Is ya'll all right
I don't know but I know what's happened to me girl
Uh, break it down now
See ya gotta work it out
Brotha gotta work it out
Oh oh
Cheer it for your horn now
So we shakin' back and forth now
Just keep it comin' Babe
Treat my body like a guitar
You gotta, gotta keep on strummin'
But in the back of my mind (I wonder)
Is it gonna be the last time
Well if it ain't about lovin'
And you gonna keep it comin'
Well baby with me that's fine
Is ya'll all right
I don't know but I know what's happened to me girl
Uh, break it down now
Is ya'll all right
I don't know but I know what's happened to me girl
Uh, break it down now
See ya gotta work it out
Brotha gotta work it out
Oh oh
Say it for your horn now
I like this
Uh, looka here
So baby hold me
Like you don't wanna let go
I'm feelin' sexy
'Cos boy you workin' it out
Now you are giving me a taste of your honey
I want the whole beehive (whole beehive)
I betta call you my sugar 'cos
I (I) had the sweetest time
See ya gotta work it out
Brotha gotta work It out
I like it when the horn blows
Austin bettter work it out (ha)
Foxxy better work it out (ha)