I got a big ego, (hahaha)
I’m such a big ego, (hahaha)
I got a big, (hahaha), Ego,
She love my big, (hahaha), Ego,
So stroke my big, (hahaha), Ego,
I like to joke around a little bit but here we go,
Welcome to the wonderful world,
Of go play the earl coz,
Everything I throw up, blow up,
Talking to the girl,
She said, know what, grow up,
You nasty,
I don’t understand why they trippin’,
If you ask me,
Flow is just as nice as,
I admit the propane,
I just spit, probably,
Just raise the gas prices,
Everybody in the club,
Try and get as fresh as me,
What you want dog,
Trying to stay recession free,
And spit, refreshly,
When I rock the stadium,
You probably get sweaty,
You should bring a extra tee,
Now I’m standing next to Jay,
Who standing next to B,
You coulda been anywhere in the world,
But you’re here with me,
That’s good for ego,
Me and my ego,
And it go wherever we go,
My ego is my imaginary friend,
He was with me when I was only imagining,
I had dreams of the league,
One day I play Kobe,
I walk up the puff and he already know me,
Coulda let the dream killers, kill my self esteem,
Or use the arrogance as a steam that power my dreams,
And my ego,
It's on baby, let's get lost,
You don't need to call into work 'cause you're the boss,
For real, want you to show me how you feel,
I consider myself lucky, that's a big deal,
Why? Well, you got the key to my heart,
but you aint gonna need it.
I'd rather you open up my body.
And show me secrets.
You didnt know was inside,
No need for me to lie.
It's too big, it's too wide,
It's too strong, it won't fit,
It's too much, it's too tough,
He talk like this 'cause he can back it up,
He got a big ego, such a huge ego,
I love his big ego, it's too much,
He walk like this 'cause he can back it up,
Usually I'm humble, right now I don't choose,
You can leave with me or you could have the blues,
Some call it arrogant, I call it confident,
You decide when you find on what I'm working with,
Damn I know I'm killing you with them legs,
Better yet them thighs,
Matter a fact it's my smile or maybe my eyes,
Boy you a site to see, kind of something like me,
It's too big, it's too wide,
It's too strong, it won't fit,
It's too much, it's too tough,
I talk like this 'cause I can back it up,
I got a big ego, such a huge ego,
But he love my big ego, it's too much,
I walk like this 'cause I can back it up,
It's too big, it's too wide,
It's too strong, it won't fit,
It's too much, it's too tough,
He talk like this 'cause he can back it up,
He got a big ego, such a huge ego,
I love his big ego, it's too much,
He walk like this 'cause he can back it up,
Ego so big, you must admit,
I got every reason to feel like I'm that bitch,
Ego so strong, if you ain't know,
I don't need no beat, I can sing it with piano.