9....4....8....1
B-Day
Mission one,
Ima put this on
When he see me in this dress I'ma get me some
Mission two,
Gotta make that call
Tell'em get the bottles poppin when they play my song
Mission three
Got my three best friends
Like we do it all the time we gon do it again
Mission four
Drop the vintage Rolls
Drop a couple hundreds tell'em leave it at the door
I aint worried doing me tonight
A little sweat aint never hurt nobody
While ya'll standin on the wall
I'm the one tonight gettin bodied
Gettin bodied (gettin bodied)
Gettin bodied (Im the only one tonight gettin bodied)
Gettin bodied
Want my body? (gettin bodied)
Won't you get me bodied (gettin bodied)
You want my body (Im the only one tonight gettin bodied)
Won't you get me bodied
Can you get me bodied
I wanna be myself tonight
Don't you see my body
I wanna let it out tonight
Wanna party, wanna dance, wanna be myself tonight
Who's that?
Who is it?
It's B
Mission five,
Skip to the front of the line
Let me fix my hair up fo' I go inside
Mission six
Gotta check these chicks
Cuz you know they gon block when I take these flicks
Mission seven
Got make my rounds
Givin eyes to the guys now I think I found him
Mission eight
While we're conversating we can skip small talk let's cut right to the chase
Hook:
I aint worried doing me tonight
A little sweat aint never hurt nobody
While ya'll standin on the wall
I'm the one tonight gettin bodied
Gettin bodied (gettin bodied)
Gettin bodied (Im the only one tonight gettin bodied)
Gettin bodied
Want my body? (gettin bodied)
Won't you get me bodied (gettin bodied)
You want my body (Im the only one tonight gettin bodied)
Won't you get me bodied
You see my body, I gotta know I'd like to know if I can get me bodied
I'm kinda tight, I'm feelin right I'd like to see somebody
I wanna let it out tonight
Wanna dance, wanna party wanna be myself tonight
Can you get me bodied
I wanna be myself tonight
Don't you see my body
I wanna let it out tonight
Wanna party, wanna dance, wanna be myself tonight
Baby all I want
Is to let it go
Aint no worries no
We can dance all night
Get me bodied
That means come closer to me
While we grind to the beat
And your body touchin me
All I need
Is to let it be
Aint no worries no
Boy dance with me
Feel my body
Dont stop just come closer to me
While we grind to the beat
And your body touchin my body
All I'm with tonight is gettin bodied
Aint no shame cuz I gotta get mine
I swing my hair and kick off my shoes
Come here boy, let me work on you
I aint worried doing me tonight
A little sweat aint never hurt nobody
While ya'll standin on the wall
I'm the one tonight gettin bodied
Gettin bodied (gettin bodied)
Want my body?
Won't you get me bodied
You want my body
Won't you get me bodied Hey
Ladies on the floor
all my ladies on the floor
if you ready get it ready lets get it and drop it!
Drop down low and sweep the floor wit it
drop drop down low and sweep the floor wit it
Do the uh oh do the uh oh
do the uh oh uh oh uh oh oh no no uh oh
do the uh oh do the uh oh uh oh uh oh oh no no
Pat your weaves ladies
pat pat pat your weaves ladies
watch it while he check up on it
Pat your weaves ladies
pat pat pat your weaves ladies
watch it while he check up on it
Tick tick tick tick fight
now tick tick tick tick tick tick fight
now tick tick tick tick fight
Now pose for the camera now click click click click
pose for the camera now flick flick flick flick
pose for the camera now click click click click
Do an old school dance an old school dance
an old school dance do an old school
do an old school dance an old school
Stop
now cool off cool off
cool off cool off
Drop
and cool off cool off
cool off cool off
Wind
Wind it back girl, wind it back girl
make your hair touch the floor wine it back,
make your hair touch the floor wine it back.
Drop to your knees arch your back girl
shake shake it like that alley cat,
Drop drop to your knees arch your back girl
shake shake it like that alley cat.
Shake ya derriere in them Dereon
Shake shake ya diary air in the House of Dereon
Do the scissor leg
touch ya heels touch ya toe
Do the Naomi Campbell walk
Naomi Campbell walk
Walk across the room like Naomi Campbell
Do the Naomi Campbell walk
Naomi Campbell walk
Walk across the room like Naomi Campbell
Snap for the kids
snap for the kids
Snap in a circle three times
Snap for the kids
snap for the kids
Snap in a circle three times
I touch ya body
while ya touch my body
We touching bodies tonight
We getting bodied
I touch ya body
while ya touch my body
We touching bodies tonight
We getting bodied
Gettin bodied Gettin bodied
You Want my body
Wont ya get me bodied
Hey