You're everything I thought you never were
And nothing like about you could've been
But still you lived inside of me
So tell me how is that
You're the only one I wish I could forget
The only one I loved and not forgive
And though you've break my heart
You're the only one
And though there are times when I hate you
Cause I can't erase the times that you hurt me
And put tears on my face
And even now I hate you its pains me to say
I know I'll be there at the end of the day
I don't wanna be without you babe
I don't want a broken heart
Don't wanna to take breath without you babe
I don't want to play that part
I know that I love you but let me just say
I don't wanna love you in no kinder way, no no
I don't want a broken heart
I don't want to play the broken-hearted girl
No, no, no broken-hearted girl
I'm no broken-hearted girl
There's something that I feel I need to say
But up 'til now I've always been afraid
That you would never come around
And still I wanna put this out
You say you got the most respect for me
But sometimes I feel your not deserving of me
And still you're in my heart
But you're the only one
And yes there are times when I hate you
But I don't complain
Cause I've been afraid that you would walk away
Oh but now I don't hate you I'm happy to say
That I will be there at the end of the day
I don't wanna be without you babe
I don't want a broken heart
Don't wanna to take breath without you babe
I don't want to play that part
I know that I love you but let me just say
I don't wanna love you in no kinder way, no no
I don't want a broken heart
I don't want to play the broken-hearted girl
No, no, no broken-hearted girl
Now I'm at a place I thought I'd never be
I'm living in a world that's all about you and me
mmm yeah
I ain't got to be afraid, my broken heart is free
To spread my wings and fly away
away with you,
Yeah yeah yeah
I don't wanna be without you babe
I don't want a broken heart
Don't wanna to take breath without you babe
I don't want to play that part
I know that I love you but let me just say
I don't wanna love you in no kinder way, no no
I don't want a broken heart
I don't want to play the broken-hearted girl
No, no, no broken-hearted girl
Broken-hearted girl, no, no
No broken-hearted girl