What goes around comes back around, hey, my baby,
What goes around comes back around, my, my, my baby (hey),
I say, what goes around comes back around, hey, my baby,
What goes around comes back around,
There was
A time
I thought
That you did everything right,
No lies, no wrong,
Boy, I must've been out of my mind,
So when I think of the time that I
Almost loved you,
You showed your ass and I, I saw the real you,
Thank God you blew it,
I thank God I dodged a bullet,
I'm so over you,
So, baby, good lookin' out,
I wanted you bad,
I'm so through with that,
'Cause, honestly, you turned out to be the
Best thing I never had,
You turned out to be the
And I'm gon' always be the
Best thing you never had,
Oh yeah, I bet it sucks to be you right now,
So sad, you're hurt,
Boohoo, oh, did you expect me to care?
You don't deserve my tears,
I guess that's why they ain't there,
When I think that there was a time that I
Almost loved you,
You showed your ass and baby, yes,
I saw the real you,
Thank God you blew it,
I thank God I dodged a bullet,
I'm so over you,
Baby, good lookin' out,
I wanted you bad,
I'm so through with that,
'Cause, honestly, you turned out to be the
Best thing I never had,
I said you turned out to be the
Mmm, and I'll never be the
Best thing you never had,
Oh, baby, I bet it sucks to be you right now,
I know you want me back,
It's time to face the facts,
That I'm the one that's got away,
Lord knows that it would take
Another place, another time,
Another world, another life,
Thank God I found the good in goodbye,
I used to want you so bad,
I'm so through with that,
'Cause, honestly, you turned out to be the
Best thing I never had,
Oh, you turned out to be the
And I will always be the
Best thing you never had,
Ooh, best thing you never had,
I used to want you so bad,
I'm so through with that,
Cause, honestly, you turned out to be the
Best thing I never had,
Oh, you turned out to be the
And I will always be the
Best thing you never had,
Oh, baby, I bet it sucks to be you right now,
Goes around, comes back around (oh),
Goes around, comes back around,
Bet it sucks to be you right now (ooh),
to be you right now,
Goes around, comes back around,
to be you right now, ooh.