Guys, this tour has been the best experience in my entire life
One, two, three, Taylors
There's somethin' about the way
The street looks when it's just rained
There's a glow off the pavement
You walk me to the car
And you know I wanna ask you to dance right there
In the middle of the parking lot
Yeah,
We're drivin' down the road
I wonder if you know
I'm tryin' so hard not to get caught up now
But you're just so cool
Run your hands through your hair
Absent mindedly makin' me want you
And I don't know how it gets better than this
You take my hand and drag me head first
Fearless
And I don't know why when with you I dance
In a storm in my best dress
Fearless
So baby drive slow
'Til we run out of road
In this one horse town
I wanna stay right here
In this passenger's seat You put your eyes on me
In this moment now capture it, remember it
Cuz I don't know how it gets better than this
You take my hand and drag me head first
Fearless
And I don't know why but with you I'd dance
In a storm in my best dress
Fearless
Well you stood there with me in the doorway
My hands shake I'm not usually this way but
You pull me in and I'm a little more brave
It's the first kiss, It's flawless,
Really something,
It's fearless.
Cause I don't know how it gets better than this
You take my hand and drag me head first
Fearless
And I don't know why but with you I would dance
In a storm in my best dress
Fearless
Cause I don't know how it gets better than this
You take my hand and drag me head first
Fearless
And I don't know why but with you I would dance
In a storm in my best dress
Fearless