You were in college working part time waiting tables
Left the small town never looked back
I was the flight risk with the fear of fallin
Wondered why we bothered with love
If it never lasts
I say "Can you believe it?"
As we're lying on a couch
The moment I could see it
Yes, I can see it now
Do you remember we were sitting there by the water
You put your arm around me for the first time
You made a rebel out of a careless man's careful daughter
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
Flash forward and we'd been taking
On the world together
And there is a drawer of my things at your place
You learned my secrets and you figured out
Why I'm guarded
You said we'd never make my parents' mistakes
But we've got bills to pay
We've got nothing figured out
When it was hard to take
Yes,
This is was I thought about Yes,
This is was I thought about
Do you remember we were sitting there by the water
You put your arm around me for the first time
You made a rebel out of a careless man's careful daughter
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
Do you remember all the city lights on the water
You saw me start to believe for the first time
You made a rebel out of a careless man's careful daughter
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
And I remember that fight, 2:30 A.M
Cause everything was slipping right out of my hands
And I ran out crying and you followed me out
Into the street
Raised myself for the goodbye
Cause that's all I've ever known
And you took me by surprised
You said "I'll never leave you"
Oh, no
You said
"I remember how we felt sitting by the water
And every time I look at you is like the first time
I fell in love with a careless man's careful daughter
She is the best thing that's ever been mine"
Hold on, make it last
Hold on, never turn back
You made a rebel out of a careless man's careful daughter
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
Do you believe it?
We're gonna make it now
And I can see it, yeah
And I can see it now,