I'm so glad you made time to see me
How's life? Tell me, how's your family?
I haven't seen them in a while
You've been good; busier than ever
We small talk, work in the weather
Your guard is up and I know why
Cause the last time you saw me
Still burns in the back of your mind
You gave me roses and I left them there to die
So this is me swallowing my pride,
Standing in front of you saying
I'm sorry for that night
And I go back to December all the time,
It turns out freedom ain't nothing but missin' you
Wishing that I realized what I had when you were mine
And I go back to December,
Turn around and make it all right
I go back to December all the time
These days I haven't been sleepin',
Stayin' up playing back myself leavin',
When your birthday passed and I didn't call,
Then I think about summer, all the beautiful times,
I watched you laughin' from the passenger side
And realized I loved you in the fall
And then the cold came, with the dark days
When the fear crept into my mind
You gave me all your love and all I gave you was goodbye
So this is me swallowing my pride,
Standing in front of you saying
I'm sorry for that night
And I go back to December all the time,
It turns out freedom ain't nothing but missin' you
Wishing that I realized what I had when you were mine
And I go back to December,
Turn around and change my own mind
I go back to December all the time
I miss your tan skin, your sweet smile,
So good to me, so right
And how you held me in your arms that September night;
The first time you ever saw me cry
Maybe this is wishful thinking
Probably mindless dreaming
If we loved again, I swear I'd love you right
I'd go back in time and change it but I can't
So if the chain is on your door I understand
But this is me swallowing my pride,
Standing in front of you saying
I'm sorry for that night
And I go back to December
It turns out freedom ain't nothing but missin' you
Wishing that I realized what I had when you were mine
I go back to December,
Turn around and make it all right
I go back to December
Turn around and change my own mind
I go back to December all the time
All the time