And it's a sad picture
The final blow hits you
Somebody else gets what you wanted again
You know it's all the same
Another time and place
Repeating history and you're getting sick of it
But I believe in whatever you do
And I'll do anything to see it through
Because these things will change
Can you feel it now?
These walls that they put up  to hold us back will fall down
It's a revolution,   the time will come for us to finally win
We'll sing hallelujah!
We'll sing hallelujah! Oh
So we've been outnumbered,
Raided and now cornered
It's hard to fight when the fight ain't fair
We're getting stronger now  from things they never found
They might be bigger  but we're faster and never scared
You can walk away  and say we don't need this
But there's something in your eyes  says we can beat this
'Cause these things will change
Can you feel it now?
These walls that they put up   to hold us back will fall down
It's a revolution
The time will come for us to finally win
We'll sing hallelujah!
We'll sing hallelujah! Oh
Tonight we standed on our knees
To fight for what we worked for all these years
And the battle was long
It's the fight of our lives
Will we stand up champions tonight?
It was the night things changed
Can you see it now?
These walls that they put up  to hold us back fell down
It's a revolution, throw your hands up
Cause we never gave in
We'll sing hallelujah!
We sang hallelujah!
Hallelujah!