State the obvious,
I didn’t get my perfect fantasy
I realized you love yourself
More that you could ever love me
So go and tell your friends
That I’m obsessive and crazy,
That’s fine
You won't mind if I say
And by the way
I hate that stupid old pickup truck,
You never let me drive
You’re a redneck, heartbreak
Who’s really bad at lying
So watch me strike a match
On all my wasted time
As far as I’m concerned,
You’re just another picture to burn.
There’s no time for tears
I’m just sitting here planning my revenge
There’s nothing stopping me
From going out \Nwith all of your best friends
And if you come around \Nsaying sorry to me
My daddy’s going \Nto show you how sorry you’ll be
‘Cause I hate that stupid old pickup truck,
You never let me drive
You’re a redneck, heartbreak
Who’s really bad at lying, yeah
So watch me strike a match
On all my wasted time
As far as I’m concerned,
You’re just another picture to burn.
And if you’re missing me
You better keep it to yourself
‘Cause coming back around here
Would be bad for your health
‘Cause I hate \Nthat stupid old pickup truck,
You never let me drive
You’re a redneck, heartbreak
Who’s really bad at lying, yeah
So watch me strike a match
On all my wasted time
In case you haven’t heard,
I really, really hate \Nthat stupid old pickup truck,
You never let me drive
You’re a redneck, heartbreak
Who’s really bad at lying, yeah
So watch me strike a match
On all my wasted time
As far as I’m concerned,
You’re just another picture to burn.
Burn, burn, burn, baby burn.
Just another picture to burn
Baby burn