I used to think one day we'd tell the story of us
How we met and sparks flew instantly
People would say 'They're the lucky ones'
I used to know my place was a spot next to you
Now I'm searching the room for an empty seat
'Cause lately I don't even know what page you're on
A super complication, miscommunication
Has lead to fallout
Too many things that I wish you knew
So when your wall's up I can't break through
Now I'm standing alone in a crowded room
And we're not speaking
And I'm dying to know
Is it killing you like it's killing me?
And I don't know what to say
Since the twist of fate when it all broke down
And the story of us looks a lot like a tragedy now
Next chapter
How'd we end up this way?
Singing nervously, pulling up my clothes
And trying to look busy
And you're doing your best to avoid me
I'm starting to think one day I'll tell the story of us
How I was losing my mind when I saw you here
But you held your pride like you should've held me
I'm scared to see the ending
Why are we pretending this is nothing?
I'd tell you I miss you but I don't know how
I've never heard silence quite this loud
Now I'm standing alone in a crowded room
And we're not speaking
And I'm dying to know
Is it killing you like it's killing me?
And I don't know what to say
Since the twist of fate when it all broke down
And the story of us looks a lot like a tragedy now
This is looking like a contest
Of who can act like they care less
But I liked it better when you were on my side
The battle's in your hands now
But I will lay my armor down
If you say you'd rather love than fight
So many things that you wish I knew
But the story of us might be ending soon
Now I'm standing alone in a crowded room
And we're not speaking
And I'm dying to know
Is it killing you like it's killing me?
But I don't know what to say
Since the twist of fate and it all broke down
And the story of us looks a lot like a tragedy now
Now,
And we're not speaking
And I'm dying to know
Is it killing you like it's killing me?
I don't know what to say
Since the twist of fate 'cause we're going down
And the story of us looks a lot like a tragedy now
The End