Drew looks at me.
I fake a smile so he won't see.
I want and I needing
Everything that we should be
I bet she's beautiful.
That girl he talks about,
and she's got everything
that I have to live without
Drew talks to me
I laugh cause it's so damn funny
But I can't even see
Anyone when he's with me
He says he's so in love,
he's finally got it right.
I wonder if he knows
he's all I think about at night.
He's the reason for the teardrops on my guitar.
The only thing that keeps me wishing on a wishing star.
He's the song in the car
I keep singing,
don't know why I do.
Drew walks by me.
Can he tell that I can't breathe?
And there he goes, so perfectly.
The kind of flawless I wish I could be.
She better hold him tight
Give him all her love,
look in those beautiful eyes
and know she's lucky cause..
He's the reason for the teardrops on my guitar
The only thing that keeps me wishing on a wishing star
He's the song in the car
I keep singing,
Don't know why I do.
So I drive home alone,
as I turn out the light,
I'll put his picture down
and maybe get some sleep tonight.
Cause he's the reason for the teardrops on my guitar.
The only one that's got enough of me to break my heart.
He's the song in the car
I keep singing,
don't know why I do.
He's the time taken up,
but there's never enough.
And he's all that I need to fall into.
Drew looks at me
I fake a smile so he won't see.