I was riding shotgun with my hair undone
in the front seat of his car,
He's got a one-hand feel on the steering wheel,
The other on my heart,
I look around, turn the radio down,
He says "Baby is something wrong?"
I say "Nothing, I was just thinking
How we don't have a song",
And he says...
Our song is the slamming screen door,
Sneakin' out late, tapping on your window,
When we're on the phone and you talk real slow,
Cause it's late and your mama don't know,
Our song is the way you laugh,
The first date, man,
I didn't kiss her and I should have,
And when I got home before I said amen,
Asking God if he could play it again.
I was walking up the front porch steps
After everything that day,
Had gone all wrong or been trampled on,
And lost and thrown away,
Got to the hallway, well on my way to my lovin' bed,
I almost didn't notice all the roses,
And the note that said...
Our song is the slamming screen door,
Sneakin' out late, tapping on your window,
When we're on the phone and you talk real slow,
Cause it's late and your mama don't know,
Our song is the way you laugh,
The first date, man,
I didn't kiss her and I should have,
And when I got home before I said amen,
Asking God if he could play it again.
I've heard every album, listened to the radio,
Waited for something to come along,
That was as good as our song...
Our song is the slamming screen door,
Sneakin' out late, tapping on your window,
When we're on the phone and you talk real slow,
Cause it's late and your mama don't know,
Our song is the way you laugh,
The first date, man,
I didn't kiss her and I should have,
And when I got home before I said amen,
Asking God if he could play it again.
Play it again
I was riding shotgun with my hair undone,
In the front seat of his car,
I grabbed a pen and an old napkin,
And I... wrote down our song.