Say you're sorry,that face of an ange comes out
Just when youneed it to
As I paced backand forth all this time
Cause I honestlybelieved in you
Holding on the days drag onStupid girl,
I should've knownI should've known
I'm not a princess,this ain't a fairytale
I'm not the oneyou'll sweep off her feet
Lead her up the stairwell
This ain't hollywood,this is a small town
I was a dreamer before you wentand let me down
Now it's too late for youand your white horse
To come around
Maybe I was naive,got lost in your eyes
And never reallyhad a chance
My mistake,I didn't know to be in love
You had to fightto have the upper hand
I had so many dreamsabout you and me
Happy endings,well now I know
I'm not a princess,this ain't a fairytale
I'm not the oneyou'll sweep off her feet
Lead her up the stairwell
This ain't hollywood,this is a small town
I was a dreamer before you wentand let me down
Now it's too late for youand your white horse
To come around
And there you areon your knees
Begging for forgiveness,begging for me
Just like I always wanted,but I'm so sorry
Cause I'm not your princess,this ain't a fairytale
I'm gonna find someonesomeday
Who might actuallytreat me well
This is a big world,that was a small town
There in my rearview mirrordisappearing now
And it's too late for youand your white horse
Now it's too late for youand your white horse
To catch me now
Try and catch me now
It's too late
To catch me now