You take a deep breath
And you walk through the doors
It's the morning of your very first day
And you say hi to your friends
You ain't seen in a while
Try and stay out of everybody's way
It's your freshman year
And you're gonna be here
For the next four years in this town
Hoping one of those senior boys
Will wink at you and say
"You know, I haven't seen you around before"
'Cause when you're fifteen
And somebody tells you they love you
You're gonna believe them
And when you're fifteen feeling like
There's nothing to figure out
But, count to ten, take it in
This is life before you know
Who you're gonna be
Fifteen
You sit in class next to a redhead named Abigail
And soon enough you're best friends
Laughing at the other girls
Who think they're so cool
We'll be outta here as soon as we can
And then you're on your very first date
And he's got a car
And you're feeling like flying
And you're momma's waiting up
And you're thinking he's the one
And you're dancing 'round your room
When the night ends,
When the night ends
'Cause when you're fifteen
And somebody tells you they love you
You're gonna believe them
When you're fifteen and your first kiss
Makes your head spin 'round
But in your life you'll do things greater than
Dating the boy on the football team
But I didn't know it at fifteen
When all you wanted was to be wanted
Wish you could go back
And tell yourself what you know now
Back then I swore I was gonna marry him someday
But I realized some bigger dreams of mine
And Abigail gave everything she had to a boy
Who changed his mind and we both cried
'Cause when you're fifteen
And somebody tells you they love you
You're gonna believe them
And when you're fifteen,
Don't forget to look before you fall
I've found time can heal most anything
And you just might find who you're supposed to be
I didn't know who I supposed to be
At fifteen
Your very first day
Take a deep breath girl
Take a deep breath as you walk through the doors