Confidence is a must
Happiness is a plus
Edginess is a rush
Edges (I like 'em rough)
A man with a Midas touch
Intoxicate on the rush
Stop you're making me blush
People are looking at us
I don't think you know (know)
I'm checking it so hot (so hot )
I Wonder if he knows he's
on my radar (on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
And if I notice you I know it's you
Choose you don't wanna lose you're
on my radar (on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
When you walk (when you walk) when you talk (when you talk)
I get the tingle, I wanna mingle
that's what I want (that's what I want)
And listen baby don't try to debate it..
try to make you understand you're
on my radar (on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
On my radar (got you on my) radar (got you on my)
radar (got you on my) RADAR
Interesting sense of style
Ten million dollar smile
Think I cant handle that
Animal in the sack
His eyes see right to my soul
I surrender self-control
Catch me looking again
Falling right into my bed..
I don't think you know (know)
I'm checking it so hot (so hot )
Wonder if he knows he's on my radar
(on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
And if I notice you I know it's you
Choose you don't wanna lose you're
on my radar (on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
When you walk (when you walk)
and when you talk (when you talk)
I get the tingle, I wanna mingle
that's what I want (that's what I want)
And listen baby don't debate it..
try to make you understand you're
on my radar (on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
on my radar (got you on my) radar (got you on my)
radar (got you on my) RADAR
I got my eye on you... and I cant let you get away
Hey baby whether it's now or later (I've got you)
you cant shake me (no)
cuz I got you on my radar
Whether you like it or not, it ain't gonna stop
cuz I got you on my radar (I've got you)
cuz I got you on my radar
I'm checking it so hot (so hot)
Wonder if he knows he's on my radar (on my radar)
on my radar (on my radar)
And if I notice you I know it's you
Choose you don't wanna lose you're
on my radar (on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
When you walk (when you walk)
and when you talk (when you talk)
I get the tingle, I wanna mingle
that's what I want (that's what I want)
And listen baby don't debate it...
try to make you understand you're
on my radar (on my radar) on my radar (on my radar)
on my radar (got you on my) radar (got you on my)
radar (got you on my) RADAR