I need time, love, joy
I need space, love
I need me
Say hello to the girl that I am
You're gonna have to see through my perspective
I need to make mistakes just to learn who I am
And I don't wanna be so damn protected
There must be another way
'Cause I believe in taking chances, but who am I to say
What a girl is to do, God I need some answers
What am I to do with my life?
(You will find it out don't worry)
How am I supposed to know what's right?
(You just gotta do it your way)
I can't help the way I feel
But my life has been so overprotected
I tell them what I like, what I want and what I don't
But everytime I do, I stand corrected
Things that I've been told, I can't believe what I hear about the world
I realize I'm overprotected
There must be another way
'Cause I believe in taking chances, but who am I to say
What a girl is to do, God I need some answers
What am I to do with my life?
(You will find it out don't worry)
How am I supposed to know what's right?
(You just gotta do it your way)
I can't help the way I feel
But my life has been so overprotected
I need time, love, I need space
(This is it, this is it)
I don't need nobody telling me just what I wanna
What I what what what I'm gonna do about my destiny
(I say no no) nobody's telling me just what I wanna (do do)
I'm so fed up with people telling me to be someone else but me
What am I to do with my life?
(You will find it out don't worry)
How am I supposed to know what's right?
(You just gotta do it your way)
I can't help the way I feel
But my life has been so overprotected
I don't need nobody telling me just what I wanna
What I what what what I'm gonna do about my destiny
(I say no no) nobody's telling me just what I wanna (do do)
I'm so fed up with people telling me to be someone else but me
What am I to do with my life?
(You will find it out don't worry)
How am I supposed to know what's right?
(You just gotta do it your way)
I can't help the way I feel
But my life has been so overprotected