People can take everything away from you
But they can never take away your truth
But the question is...
Can you handle mine?
They say I'm crazy
I really don't care
That's my Prerogative
They say I'm nasty
But I don't give a damn
Getting boys is how I live
Some ask me questions
Why am I so real?
But they don't understand me
I really don't know the deal
About my sister
Trying hard to make it right
Not long ago before I won this fight
Everybody's talking all this stuff about me
Why don't they just let me live (Tell me why)
I don't need permission
Make my own decisions (oh)
That's my prerogative (It's my prerogative)
It's my prerogative
It's the way that I wanna live
You can't tell me what to do
Don't get me wrong
I'm really not souped
Ego trips is not my thing
All these strange relationships
Really gets me down
I see nothing wrong with
Spreading myself around
Everybody's talking all this stuff about me
Why don't they just let me live (Tell me why)
I don't need permission
Make my own decisions (oh)
That's my prerogative (It's my prerogative)
Everybody's talking all this stuff about me
Why don't they just let me live (Tell me why)
I don't need permission
Make my own decisions (oh)
That's my prerogative (It's my prerogative)
It's the way that I wanna live
It's my prerogative
You can't tell me what to do
Why can't I live my life
Without all of the things that people say oooooh
Everybody's talking all this stuff about me
Why don't they just let me live (Tell me why)
I don't need permission
Make my own decisions (oh)
That's my prerogative (It's my prerogative)
(they say I'm crazy)
Everybody's talking all this stuff about me
Why don't they just let me live (Tell me why)
(they say I'm nasty)
I don't need permission
Make my own decisions (oh)
That's my prerogative
It's my prerogative