Baby, I'm so into you
You've got that something, what can I do?
Baby, you spin me around, ...ow
The earth is movin, but I can't feel the ground
Everytime you look at me
My heart is jumpin', it's easy to see
You drive me crazy
I just can't sleep
I'm so excited, I'm in too deep
But it feels alright
Baby thinking of you keeps me up all night
Tell me, you're so into me
That I'm the only one you will see
Tell me I'm not in the blue, ...ow
That I'm not wastin' my feelins on you
Everytime I look at you
My heart is jumping, what can I do?
You drive me crazy
I just can't sleep
I'm so excited, I'm in too deep
Ohh, Ohh, Ohh... Crazy
But it feels alright
Baby thinking of you keeps me up all night
You drive me crazy,
Sing it
STOP!
You drive me crazy, baby
Excited, I'm in too deep
Oh but it feels alright
Baby thinking of you keeps me up all night
You drive me crazy (crazy)
I just can't sleep
I'm so excited, I'm in too deep
But it feels alright
Baby thinking of you keeps me up all night
Sing it
Crazy
You drive me crazy
But it feels alright
Baby thinking of you keeps me up all night