Ladies and gentlemen
we interrupt our program of dance music
to bring you a special bulletin
from the intercontinental radio news
Our very own pop princess
now queen of pop
has a special announcement
she would like to make
You ready?
I think I'm ready for my close up
Yeah
You don't like me, I don't like you, It don't matter
Only difference, you still listen, I don't have to
In one ear and out the other, I dont need ya
Your words don't stick, I ain't perfect but you ain't either
If you're feelin' grubbily, I ain't even losin' sleep
Theres more to me than what you see
You wouldn't like me when I'm angry
Mr. Photographer, I think I'm ready for my close-up (tonight!)
Make sure you catch me from my good side (pick one!)
These other ha! just wanna be me
Is the money in your pocket?
or you're happy to see me?
Kill the Lights!
Take em out, turn em off, break em down
Don't be scared, you can move see me now
Kill the Lights!
I've felt you, watching me watching you
You can't handle the truth, what happened to you?
I killed the lights (Pure satisfaction)
I killed the lights (Lights, camera, action)