Oh baby baby,
have you seen Amy tonight?
Is she in the bathroom?
Is she smoking up outside?
Oh baby baby,
does she take a piece of lime?
For the drink that I'ma buy her?
Do you know just what she likes?
Oh oh, tell me
have you seen her
'Cause I'm so, oh,
I can't get her off of my brain
I just wanna go
to the party she gon' go
Can't somebody
take me home?
Love me, hate me,
say what you want about me
But all of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy
Love me, hate me,
but can't you see what I see?
All of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy
Love me,
Hate me
Amy told me that
she's gonna meet me up
I don't know where or when
and now their closing up the club
I've seen her once or twice
before she knows my face
But its hard to see with
all the people standing in the way
Oh oh, tell me
have you seen her
'Cause I'm so, oh,
I can't get her off of my brain
I just wanna go
to the party she gon' go
Can't somebody
take me home?
Love me, hate me,
say what you want about me
But all of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy
Love me, hate me,
but can't you see what I see?
All of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy
Oh say
what you want about me
Oh but can't you see
what I see?
Yeah, say what you want about me,
about me, about me...
So tell me
if you see her
If you knew what
she was wearing and what she was like
'Cause I've been
waiting here forever
If you knew if
she was going out of line
Oh baby baby
if you seek Amy tonight
we'll do whatever you like
Oh baby, baby, baby.
Oh baby, baby, baby
Love me, hate me,
say what you want about me
But all of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy
Love me, hate me,
but can't you see what I see?
All of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy
Love me, hate me,
say what you want about me
but can't you see what I see?
All of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy
Oh say what you
want about me
Oh but can't you see
what I see?
Yeah,
say what you want about me
All of the boys and all of the girls
are begging to if you seek Amy