Nothing seems to be the way
That it used to
Everything seems shallow
God give me truth
In me
And tell me somebody's watching
Over me
And that is all I'm praying is that
Someday I will understand
In God's whole plan
And what He's done to me
Oh but maybe someday I will breathe
And I'll finally see
I'll see it all in my baby
Don't you run too fast my dear
Why don't you stop?
Just stop and listen to your tears
They're all you've got
It's in you
You see somebody's watching
Over you
And that is all I'm praying is that
Someday you will understand
In God's whole plan
And what He does to you
Oh but maybe someday you will breathe
And you'll finally see
You'll see it all in your baby
No moment will be more true
Than the moment I look at you
It's in you
You see somebody's watching
Over you
And that is all i'm praying is that
Someday you will understand
In God's whole plan
And what He does to you
Oh but maybe someday you will breathe
And you'll finally see
You'll see it all in your baby