Britney Spears
Lucky
This is A story about A girl named lucky...
Early morning, she wakes up
Knock knock knock on the door
It's time for makeup, perfect smile
It's you they're all waiting for, they go
Isn't she lovely
This, Hollywood girl?
And they say she's so lucky
She's A star but she cry cry cry
Cries in her lonely heart, thinking
If there's nothing missing in my life
Then why do these tears come at night
Lost in an image, in A dream
But there's no one there to wake her up
And the world is spinning
And she keep or winning
But tell me what happens when it stops?
They go
Isn't she lovely
This, Hollywood girl?
And they say she's so lucky
She's A star but she cry cry cry
Cries in her lonely heart, thinking
If there's nothing missing in my life
Then why do these tears come at night
Best actress, and the winner is...
lucky!
I'm Roger Johnson for Pop News
Standing outside the arena waiting for lucky oh my god... here she comes!
Isn't she lovely this
Hollywood girl?
She is so lucky
But why does she cry?
If there's nothing, missing in her life
why do tears come at night?
she's so lucky, she's A star, but she cry cry cry
Cries in her lonely heart, thinking
If there's nothing, missing in my life
Then why do these...
Tears come at night
She's so lucky
But she cry cry cry
Cries in her lonely heart, thinking
If there's nothing, missing in my life
Then why do these...
Tears come at night