I know I may be young
But, I've got feelin's too
And I need to do
What I feel like doin'
So Let Me go
All you people look at me like I'm a little girl
Well did you ever think it be ok for me to step into this world
Always sayin little girl don't step into the club
Well I'm just trying to find out why cuz dancin's what I love (yea)
Get it Get it (6x)
(Do you like it)
I know I may come off quiet, May come off shy
But I feel like talkin, feel like dancin when I see this guy
What's practical is logical what the hell who cares
All I know is that I'm so happy when you're dancin there
I'm a slaaaaaaaaaaave for you
I cannot hold it I cannot control it
I won't deny it, I'm not tryin to hide it
Baby, Dont You wanna dance upon me, to another time and place
Baby, Don't You wanna dance upon me
Leaving behind my name, my age.
(Let's go)
(Like that)
(You like it)
(Now watch me)
Get it Get it (6x)
(Do you like it)
I really wanna dance tonight with you
I really wanna do what you want me to
I really wanna do what you wanna do ( Uh )
Baby, Dont You wanna dance upon me, to another time and place
Baby, Don't You wanna dance upon me
Leaving behind my name, my age.
I'm a slaaaaaaaaaaave for you
I cannot hold it I cannot control it
I won't deny it, I'm not tryin to hide it
Get it Get it (6x)
I'm a slaaaaaaaaaaave for you
I cannot hold it I cannot control it
I won't deny it, I'm not tryin to hide it
Take that