"Never look back,"
we said
How was I to know
I'd miss you so?
Loneliness up ahead,
emptiness behind
Where do I go?
And you didn't hear
All my joy through my tears
All my hopes through my fears
Did you know
Still I miss you somehow
From the bottom of my broken heart
There's just a thing
or two I'd like you to know
You were my first love,
you were my true love
From the first kisses to
the very last rose
From the bottom of my broken heart
Even though time may
find me somebody new
You were my real love,
I never knew love
'Til there was you
From the bottom of my broken heart
"Baby," I said,
"please stay.
Give our love a chance
for one more day"
We could have worked things out
Taking time is
what love is all about
But you put a dart
Through my dreams
through my heart
And I'm back where I
started again
Never thought it would end
From the bottom of my broken heart
There's just a thing
or two I'd like you to know
You were my first love,
I never knew love
'Til there was you
From the bottom of my broken heart
You promised yourself
But to somebody else
And you made it so
perfectly clear
Still I wish you were here
From the bottom of my broken heart
There's just a thing
or two I'd like you to know
You were my first love,
you were my true love
From the first kisses to
the very last rose
From the bottom of my broken heart
Even though time may
find me somebody new
You were my real love,
I never knew love
'Til there was you
From the bottom of my broken heart
"Never look back,"
we said
How was I to know
I'd miss you so?