Superstar
Where you from, how's it going?
I know you
Gotta clue, what youre doing?
You can play brand new to all
The other chicks out here
But I know what you are
what you are, baby
Look at you
Gettin' more than just re-up
Baby, you
Got all the puppets with their strings up
Fakin' like a good one
But I call 'em like I see 'em
I know what you are
What you are, baby
Womanizer, woman-womanizer
You're a womanizer
Oh womanizer
Oh You're a womanizer baby
You, you you are
Womanizer, womanizer, womanizer
Boy don't try to front
I (I) know just (just) what you are (are are)
You got me goin'
You're Oh-So charmin'
But I can't do it
U womanizer
Boy don't try to front
I (I) know just (just) what you are (are are)
You say I'm crazy
I got you crazy
You're nothing but a womanizer
Daddy-O
You got the swagger of champion
Too bad for you
Just can't find the right companion
I guess when you have one too many, makes it hard
It could be easy
Who you are, that's who you are, baby
Lollipop
Must mistake me you're a sucker
To think that I would be a victom not another
Say it, play it how you wanna
But no way I'm ever gonna fall for you
Never you, baby
Womanizer, woman-womanizer
You're a womanizer
Oh womanizer
Oh You're a womanizer baby
You, you you are
Womanizer, womanizer, womanizer
Boy don't try to front
I (I) know just (just) what you are (are are)
You got me goin'
You're Oh-So charmin'
But I can't do it
U womanizer
Boy don't try to front
I (I) know just (just) what you are (are are)
You say I'm crazy
I got you crazy
You're nothing but a womanizer
Maybe if we both lived in a different world
Womanizer, womanizer...
It would be all good
And maybe I could be ya girl
But I can't 'cause we don't
Womanizer, woman-womanizer
You're a womanizer
Oh womanizer
Oh You're a womanizer baby
You, you you are
Womanizer, womanizer, womanizer
Boy don't try to front
I (I) know just (just) what you are (are are)
You got me goin'
You're Oh-So charmin'
But I can't do it
U womanizer
Boy don't try to front
I (I) know just (just) what you are (are are)
You say I'm crazy
I got you crazy
You're nothing but a womanizer
Boy don't try to front
I (I) know just (just) what you are (are are)
Womanizer, woman-womanizer
You're a womanizer
Oh womanizer
Oh You're a womanizer baby