Ooh hey, yeah
Hush, just stop
There's nothing you can do or say, baby
I've had enough
I'm not your property as from today, baby
You might think that I won't make it on my own
But now I'm Stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but my way
My loneliness ain't killing me no more
I'm.. stronger
That I ever thought that I could be, baby
I used to go with the flow Didn't really care 'bout me
You might think that I can't take it, but you're wrong
Cause now I'm Stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but my way
My loneliness ain't killing me no more
I'm.. stronger
Come on, now
Oh, yeah
Here I go, on my own
I don't need nobody, better off alone
Here I go, on my own now
I don't need nobody, not anybody
Here I go, alright, here I go
Stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but my way
My lonliness ain't killing me no more
I'm..
Stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but my way
My lonliness ain't killing me no more
Now I'm stronger than yesterday
Now it's nothing but my way
My loneliness ain't killing me no more
I'm..  stronger