Britney Spears
pouria Alikhani
Sometimes
You tell me you're in love with me
That you can't take your pretty eyes away from me
It's not that I don't want to stay
But everytime you come too close I move away
I wanna believe in everything that you say
cause it sounds so good
But if you really want me, move slow
There's things about me you just have to know.
Sometimes I run
sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight
Treat you right,
be with you day and night
Baby all I need is time.
I don't wanna be so shy, ah-ah
Everytime that I'm alone I wonder why
Hope that you will wait for me
You'll see that, you're the only one for me
I wanna believe in everything that you say
Cause it sounds so good
But if you really want me, move slow
There's things about me, you just have to know.
Sometimes I run (sometimes) sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight
Treat you right, be with you day and night
All I really want is to hold you tight
Baby, all I need is time.
Just hang around and you'll see
There's nowhere I'd rather be
If you love me, trust in me
The way that I trust in you.
Sometimes I run (sometimes) sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight (hold you tight)
Treat you right, be with you day and night (day and night)
Sometimes I run (sometimes)
sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you uh uh ah ah
But all I really want is to hold you tight treat you right,
Be with you day and night (day and night)
All I really want is to hold you tight
Be with you day and night
Sometimes I run (sometimes)
Sometimes I hide
Sometimes I'm scared of you
But all I really want is to hold you tight,treat you right,
Be with you day and night