Is it true you've banned junk food Smiles, candy, sunshine and laughter
From you Femme Fatale tour?
Yes, Yes, it is
Britney, can you confirm reports that You're pregnant with Brad Pitt's lovechild?
That is false It's quintuplets
Britney, britney! Does this suit make me look fat?
Yes, it does
Is this true that you hate puppies?
Fuck you!
You're cool
I'm out
Lately I've been stuck imaginin'
What I wanna do and what I really think
Time to blow out
Be a little inappropriate
'Cause I know that everybody's thinkin' it
When the light's out
Shame on me
To need release
Uncontrollably
I-I-I wanna go-o-o all the way-ay-ay Taking out my freak tonight
I-I-I wanna show-o-o all the dir-ir-irt I got running through my mind
Wo-oh-oh
I-I-I wanna go-o-o all the way-ay-ay Taking out my freak tonight
I-I-I wanna show-o-o all the dir-ir-irt I got running through my mind
Wo-oh-oh
Lately people got me all tied up
There's a countdown waiting for me to e-rupt
Time to blow out
I've been told who I should do it with
To keep both my hands above the bl-an-ket
When the light's out
Shame on me
To need release
Uncontrollably
I-I-I wanna go-o-o all the way-ay-ay Taking out my freak tonight
I-I-I wanna show-o-o all the dir-ir-irt I got running through my mind
Wo-oh-oh
I-I-I wanna go-o-o all the way-ay-ay Taking out my freak tonight
I-I-I wanna show-o-o all the dir-ir-irt I got running through my mind
Wo-oh-oh
Shame on me
To need release
Uncontrollably
Britney, come on Get in quick
I-I-I wanna go-o-o all the way-ay-ay Taking out my freak tonight
I-I-I wanna show-o-o all the dir-ir-irt I got running through my mind
Wo-oh-oh
Britney!
Why is my wife cheating on me?
No more questions!
Guillermo, I had the strangest dream
I love dreams and seashells
C'mon, let's get out of here