Hey!? Is this thing on?
I saw him dancing there by the record machine
I knew he must have been about seventeen
The beat was going strong
Playing my favourite song
And I could tell it wouldn't be long
until he was with me
YEAH Me
And I could tell it wouldn't be long
until he was with me
YEAH With me Singin'
I love Rock 'N Roll
So put another dime in the jukebox, Baby
I love Rock N' Roll
So come and take your time and dance with me
Ouw !
He smiled, so I got up and asked for his name"
That don't matter," he said, "'cause it's all the same."
I said, "Can I take you home where we can be alone?"
And next we were moving on
and he was with me, yeah, me
And we were moving on
singin the same old song
Yeah with me
Singing:
I love Rock N' Roll
So put another dime in the jukebox, Baby
So come and take your time and dance with me
I love Rock N' Roll
'cause it suits my soul
I love Rock N' Roll Yeah....
I said, "Can I take you home where we can be alone?"
And next thing we were moving on
and he was with me, yeah, me,
And we were moving on
and singin that same old song
Yeah with me
Singing:
I love Rock N' Roll
So put another dime in the jukebox Baby
So come and take your time and dance with me
I love Rock N' Rol l(I love Rock N' Rolll)
So put another dime in the jukebox Baby
I love Rock N' Roll
So come and take your time and dance with me
(dance with me)
I love Rock N' Roll (I Rock N' Roll)
So put another dime in the jukebox Baby(so dance with me)
I love Rock N' Roll
So come and take your time and dance with me(dance with me)
I love Rock N' Roll(oh....)
So put another dime in the jukebox Baby(oh....)
I love Rock N' Roll So come and take your time and dance with me(dance with me)
I love Rock N' Roll
So put another dime in the jukebox Baby
So come and take your time and dance with me!