This kicked in got your
tongue tied in knots, I see
Spit it out
'cause I'm dying for company
I notice that
you got it
You notice
that I want it
You know that I can take it
to the next level baby
If you want this good shit
sicker than the remix
Baby, let me blow
your mind tonight
I can't take it
no more
Never felt like
this before
Come on get me,
get me on the floor
DJ what you,
what you waiting for?
Watch me move
when I lose,
When I lose it hard
Get you off with the
touching dance in the dark
You notice
what I'm wearing
when you're stepping
You know that I can take it
to the next level baby
Hotter than
the A-list
Next one on
my hit list
Baby let me blow
your mind tonight
I can't take it
no more
Never felt like
this before
Come on get me,
get me on the floor
DJ what you,
what you waiting for?
See the sunlight,
we ain't stopping
Keep on dancing
til the world ends
If you feel it,
let it happen
Keep on dancing
til the world ends
See the sunlight,
we ain't stopping
Keep on dancing
til the world ends
If you feel it,
let it happen
Keep on dancing
til the world ends