It's Britney bitch
I see you
And I just wanna dance with you
Every time they turn the lights down
Just wanna go that extra mile for you
Public display of affection
Feels like no one else in the room
(But You)
We can get down like there's no one around
We keep on Rockin (We keep on Rockin)
Cameras are flashin'
While we're dirty dancin
They keep watchin' (They keep watchin)
Keep watchin'
Feels like the crowd is sayin'
Gimme gimme (more)
Gimme (more)
Center of attention (Do you feel this?)
Even when we're up against the wall
You got me in a crazy position
If you're on a mission
You got my permission, oh!
We can get down like there's no one around
We keep on Rockin (We keep on Rockin)
Cameras are flashin'
While we're dirty dancin
They keep watchin' (They keep watchin)
Keep watchin
Feels like the crowd is sayin'
Gimme gimme (more)
Gimme (more)
I just can't
Control myself
They want more,
Well, I'll give them more
Gimme gimme (more)
Gimme (more)
Gimme more, gimme more
(more, more, more)
Gimme more, gimme more babe
I just want more
Gimme gimme
Gimme
I bet you didn't see this one coming
The incredible lygo
(more, more, more)
The legendary Ms. Britney Spears
And the unstoppable Danja
You're gonna have to remove me
Cause I ain't goin' nowhere