For whatever reason,
I feel like I've been wanting you all my life
You don't understand
I'm so glad we're at the same place at the same time
I spotted you dancin'
It's over now
You made all the girls stare
Those lips and your brown eyes (Oooh)
And the sexy hair
I should shake my thang (Ooh)
Make the world want you (Ha Ha Ha)
Tell your boys you'll be back
I wanna see what you can do (Uh)
What would it take for you to just leave with me?
Not trying to sound conceited but
You and me were meant to be (Yeah Yeah)
You're a sexy guy, I'm a nice girl (Uh)
Let's turn this dance floor into our own little nasty world
Boys!
Sometimes a girl just needs one (You know I need you)
To love her and to hold (I just want you to touch me)
Boys!
And when a girl is with one (Mmm)
Then she's in control!
Pull the girl off the dance floor
Whisper in ear
Must've said somethin' bout me (What you say)
Cos now she's lookin' over here
You lookin' at me (He He He)
With that sexy attitude
But the way your girls movin' it (Uh)
It puts me in the mood
(Ow!)
What would it take for you to just leave with me?
Not trying to sound conceited
But meeting you was destiny
I'm from N.E.R.D, Aren't you Britney? (Don't you know?)
Let's turn this dance floor into our own little nasty thing (Get Nasty!)
Girls!
I can't speak for no one (I get nasty)
But I need her all the time (It's just me and you baby)
Girls!
I don't know 'bout your girl
But I know she's on your mind (Get Nasty)
You like that
Here we go
Have no Fear
Baby what you waiting for?
Uh-huh
Let me see what you can do
Boys!
Sometimes a girl just needs one (Ooh)
(I like that)
To love her and to hold (The way you move)
Boys!
And when a girl is with one (It's gonna turn me on)
Then she's in control (Ooh)
Girls!
I can't speak for no one (I get nasty)
But I need her all the time (It's just me and you baby)
Girls!
I don't know 'bout your girl
But I know she's on your mind (Get Nasty)
Boys
Girls (Ow)
Girls
Boys (Can't live with them)
Boys (Can't live without them)
Girls (Get Nasty!)