It's been a while
I know I shouldn't have kept you waiting
But I'm here now
I know it's been a while
But I'm glad you came
And I've been thinking 'bout
How you say my name
Got my body spinning
Like a hurricane
And it feels like
You got me going insane
And I can't get enough
So let me get it up
Ooh, looks like we're alone now
You ain't gotta be scared
Where you going now?
I'm a have to floss on you
Let's get it blazin'
We can turn the heat up if you wanna
Turn the lights down low if you wanna
Just wanna move you
But you're frozen
That's what I'm saying
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
So you warming up yet?
You got me hypnotised
I never felt this way
Got my heart beating
Like an 808
Can you rise to the occasion?
I'm patiently waiting
Cause it's getting late
And I can't get enough
So let me get it up
Ooh, looks like we're alone now
You ain't gotta be scared
Where you going now?
I'm a have to floss on you
Let's get it blazin'
We can turn the heat up if you wanna
Turn the lights down low if you wanna
Just wanna move you
But you're frozen
That's what I'm saying
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
I like this part
Feels kinda good
Yeah
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
Hot (more)
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
Let me break the ice
Allow me to get you right
But you warm up to me
Baby I can make you feel
Hot hot hot...