Hey over there
Please forgive me
If i'm coming on too strong
Hate to stare
But you're winning
And they're playing my favorite song
So come in little closer
Wanna whisper in your ear
Make it clear, little question
Wanna note just how you feel
If I feel my heart was beating loud
If we could escape the crowd some how
If I said I want your body now
Would you hold it against me
Cause you feel like paradise
And I need a vacation tonight
So if I said I want your body now
Would you hold it against me
Hey you might think
That i'm crazy
But you know I'm just your type
I might be little hazy
But you just cannot deny
There's a spark in between us
When we're dancin' on the floor
I want more, wanna see it,
So I'm askin' you tonight
If I feel my heart was beating loud
If we could escape the crowd some how
If I said I want your body now
Would you hold it against me
Cause you feel like paradise
And I need a vacation tonight
So if I said I want your body now
Would you hold it against me
If I said I want your body
Gimmie something good
Don't wanna wait I want it now
Drop it like a hood
And show me how you work it out
Alright !
If I feel my heart was beating loud
If I said I want your body now
Would you hold it against me
If I feel my heart was beating loud
If we could escape the crowd some how
If I said I want your body now
Would you hold it against me
Cause you feel like paradise
And I need a vacation tonight
So if I said I want your body now
Would you hold it against me