There's only two types of people
In the world
The ones that entertain
And the ones that observe
Well baby, I'm a put-on-a-show
Kinda girl
Don't like the backseat
Gotta be first (Oh, oh)
I'm like the ringleader
I call the shots (Call the shots)
I'm like a firecracker
I make it hot
When I put on a show
I feel the adrenaline
Movin' through my veins
Spotlight on me
And I'm ready to break
I'm like a performer that
The dancefloor is my stage
Better be ready
Hope that you feel the same
All eyes on me in the center of the ring
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)
When I crack that whip, everybody gonna trip
Don't stand there watchin' me, follow me
Show me what you can do
Everybody let go, we can make a dance floor
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)
There's only two types of guys
Out there
Ones that can hang with me
And ones that are scared
So baby, I hope that you
Came prepared
I run a tight ship
So beware
I'm like the ringleader
I call the shots (Call the shots)
I'm like a firecracker
I make it hot
When I put on a show
I feel the adrenaline
Movin' through my veins
Spotlight on me
And I'm ready to break
I'm like a performer which
The dancefloor is my stage
Better be ready
Hope that you feel the same
All eyes on me in the center of the ring
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)
When I crack that whip, everybody gonna trip
Don't stand there watchin' me, follow me
Show me what you can do
Everybody let go, we can make a dance floor
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)
Let's go
Let me see what you can do
I'm running this
Like-like-like-like a circus
Like a what?
All eyes on me in the center of the ring
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)
When I crack that whip, everybody gonna trip
Don't stand there watchin' me, follow me
Show me what you can do
Everybody let go, we can make a dance floor
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)
All eyes on me in the center of the ring
When I crack that whip, everybody gonna trip
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)
Don't stand there watchin' me, follow me
Show me what you can do
Everybody let go, we can make a dance floor
Just like a circus (Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh-huh)