Notice me
Take my hand
Why are we
Strangers when
Our love is strong
Why carry on without me?
Everytime I try to fly
I fall Without my wings
I feel so small
I guess I need you Baby
And everytime I see you in my dreams
I see your face
It's haunting me
I guess I need you Baby
I make believe
That you are here
It's the only way
I see clear
What have I done?
You seemed to move on easy
And everytime I try to fly
I fall without my wings
I feel so small
I guess I need you Baby
And everytime I see you in my dreams
I see your face
You're haunting me
I guess I need you Baby
I may have made it rain
Please forgive me
My weakness caused you pain
And this song is my sorry
At night I pray
That soon your face will fade away
And everytime I try to fly
I fall without my wings
I feel so small
I guess I need you Baby
And everytime I see you in my dreams
I see your face
You're haunting me
I guess I need you baby