Can you try smiling just once?
It's embarrassing.
You look like you're at a funeral
Why don't we see that pretty little face of yours?
Oy, when I'm talking to you,
Look me in the face and don't disrespect me.
Sorry about that guys
So you're not working the street corner tonight I see,
I'm so sorry, what's wrong with you?
How dare you disrespect like that?
Who do you think you are?
Who do you think you're talking to?
You're ok?
Yeah,
Wait!
Now I'm ok!
He is a hustler, he's no good at all
He is a loser, he's a bum-bum-bum-bum
He lies, he fluffs,
He's unreliable
He's is a sucker with a gun
I know you told me I should stay away
I know you said he's just a dog astray
He is a bad boy with a tainted heart
And even I know this ain't smart
But, mama, I'm in love with a criminal
And this type of love isn't rational,
It's physical
Mamma, please don't cry, I will be all right
All reason aside, I just can't deny
I love that guy
He is a villain by the devil's law
He is a killer just for fun
That man's a snitch, unpredictable
He's got no conscience, he got none
I know
Should've let go, but no
'Cause he's a bad boy with a tainted heart
And even I know this ain't smart
But, mama, I'm in love with a criminal
And this type of love isn't rational,
It's physical
Mamma, please don't cry, I will be all right
All reason aside, I just can't deny
I love that guy
And he's got my name
Tattooed on his arm, his lucky charm
So I guess it's okay
He's with me
And we hear people talk
Trying to make remarks, keep us apart
But I don't even hear
I don't care
Cause, mama, I'm in love with a criminal
And this type of love isn't rational,
It's physical
Mamma, please don't cry, I will be all right
All reason aside, I just can't deny
I love that guy
Mama, I'm in love with a criminal
And this type of love isn't rational,
It's physical
Mamma, please don't cry, I will be all right
All reason aside, I just can't deny
I love that guy
The suspects have left the building
I repeat: they have left the building