I can tell you're lookin at me I know what you see
Any closer and you'll feel the heat
You don't have to pretend that you didn't notice me
Every look will make it hard to breathe
Bring the boys out
(yeah you know)
(we bring the boys out
we bring the boys out
yeah)
Bring the boys out
Soon as I step on the scene
I know that they'll be watching me watching me (get up)
I'ma be the hottest in this spot
There ain't no stopping me (That's funny) stopping me
I know life is a mystery
I'm gonna make history
I'm taking it from the start
Call all emergency I'm watching the phone ring
I'm feeling this in my heart (my heart)
Bring the boys out.
Girls' Generation make you feel the heat
And we're doin it we can't be beat
(Bring the boys out)
We're born to win Better tell all your friends
Cuz we get it in You know the girls
(Bring the boys out)
Wanna know my secrets But no I'll never tell
Cuz I got the magic touch and I'm not trying to fail
That's right (yes fly high!)
And I (I) (you fly high!)
Can't deny
I know I can fly
I know life is a mystery
I'm gonna make history
I'm taking it from the start
Call all emergency
I'm watching the phone ring
I'm feeling this in my heart (my heart)
Bring the boys out.
Girls' Generation make you feel the heat
And we're doin it we can't be beat
(Bring the boys out)
We're born to win Better tell all your friends
Cuz we get it in You know the girls
(Bring the boys out)
Girls bring the boys out!
I wanna dance right now
We can show em how the girls get down
Yes we go for more than zero
Number one everyone should know Check this out
All'a(all the) Boys, All'a(all the) Boys want my heart
Better know how to rock and don't stop
Oh gee we make it so hot
Girls generation we won't stop
Bring the boys out
It's not a fantasy
This is right for me
Living it like a star
Can't get the best of me
I'ma be what I wanna be
This is deep in my heart  (my heart)
I can tell you're lookin at me
I know what you see
Any closer and you'll feel the heat (Just Bring the boys out)
You don't have to pretend that you didn't notice me
Every look will make it hard to breathe (Bring The Boys out)
Cuz the girls bring the boys out
Girls bring the boys out
Girls' Generation make em feel the heat
And we're doin it we can't be beat (Bring the boys out)
We're born to win Better tell all your friends
Cuz we get it in You know the girls
(Bring the boys out)