It's the most beautiful
time of the year
Lights fill the streets
spreading so much cheer
I should be
playing in the winter snow
But I'mma be
under the mistletoe
I don't wanna miss
her on the holiday
But I can't stop
staring at your face
I should be playing
in the winter snow
But I'mma be
under the mistletoe
With you,
shawty with you
under the mistletoe,
Everyone's gathering
around the fire
Chestnuts roasting
like a hot July
I should be chillin'
with my folks, I know
But I'mma be
under the mistletoe
Word on the streets
Santa's coming tonight
Reindeers flying
through the sky so high
I should be making a list,
I know
But I'mma be
under the mistletoe
With you,
shawty with you
under the mistletoe
With you,
shawty with you
under the mistletoe
Hey love,
the Wise Men followed a star
The way
I followed my heart
And it led me
to a miracle
Aye love,
don't you buy me nothing
'Cause I am
feeling one thing
Your lips
on my lips
That's a Merry
Merry Christmas
It's the most beautiful
time of the year
Lights fill the streets
spreading so much cheer
I should be playing
in the winter snow
But I'mma be
under the mistletoe
I don't wanna miss her
on the holiday
But I can't stop
staring at your face
I should be playing
in the winter snow
But I'mma be
under the mistletoe
With you,
shawty with you
under the mistletoe
With you,
shawty with you
under the mistletoe
Kiss me
underneath the mistletoe
Show me baby
that you love me so
Kiss me
underneath the mistletoe
Show me baby
that you love me so