I feel you even though we're apart
and without you theres a hole in my heart
Ohh baby baby, though i tried i just cant adjust
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us, happened to us
We were in love we both felt the same
The good thing that we had boy was insane
We had a bond that would never break
why we let it go oh
We used to stay all night long
kissing to our favorite songs
Tell me where it all went wrong
thats what i got to know oh
Cuz i feel you even though we're apart
and without you theres a hole in my heart
Ohh baby baby though i tried i just cant adjust
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us
Thought that i could get over you oh
but baby that is so far from true
Ohh baby baby got something i want to discuss
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us, happened to us
I think that we oughta gotta work it out
like air your love i cant live without
So have mercy dont leave me in doubt saying i love still hurts
still burns, still burns
I try to go my separate way
at first i thought it was okay
I miss you more with each day, so to you i turn
Cuz i feel you even though we're apart
and without you theres a hole in my heart
Ohh baby baby though i tried i just cant adjust
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us
Thought that i could get over you oh
but baby that is so far from true
Ohh baby baby got something i want to discuss
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us, happened to us
I know that you saw me with someone else
But believe me im over myself
Cuz i feel you even though we're apart
and without you theres a hole in my heart
Ohh baby baby though i tried i just cant adjust
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us
Thought that i could get over you oh
but baby that is so far from true
Ohh baby baby got something i want to discuss
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us, happened to us
(tell me, yeah)
Cuz i feel you even though we're apart
and without you theres a hole in my heart
Ohh baby baby though i tried i just cant adjust
Ohh boy what happened to us, happened to us
(what happened to us)