This one's for you and me,
Living out our dreams
We are right where we should be
Lift my arms out wide, I open my eyes
And now all I wanna see
Is a sky full of lighters
A sky full of lighters
By the time you hear this
I will have already spiralled up
I would never do nothing
To let you cowards fuck my world up
If I was you, I would duck,
Or get struck like lightening fighters keep fighting,
Put your lighters up, point em' skyward
Had a dream I was king,
I woke up, still king?
This rap game's nipple is mine for the milking
Till nobody else even fucking feels me,
Till' it kills me
I swear to god
I'll be the fucking illest in this music
There is or there ever will be, disagree
Feel free,
But from now on I'm refusing to ever give up
The only thing I ever gave's using no more excuses
Excuse me if my head is too big for this building
And pardon me
If I'm a cocky prick but you cocks are slick
Poppin shit on how you flipped ya life around,
Crock-o-shit
Who you dicks try to kid,
Flipped dick, you did the opposite
You stayed the same,
Just cock back with this still cock you pricks
I love it when I tell em shove it
Cause it wasn't that long ago when Marshall said bust a leg
Muster cause he couldn't cut mustard mustered up
Nothing brain fuzzy, cause he's buzzin',
Woke up from that buzz
Now you wonder why he does it?
How he does it?
Wasn't cause he had buzzards circle around his head
Waiting for him to drop dead, was it?
Or was it, cause them bitches wrote him off
Little hussy ass, cause fuck it,
Guess it doesn't matter now, does it
What difference it make?
What it take to get it through your thick skulls
As if this ain't some bullshit
People don't usually come back this way
From a place that was dark as I was in
Just to get to this place
Now let these words be like a switch blade to a haters rib cage
And let it be known from this day forward
I wanna just say thanks
Cause your hate is what gave me strength
So let em cause
I came with 5'9' but I feel like I'm 6'8'
This one's for you and me,
Living out our dreams
We are right where we should be
Lift my arms out wide I open my eyes
And now all I wanna see
Is a sky full of lighters
A sky full of lighters
By the time you hear this I'll probably already be outtie
I advance like going from toting iron to going
From buying 4 or 5 of the homies to iron man outtie
My daddy told me slow down, boy,
You goin to blow it
And I ain't gotta stop the beat a minute
To tell Shady I love him
The same way that he did Dr Dre on the Chronic
Tell him how real he is or high I am
Or how I would kill for him for him to know it
I cried many tears, my daddy got a bad back
So it's only right that I right till he can march
Right into that post office and tell em to hang it up
Now his career's Lebron's jersey in 20 years
I'll stop when I'm at the very top
You shitted on me on your way up
It's bout to be a scary drop
Cause what goes up must come down
You going down on something
You don't wanna see like a hairy box
Every hour, happy hour now
Life is wacky now
Used to have to eat the cat to get the pussy
Now I'm just the cats meow,
Classic cow,
Always down for the catchweight like Pacquiao
Ya'll are doomed
I remember when T-Pain ain't wanna work with me
My car starts itself,
Parks itself and autotunes
Cause now I'm in the Aston
I went from having my city locked up
To getting treated quite like Patrick
And now I'm fantastic compared to a weed high
And y'all niggas just gossiping
Like bitches on a radio and TV
See me, we fly
Y'all buggin out like Wendy Williams staring at a bee-hive
And how real is that
I remember signing my first deal
And now I'm the second best I can deal with that
Now Bruno can show his ass,
Without the MTV awards gag
You and I know what it's like
To be kept down, forced to fight
But tonight we're alright
So hold up your light
Let it shine
Cause this one's for you and me
Living out our dreams
We are right where we should be
With my arms out wide I open my eyes
And now all I wanna see
Is a sky full of lighters
A sky full of lighters