I'm trying not to pretend,
It won't happen again and again like that.
I never thought it would end,
'cause you got up in my head, in my head like that.
And made me happy, baby, love is crazy,
So amazing, but it's changing, rearranging,
I don't think I can take anymore
'Cause the walls burned up and our love fell down,
And it turned into whatever, now we're saying never.
Feel the fire 'cause it's all around,
And it's burning for forever and always.
You gotta let it go the other way
And live for another day,
'cause it ain't the same, my baby.
Watch it all falling to the ground.
No happy ever after  just disaster.
I didn't want it this way,
I only wanted to say I loved you right.
But now you're walking away,
And leaving me here to stay,
So foolish of me to wait for you to realize
All the things I gave you, made you,
Changed you, your dreams came true
When I met you, now forget you,
Don't want anymore
'Cause the walls burned up and our love fell down
And it turned into whatever, now we're saying never.
Feel the fire 'cause it's all around,
And it's burning for forever and always.
You gotta let it go the other way
At least for another day,
Cause it ain't the same, my baby.
Watch it all falling to the ground.
No happy ever after  just disaster.
You shot the bullet, you shot the bullet that killed me,
Not feeling my heart beat, and now it's dying.
I am through it, I-I am through the agony,
Now my eyes are drying, drying,
No more crying,
Lying's just a game.
So disaster strikes,
And I'm alright
'cause my love's on its way... yeah
Burning up forever and always... yeah
'Cause the walls burned up, and our love fell down,
And it turned into whatever, now we're saying never.
Feel the fire 'cause it's all around,
And it's burning for forever and always.
You gotta let it go the other way
At least for another day,
'Cause it ain't the same, my baby.
Watch it all falling to the ground.
No happy ever after just disaster.
'Cause the walls burned up, and our love fell down,
And it turned into whatever, now we're saying never.
Feel the fire 'cause it's all around,
And it's burning for forever and always.
You gotta let it go the other way
At least for another day,
'Cause it ain't the same, my baby.
Watch it all falling to the ground.
No happy ever after  just disaster, just disaster
Burning for forever and always, yeah.
Subtitled by Wind@NhacSo