Girl I see it in your eyes you're disappointed
Cause I'm the foolish one that you anointed with your heart
I tore it apart
And girl what a mess I made upon your innocence
And no woman in the world deserves this
But here I am asking you for one more chance
Can we fall, one more time?
Stop the tape and rewind
Oh and if you walk away I know I'll fade
Cause there is nobody else
It's gotta be you
Only you
It's got to be you
Now girl I hear it in your voice and how it trembles
When you speak to me I don't resemble, who I was
You've almost had enough
And your actions speak louder than words
And you're about to break from all you've heard
Don't be scared, I ain't going no where
I'll be here, by your side
No more fears, no more crying
But if you walk away
I know I'll fade
Cause there is nobody else
It's gotta be you
Only you
It's got to be you
Oh girl, can we try one more, one more time?
One more, one more, can we try?
One more, one more time
I'll make it better
One more, one more, can we try?
One more, one more,
Can we try one more time to make it all better?
Cos its gotta be you
Its gotta be you
It's gotta be you
Only you
Only you!