If you ever leave me, baby
Leave some morphine at my door
'Cause it would take a whole lot of medication
To realize what we used to have
We don't have it anymore
There's no religion that could save me
No matter how long my knees are on the floor
So keep in mind all the sacrifices I'm makin'
To keep you by my side
And keep you from walkin' out the door
Cause there'll be no sunlight
If I lose you, baby
And there'll be no clear skies
Just like the clouds my eyes will do the same
If you walk away, everyday it will rain
Rain,
I'll never be your mother's favorite
Your daddy can't even look me in the eye
If I was in their shoes, I'd be doing the same thing
Sayin' there goes my little girl
Walkin' with that troublesome guy
But they're just afraid of something they can't understand
But little darlin' watch me change their minds
Yeah, for you I'll try,
I'll pick up these broken pieces 'till I'm bleeding
If that'll make it right
Cause there'll be no sunlight
If I lose you, baby
And there'll be no clear skies
Just like the clouds my eyes will do the same
If you walk away, everyday it will rain
Rain,
Don't you say, goodbye
I'll pick up these broken pieces 'til I'm bleeding
If that'll make it right
Cause there'll be no sunlight
If I lose you, baby
And there'll be no clear skies
Just like the clouds my eyes will do the same
If you walk away, everyday it will rain
Rain,