I can't believe I had to see
The girl of my dreams cheating on me
The pain you caused has left me dead inside
I'm gonna make sure, you regret that night
I feel you close, I feel you breathe
And now it's like you're here
You're haunting me
You're out of line, you're out of sight
You're the reason that we started this fight
But I know,
I just gotta let it go,
I, should've known
I gotta learn to say goodbye now
I throw my armour down,
And leave the battleground
For the final time now,
I, I know.
I'm running from a warzone
In our house, I hate that place,
Everywhere I walk I see your face
Try to erase a memory with a flame,
And hope I never see you again
Standing here, in this burning room,
You know the end could never come so soon,
It's clear to me,
The lies you use,
The ones that killed me ain't hurting you,
So I know,
I just gotta let it go,
I, should've known
I gotta learn to say goodbye now
I throw my armour down,
And leave the battleground
For the final time now,
I, I know.
I'm running from a warzone
I can't do this anymore
What are we fighting for?
I'm running from a warzone...
I know,
I just gotta let it go,
I, should've known
I gotta learn to say goodbye now
I throw my armour down,
And leave the battleground
For the final time now,
I, I know.
I'm running from a warzone