Summer after high school
when we first met
We make out in
your Mustang to Radiohead
And on my 18th Birthday
We got matching tattoos
Used to steal your parents' liquor
And climb to the roof
Talk about our future
Like we had a clue
Never planned that one day
I'd be losing you
In another life
I would be your girl
We keep all our promises
Be us against the world
In another life
I would make you stay
So I don't have to say
You were the one that got away
The one that got away
I was June and you were
my Johnny Cash
Never one without the other
we made a pact
Sometimes when I miss you
I put those records on
Someone said you had
your tattoo removed
Saw you downtown
singing the Blues
It's time to face the music
I'm no longer your muse
But in another life
I would be your girl
We keep all our promises
Be us against the world
In another life
I would make you stay
So I don't have to say
You were the one that got away
The one that got away
The o-o-o-o-o-one
All this money can't buy me
a time machine (Nooooo)
Can't replace you with a
million rings (Nooooo)
I shoulda told you
what you meant to me (Wooow)
'Cause now I pay the price
In another life
I would be your girl
We keep all our promises
Be us against the world
In another life
I would make you stay
So I don't have to say
You were the one that got away
The one that got away
The o-o-o-o-o-one
The One..
In another life
I would make you stay
So I don't have to say
You were the one that got away
The one that got away