I've been around the world
Hey hey
In the kitchen
Where I'm cooking
What is good for me?
Spices from the globe
Little by little
It's the finest meal
It's appetite for hope
Come and see
You mix it all together
In your dreams
Ingredients from the seven seas
And I'm realizing things ain't
What they seem
That's the riddle of it
That's the spirit of it
That's the power of life
I've been around the world
And I've seen it all
The sun will always rise
And fall
I've been around the world
And I want you to see
I've been the only girl
All surrounded by mystery
In the living room
I'm cleaning up
From top to floor
The place I love the most
The wall is covered up with
All my souvenirs
I've got from coast to coast
Come and see
You mix it all together
In your dreams
Ingredients from the seven seas
And I'm realizing things ain't
What they seem
That's the riddle of it
That's the spirit of it
That's the power of life
I've been around the world
And i've seen it all
The sun will always rise
And fall
I've been around the world
And I want you to see
I've been the only girl
All surrounded by mystery
I'm still coming around
I keep chasing dreams
Girl I keep coming around
Hey hey
I keep coming around
And I can never stop
Girl I keep coming around
Cause if I do I'll walk around
Around
Around the world
I've been around the world
Hey hey
All surrounded by mystery
I've been around the world
And i've seen it all
The sun will always rise
And fall
Round the world