I am the Candyman - Coming from Bountyland.
I wish that you were my Lollipop.
Sweet things, I will never get enough.
If you show me to the sugar tree,
will you give me a sodapop for free.
Come with me Honey,
I'm your sweet sugar Candyman.
Run like the wind - fly with me to Bountyland.
Bite me, I'm yours - if you're hungry please understand.
This is the end - of the sweet sugar Candyman.
Oh my love - I know you are my Candyman,
And oh my love - your word is my command.
And oh my love - let us fly to Bountyland.
You are my Lollipop - sugar sugar top
I wish that I were a Bubble Gum,
chewing on me baby all day long.
I will be begging for sweet delight,
until you say I'm yours tonight.
Come with me Honey,
I'm your sweet sugar Candyman.
Run like the wind - fly with me to Bountyland.
Bite me, I'm yours - if you're hungry please understand.
This is the end - of the sweet sugar Candyman.
Oh my love - I know you are my Candyman,
And oh my love - your word is my command.
And oh my love - let us fly to Bountyland.
Oh my love - I know you are my Candyman,
And oh my love - your word is my command.
And oh my love - let us fly to Bountyland.
I am the Candyman - Coming from Bountyland
Oh my love - I know you are my Candyman,
And oh my love - your word is my command.
And oh my love - let us fly to Bountyland.
You are my Lollipop - sugar sugar top