Give me time to reason,
give me time to think it through
Passing through the season,
where I cheated you
I will always have a cross to wear,
but the bolt reminds me I was there
So give me strength,
to face this test tonight
If only I could turn back time,
If only I had said what I still hide
I would stay for the night... for the night
Claim your right to science,
Claim your right to see the truth
Though my pangs of conscience,
Will drill a hole in you
I've seen it coming like a thief in the night,
I've seen it coming from the flesh of your light
So give me strength,
to face this test tonight
If only I could turn back time,
if only I had said what I still hide
if only I could turn back time,
I would stay.
The bolt reminds me I was there
the bolt reminds me I was there
If only I could turn back time,
If only I had said what I still hide
I would stay for the night... for the night
If only I could turn back time,
If only I had said what I still hide
I would stay for the night.
If only I could
If only I could turn back time,
I would stay for the night.
If only I could
If only I could turn back time,
I would stay for the night.
If only I could