Nhacso's Lyric
Ngày còn thơ bé cha về khi đêm mờ sương
Ngọn đèn dầu hiu hắt in hình cha tôi ngả vệt tường
Người dịu dàng hỏi thăm con và nhẹ nhàng ngồi bên con
Giọng cười hiền làm cho con được sưởi ấm dưới bóng cha
Đời nhọc nhằn là để cho con, ngày lại ngày cặm cụi nuôi con
Chỉ một mình một mình cha tôi gà trống nuôi con từ bé thơ!
Oh, Papa! Có những lúc con chợt thấy người
Ngồi thật buồn như đã ngậm ngùi tìm lại mẹ xuôi dòng tiếc nuối
Oh, Papa! Tháng năm qua nay cha đã già
Mong manh nghiêng nghiêng một bóng cả
Con chẳng làm được gì cho cha, Papa!
Nhacso's Lyric
The days, the months and the years that passed by
Give me life... but you used to lie
And tell me they were... happy tears!
I wish you'd better and those tears were mine
I can feel your change on hand, on my soulder
A million memories, they start to wander...
Now that I'm older, a little bit wiser
I know that no greater than the love that yours !
Oh, Papa! Do you remember?
We only had each other when there was nobody else...
Oh, Papa! Have I ever thanked you?
I always looked up to you
And you're always in my heart... Papa!
You were my eyes when I was crying
You were my blanket through the night
You were my strength when I had none to fight
You were my patience when there was no time
Oh, Papa! Do you remember?
We only had each other when there was nobody else
Oh, Papa! Have I ever thanked you?
I always looked up to you
And you're always in my heart.
Oh, Papa! Có những lúc con chợt thấy người
Ngồi thật buồn như đã ngậm ngùi tìm lại mẹ xuôi dòng tiếc nuối
Oh, Papa! Tháng năm qua nay cha đã già
Mong manh nghiêng nghiêng một bóng cả
Con chẳng làm được gì cho cha, Papa!
Nhacso's Lyric