Love After War
Oooh it's a knock-out baby, you want the fight
I said I'm sorry that I acted like a selfish child
Please forgive me baby, I was out of line
You know I can make it right
Don't you love it when we fight
Love After War
I need you tonight baby
Come on and let me make it right baby
Love After War
I'm knockin on your door
You know I want it, you know I want ya
Cuddle up, doors, clap, door slams and broken lights
Bottles at the TV screen
You got to go, or I'm gonna leave
Throwing closing to the yard
When we go we go so hard
It only makes me want you more, more, more
Love After War
I need you tonight baby
Come on and let me make it right baby
Love After War
I'm knockin on your door
You know I want it,
Don't you leave
That's all we need
All we need
Thats all we need
Love After War
I just wanna love you lady
Wanna put down our weapons baby
Love After War
Lay it cause down on the floor
And give me some love after war
Love After War
You know it's gonna be your night baby
You know the way that we fight
Love After War
Just drink this glass of wine
And you'll remember you're mine
Love After War
Remember you're mine babe, you're mine baby
Come on and let me in
Love After War
Let me let me in
You know I want it, you know I want you baby