Is it time, I hear you can give it,
Give it, give it, give it all
One through the note your list you can get it,
Get it, get it, get it now
Make your wish tonight
When you open your eyes
When the lights go bright girl
I'll be right there
Baby you deserved everything you want
It's your night, ohhh
Wanna put my EP a chance a girl
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
Fa la la, fa la la
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
(Fa la la)
Know that it's christmas time
You got on my favourite treasure
You're looking, looking, looking, good
Snow falling on your hair, and I don't, I don't
Wanna get it off
Even the stars in the sky can't outshine your eyes
Wanna be your biggest gift
Baby you deserved everything you want
It's your night, ohhh
Wanna put my EP a chance a girl
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
Fa la la, fa la la
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
(Fa la la)
Know that it's christmas time
I'll take your heart with...
Fa la la, fa la la
Baby cuz you're the reason to be...
I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
Fa la la, fa la la
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
(Fa la la)
Know that it's christmas time
Fa la la, fa la la
Like christmas
Know that it's christmas time
Fa la la, fa la la
Know that it's christmas time...