I'm gonna marry the night,
I won't give up on my life
I'm a warrior queen,
Live passionately tonight
I'm gonna marry the dark,
Gonna make love to the stark
I'm a soldier to my,
Emptiness im a winner
I'm gonna marry the night,
I'm gonna marry the night
I'm gonna marry, the night,
I'm not gonna cry anymore
leave nothing on these streets to explore
m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry the night
oh m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry the night
I'm gonna lace up my boots,
throw on some leather and grooves
Down the streets i got love,
and my fishnet loves im a sinner
Then i'll go down to the bar,
but I won't cry anymore
I'll hold my whiskey up high,
kiss the bartender twice
I'm a looser
I'm gonna marry the night,
I'm gonna marry, the night,
I'm not gonna cry anymore
leave nothing on these streets to explore
m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry the night
oh m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry the night
Nothing's to cool,
to take me from you,
New York is not
just a tan that you never knew
Love is the new denim or black
Skeleton guns or wedding bells in the attic
Get Ginger ready
Climb to El Camino front
Wont poke holes in the seat with my heals,
thats where we make love
Come on and run,
come on and run
I'm gonna marry, the night,
I'm gonna burn a hole in the road
leave nothing on these streets to explore
m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry the night
oh m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry the night
oh m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry,
m-m-m-marry the night
I'm gonna marry,
marry, I'm gonna marry,
marry, come on, come on,
the night, the night, the night,
the night, the night, the night, the night,