When you wanna do something that’s new
And it seems really.. \NReally hard to do
You feel like quitting.. \NFeel ya through
Well I have some advice for you..
Don’t give up… \NKeep on tryin’
You’re gonna make it, I aint lyin’
Don’t give up, don’t ever quit..
Try and try and you can do it..
Don’t give up……. Yeahh
If you want to catch a ball
But you’re havin’ no luck at all
The ball hits your head, it hits your nose
It hits your belly, \Nyour chin and toes
Well try and try and try again
Keep on trying to the end
You put your hands out in the air,
you’ll catch the ball ,\NYes this I swear,
Don’t give up, keep on going,
You’re on a boat, so keep on rowing
Don’t give up, don’t ever stop
Try and try and you’ll come out on top
Don’t give up
You got yourself rollerskates, \Nyou put them on
And you feel great, you stand up
Then you fall, don’t think you can skate at all
You get back up, then you trip, \Nyou skip and tip and slip, and flip,
you try and try and try some more,
Soon you’re skating across the floor,
Don’t give up, keep on moving,
You’re gonna get there, \Njust keep on grooving
Don’t give up, don’t pack it in
Try and try, and you’ll win
Don’t give up, no no no
Don’t give up, no no no no
Don’t give up, no no, Don’t give up