The way you move is like a full on rainstorm
And I'm a house of cards
You're the kinda reckless that should send me running
But I kinda know I won't get far
And you stood there in front of me just
Close enough to touch
Close enough to hope you couldn't see
What I was thinking of
Drop everything now
Meet me in the pouring rain
Kiss me on the sidewalk
Take away the pain
'Cause I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
Get me with those green eyes, baby
As the lights go down
Something that'll haunt me when you're not around
'Cause I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
My mind forgets to remind me
You're a bad idea
You touch me once and it's really something
You find I'm even better than you
Imagined I would be
I'm on my guard for the rest of the world
But with you I know it's no good
And I could wait patiently but I really wish you would
Drop everything now
Meet me in the pouring rain
Kiss me on the sidewalk
Take away the pain
'Cause I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
Get me with those green eyes, baby
As the lights go down
And something that'll haunt me when you're not around
'Cause I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
I run my fingers through your hair
And watch the lights go out
Just keep on keeping your eyes on me
It's just strong enough to make you feel right
Lead me up the staircase
Won't you whisper soft and slow
I'm captivated by you baby
Like a firework show
Drop everything now
Meet me in the pouring rain
Kiss me on the sidewalk
Take away the pain
'Cause I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
Get me with those green eyes, baby
As the lights go down
And something that'll haunt me when you're not around
'Cause I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
Sparks fly, baby smile,
Sparks fly