Shawty,
what yo name is?
Them hustlers
keep on talkin'
They like
the way I'm walkin'
You saying
that you want me
So press record,
I'll let you film me
On your video phone,
make a cameo
Tape me on your video phone,
I can handle you
Watch me on your video phone,
on your video,
If you want me
you can watch me on your video phone
I love how you
approach me,
Fresh white with your pants
hangin' grown man low
Everything you sayin'
soundin' good to me
No need to
convince me anymore
Swag up, it's right,
one blade, it's tight
And I smell
your cologne in the air
Baby,
you doin' somethin' right
You just cancelled
every other man here
You say you like my bag
and the color of my nails
You can see
that I got it goin' on
I wanna make sure
you remember me
So I'ma leave my number
on your video phone
I got no time
for frontin'
I know just
what I'm wantin'
If it's gonna be
you and me,
when I call, they better
see me on your video screen
Them hustlers
keep on talkin'
They like
the way I'm walkin'
You saying
that you want me
So press record,
I'll let you film me
On your video phone,
make a cameo
Tape me on your video phone,
I can handle you
Watch me on your video phone,
on your video,
If you want me,
you can watch me on your video phone
You my phone star,
And I'm happy when my lights flashin',
'Cause you on my receiver
Hubba, hubba, honey, baby is so sexy
that he should win an Oscar
And when
you miss me,
Just remember
that I always got you with me
I'll be your Gene,
you'll be my Brando
I'ma put you in my move,
if you think that you can handle
Can you handle it?
I know you like that,
can you handle it?
Turn you into a star,
I got it like that
Baby don't fight it,
'Cause when I miss yo
call I hit you right back
On my video phone,
You like what you see?
Them hustlas like my fashion,
You wanna video me?
They like the way I'm walkin',
You like what you see?
You sayin'
that you want me,
So press record,
I'll let you film me
On your video phone,
make a cameo
Tape me on your video phone,
I can handle you
Watch me on your video phone,
on your video,
If you want me,
you can watch me on your video phone
Can you handle it?
Tell 'em, B
You like what you see?
Can you handle it?
You wanna video me?
You like what you see?
Can you handle it?
Go on and video me,
You like what you see?
Can you handle it?
You wanna video me?
You know them Gs,
they be hollerin',
'specially them hot ones
Brooklyn, Atlanta,
Houston, to New Orleans
When they see me, they be like
"Yo B, let me call you"
You breakin' my focus, boy,
you cute and you ballin'
You like it
when I shake it?
Shawty on a mission,
what yo name is?
What,
you want me naked?
If you likin' this position
you can tape it
On your video phone
Hustla keep on talkin'
You like
the way it's poppin'
You sayin'
that you want me
Press record and baby,
film me
On your video phone,
make a cameo
Tape me on your video phone,
I can handle you
Watch me on your video phone,
on your video,
If you want me,
you can watch me on your video phone
Video phone...