Why is the sky so much more blue?
Why is the breeze so perfect today?
Pretending like I don't know
Like I didn't hear a thing
Like I erased it
Should we start talking about something else?
Should we kiss so we can't say anything?
My eyes fill with tears, so I lift my head up
I smile a little so that they won't fall
Why are you like this to me?
What are you saying?
All the things we talked about go to the sky
The words I have never said
The words I didn't know, I'd say as I cried
I like you, oppa
what do I do?
Was my recently hairstyle change bad?
Did I wear the wrong clothes?
Still pretending like I don't know
Like I don't remember
Should I act as if nothing happened?
Should I just say that we should go out?
My eyes fill with tears, so I lift my head up
I smile a little, so they won't fall
Why are you like this to me?
What are you saying?
All the things we talked about go to the sky
The words I have never said
The words I didn't know, I'd say as I cried
I, oppa, like you
what do I do?
Don't say those kind of sad things while looking at me like this
Is it that I'm childish, or a bit slow?
I can't believe it
Even though I'm crying, I smile
I block your way and I just smile widely
Why are I being like this?
Do I have no shame?
I fold up my pride and throw it up to the sky
The words I have never said
The words I might never be able to say again
I, oppa, like you
(one, two)
I'm in my dream
(It's too beautiful, beautiful day)
(Make it a good day)
(Just don't make me cry)
Such a good day