Tryin' to do my own thing, and I'm starting to figure it out
That it's alright keep it together where ever we go
And it's alright oh well whatever
Everybody needs to know
You might be crazy
Have I told you lately
That I love you
You're the only reason that I'm not afraid to fly
And it's crazy
That someone could change me
Now no matter what it is I have to do
I'm not afraid to try
And you need to know that you're the reason, why!
I don't even care when they say you're a little bit off
Look them in the eye I'd say I could never get enough
Cuz it's alright keep it together where ever we go
And it's alright oh well whatever
Everybody needs to know
You might be crazy
Have I told you lately
That I love you,
You're the only reason that I'm not afraid to fly,
And it's crazy
That someone could change me
Now no matter what it is I have to do
I'm not afraid to try
And you need to know that you're the reason, why!
If it was rainin' you would yell at the sun
Pick up the pieces when the damage is done
You say it's just another day in the shade
Look at what a mess we made
You might be crazy
Have I told you lately
That I love you
You're the only reason that I'm not afraid to fly
You might be crazy
Have I told you lately
That I love you
You're the only reason that I'm not afraid to fly
And it's crazy
That someone could change me
Now no matter what it is I have to do
I'm not afraid to try
And you need to know that you're the reason, why!
I don't wanna make a scene. I don't wanna let you down