Elevator buttons
And morning air
Stranger's silence
Makes me wanna take the stairs
If you were here
We'd laugh about
Their vacant stares
But right now...
My time is theirs
Seems like there's always
Someone who disapproves
They'll judge it like they
Know about me and you
And the verdict comes from laws
With nothing else to do
The jury's out...
My choice is you
So don't you worry
Your pretty little mind
People throw rocks
At things that shine
And life makes love look hard
The stakes are high
The water's rough
But this love is ours
You never know
What people have
Up their sleeves
Ghosts from your past
Gonna jump out at me
Lurking in the shadows
With their lipgloss smiles
But I don't care...
Cause right now you're mine
And you'll say -
Don't you worry
Your pretty little mind
People throw rocks
At things that shine
And life makes love look hard
The stakes are high
The water's rough
But this love is ours
And it's not theirs to speculate
If it's wrong and..
Your hands are tough
But they are where
Mine belong in...
I'll fight their doubts
And give you faith
With this song for you...
Cause I love
The gap between your teeth
And I love
The riddles that you speak
And any snide remarks
From my father about
Your tattoos
Will be ignored
Cause my heart is yours
So don't you worry
Your pretty little mind
People throw rocks
At things that shine
And life makes love look hard
Don't you worry
Your pretty little mind
People throw rocks
At things that shine
But they can't take what's ours
They can't take what's ours
The stakes are high
The water's rough
But this love is ours