watching the minute hand
frozen solid not moving
still we believe we can
but we're afraid of losing
watching from over here
its hardly worth competing
im almost out of here
while breaking a heart thats beating
just as i start giving up
im not backing up
run into the light
get out of your own way
not afraid to fight
believe in what you say
i'll hold on till the night
hanging by a thread
i'm not scared to let go
thoughts inside your head
that creep up to get you
i believe this is right
so i'll hold on til the night
i climbed up on a tree
to get a new perspective
if love is worth the time
the price is being rejected
just as i start falling down
i turned this around
run into the light
get out of your own way
not afraid to fight
believe in what you say
i'll hold on till the night
hanging by a thread
i'm not scared to let go
thoughts inside your head
that creep up to get you
i believe this is right
so i'll hold on til the night
hold on til im with you
all i've got to give you
all my fears are slowly fading to never know
yes i start running running running running!!
run into the light
get out of your own way
not afraid to fight
believe in what you say
i'll hold on till the night
(believe that this is the night)
hanging by a thread
i'm not scared to let go
thoughts inside your head
that creep up to get you
i believe this is right
so i'll hold on til the night