Went from Mr. 305 (Dade county)
to Worldwide (All around the world)
Now.. we're International
So, International [x2]
You can't catch me boy
I'm overseas at about a 100g's for sho'
Don't test me boy
Cause I rap with the best for sho'
305 til the death of me
Cremate my body let the ocean have what's left of me
But for now forget about that
Blow the whistle baby you the referee
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat
Ohh Miss International Love
I don't play football but I've touched down everywhere,
(everywhere?) everywhere
I don't play baseball but I've hit a home run everywhere, everywhere (dah!)
I've been to countries and cities I can't pronounce
And the places on the globe I didn't know existed
In Romania she pulled me to the centre she said
Pit you can have me and my sister
In Lebanon yeah the women are bomb
And in Greece you've guessed it the women ' they sweet
Spinned all around the world
but I ain't gon' lie there's nothing like Miami's heat
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat
Ohh Miss International Love
Down in DR, they're looking for Visa's
I ain't talking credit cards if you know what I mean!
En cuba la cosa esta dura
But the woman get down, if you know what I mean
In Colombia, the women got everything on,
with some of the most beautiful women I've ever seen
In Brazil, they're freaky with big oh boobs
and they bounce, blue, yellow and green!
In L.A. tengo la Mexicana,
In New York, tengo la Boricua
Besitos para todas las mujeres en Venezuela, muah!
Y en Miami, tengo cualquiera!
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat
Ohh Miss International Love
There's not a place that your love don't affect me baby
So don't ever change
I crossed the globe when I'm with you baby
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat
Ohh Miss International Love
You put it down like New York City
I never sleep
Wild like Los Angeles
My fantasy
Hotter than Miami
I feel the heat
Ohh Miss International Love
Oh Ohhh Ohh (So International)
International Love