You come around to every child in the world
Always on time you're never late, every year
How does it feel to work, everyone's off, no one to help you
How do you reach us all, it's for sure, no one does it better
Christmas is finally here
It's time to celebrate
'Cause you make a better world, year after year
Soon you'll be on your way
Spreading joy everywhere
There's no one like you
Santa, you are the one
You creep down the chimneys at night, that's right
And you always know who has been naughty or nice
How does it feel to work, everyone's off, no one to help you
How do you reach us all, it's for sure, no one does it better
Christmas is finally here
It's time to celebrate
'Cause you make a better world, year after year
Soon you'll be on your way
Spreading joy everywhere
There's no one like you
Santa you are the one
Thank you Santa, thank you (You are the one)
Don't go Santa, don't go (You are the one)
Don't go santa, don't go (You are the one)
I hope you enjoy this song
It's a gift from everyone
Thank you for all that you have done
Christmas is finally here
It's time to celebrate
'Cause you make a better world, year after year
Soon you'll be on your way
Spreading joy everywhere
There's no one like you
Santa you are the one
You are the one
Santa, you are the one
I said, you are the one