This is the time of year we can give it,
Give it, give it, give it all
One through ten on your list you can get it,
Get it, get it, get it now
Make your wish tonight
When you open your eyes
When the lights go bright girl
I'll be right there
Baby you de-serve every-thing you want
It's your night, ohhh
Wanna put my ear to your chest girl
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
Fa la la la la, fa la la la la
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
(Fa la la la la, fa la la la la)
I know that it's christmas time
You got on my favourite dress
You're looking, looking, looking good
Snow falling on your hair, and I don't, I don't
Wanna get it off
Even the stars in the sky can't outshine your eyes
Wanna be your biggest gift
Baby you de-served every-thing you want
It's your night, ohhh
Wanna put my ear to your chest now
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
Fa la la la la, fa la la la la
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
(Fa la la la la, fa la la la la)
I know that it's christmas time
I'll deck your heart with bells of holly (bells of holly)
Fa la la la la la la, fa la la la la la la...
Baby cause you're the reason to be, jolly
Fa la la la la la la, la la la la la la la...
I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
Fa la la la la, fa la la la la
Baby I hear melodies when your heart beats
Baby it sings to me like
(Fa la la la la, fa la la la la)
I know that it's christmas time
Fa la la la la, fa la la la la
Like christmas
I know that it's christmas time
Fa la la la la, fa la la la la
Know that it's christmas time...