Here we go, life's little lessons
Sometimes I mess up my intentions
I get lost; the cost was losing everything I've known
Laying here, staring at the ceiling
Sometimes still dealing with the feelings
Of where I've been, what I've done, I'm so far out there on my own
So quick to point the finger, to find the one to blame
So hard to realize I kept getting in my own way
I never thought that I was that strong
To carry on, carry on tonight
Forgiveness in your eyes with nothing to hide
All I know is you've shown me it's a beautiful world
Oh, it's a beautiful world, oh
No more fearing my reflection
Here I am with these imperfections
You know my faults but you don't care, you take them all
Until now I was barely breathing
But you gave me something to believe in
We're writing history, life's made up of small victories
We could go round in circles and never get to here
So good to realize that we have nothing left to fear
I never thought that I was that strong
To carry on, carry on tonight
Forgiveness in your eyes with nothing to hide
All I know is you've shown me it's a beautiful world
Oh, it's a beautiful world, oh
So quick to point the finger when it was me to blame
So hard to realize I kept getting in my own way
I never thought that I was that strong
To carry on, carry on tonight
Forgiveness in your eyes with nothing to hide
All I know is you've shown me it's a beautiful world
Oh, these stars aligned, let's watch them shine for you and I
Oh, these open skies, can we just lie here a while?
In this beautiful world
I never thought that I was that strong
To carry on but it's a beautiful world
It's a beautiful world