Take it off, I wanna love you
And errbody wanna touch you
You move it right wanna see what's up under
Then back it up, beep beep like a trucker
Nice thighs, nice waist
And you know I can't forget about your face
But don't none of that matter
I'm about to make your pockets fatter
Girl I just wanna see you strip, right now,
Cause it's late, late!
Girl I just wanna see you strip
Girl, take it down with' it
God damn you're sexy!
Girl I just wanna see you strip!
Got my jeans on with my jays on,
In the club with a pocket full of ones
This girl booty out of control
There she go up and down that pole
Which one I'm a take home, get my freak on
If you ain't freakin' we ain't speakin'
You think I'm playing
No, I'm not!
Let me see you back it up and drop
Yeah, I wanna see your legs in the air!
Baby don't worry about your hair over sex
I don't give a damn about that
In the club they're playing my song,
Turn it up, play it all night long!
If you think you can, and you know you can
I'm a give you all this money money money
Girl I just wanna see you strip, right now,
Cause it's late, late!
Girl I just wanna see you strip
Girl, take it down with' it
God damn you're sexy, baby!
Girl I just wanna see you strip!
Pants, shirt, you can take it off
Panties, bra, you can take it off
Red bottom heels, you can take 'em
Wait, wait, leave 'em on, cause I like my woman tall!
You got a hot momma, you're hotter than the sun,
I wanna put clothes on your body like a banana,
The only reason I dress you in that designer
Is to get you out that Dolce and Gabbana!
I throw this money up, he watch it all fall,
Anything you're wanting baby, you can have it all,
Starting with my last name now they call Mrs McCall
Girl I just wanna see you strip, right now,
Cause it's late, late!
Girl I just wanna see you strip
Girl, take it down with' it
God damn you're sexy, baby!
Girl I just wanna see you...