My angel
How'd you get to be so fly?
How'd you get to shine so bright, girl?
How'd you get to look like that?
Heaven don't you call her back
Yeah
Halo, halo
I'm not sayin' hi
Baby, there's a ring above your head
And it shines so bright in the sunlight, in the sunlight
Ayo, ayo
This is like a dream
Every bit of you, it makes me wake
How did I get here?
In the sunlight, in the sun
I must be in heaven
Cause I'm looking at an angel
Who's staring back at me
Her eyes so heavenly
I must be in heaven
Cause I'm looking at an angel
There's no one on this earth
That's made this beautiful
I must be in heaven
Here we are, looking at the stars
I can hear the beating of your heart
And I could listen to this song forever
You're the breeze, cruising down the coast
You're the jelly, baby I'm the toast
It's so sweet when we're together
And if I ruled the world
I'd name an island for ya
You can tell all your girls
I named an island for you
I must be in heaven
Cause I'm looking at an angel
Who's staring back at me
Her eyes so heavenly
I must be in heaven
Cause I'm looking at an angel
There's no one on this earth
That's made this beautiful
I must be in heaven
Halo, halo
I'm not sayin' hi
Baby, there's a ring above your head
And it shines so bright in the moonlight, in the moonlight
My angel
How'd you get to be so fly?
How'd you get to shine so bright, girl?
How'd you get to look like that?
Please heaven don't you call her back
Oh
My angel