The whole world
Feels a little bit more love
When Christmas comes
And everywhere that you go
People singing "Let It Snow"
And hanging up
That mistletoe
And me and you gonna have ourselves
A holiday
And we don't need nobody else
To celebrate
And we're gon' kiss our worries
And our cares away
I can't wait
Because this Christmas time
Get together
It's gonna be so nice
Better than ever
And baby you're the one
Special treasure
I can't wait to unwrap your love
Until Christmas comes
Oh baby...
So many souls hurt
So many don't have enough
When Christmas comes
But baby if you spread love
Someday it might be enough
To heal each other
One by one
And we gon' get together
And rejoice and pray
And we gon' help the world
Become a better place
And we gon' sing and shout
Because the savior reigns
So don't dismay
Because this Christmas time
Get together
It's gonna be so nice
Better than ever
Because this gift of love
Lasts forever
The Lord makes our hearts open up
Soon as Christmas comes
It's gon' be alright
When Christmas comes
Oh jingle all the way
Oh what fun, hmm
And we gon' reminisce about
The good old days
And we gon' laugh together as
The children play
And through the years is always
Gonna be this way
Come what may
Because this Christmas time
Get together
It's gonna be so nice
Better than ever
And baby you're the one
That I treasure
I can't wait to unwrap your love
When Christmas comes
Lalala dada dada dada dadada dada