Baby, you don't have to try to read my mind
Cause you know I wanna get it in
And tell me why would we just think about
If you wanna feel my body
We can be body to body
Body to body
I don't need to rush you girl
We should be body to body
Body to body, body to body
Uh, picture your body soaking, bath water
No panties on, come up out them leg warmers
Wrap up your hair, leave on your heels
Kissing you while I whisper, shawty how it feels
Let ya mind wonder, oh you're thinking dirty
I was thinking you can rob me, miss kentucky dirty
I dream about it, let's take advantage
My body on your body, hope that you can manage
Gotta moan it, damn-it, feels good
Pulling on her hair to let her know I'm still hood
Damn right, so unreal
This year of the Ace, bet she know the deal
Baby, you don't have to try to read my mind
Cause you know I wanna get it in
And tell me why would we just think about
If you wanna feel my body
We can be body to body
Body to body
I don't need to rush you girl
We should be body to body
Body to body, body to body
Uh, so quit ya contemplating, skip this conversation
By the way, you biting on your lip just gave me confirmation
Was that chanel 5? Very sexy fragrance
Are those your real eyes
Cant tell you're partially asian
But I know your body got me focused, I'm just so sedated
And I guarantee I do you better than your past-n-latest
Body to body, where is the sunny
Bet if I hit your spot, I'll make you tsunami
Change up the sheets, no time to sleep
Asked what she's thinking, she replied that I'm a beast
Yeah she replied that I'm a beast
Got it locked between the sheets and even in the streets
Baby, you don't have to try to read my mind
Cause you know I wanna get it in
And tell me why would we just think about
If you wanna feel my body
We can be body to body
Body to body
I don't need to rush you girl
But we should be body to body
Body to body, body to body
We'll make love on the floor, you kissing my tattoos
I'm pulling your hair you scream my name
Call me daddy, baby I got you
Go get in your bed and lay down, down, down
Girl, are you ready, cause I'm gonna want you face down, down, down
Right now, you f-ckin' with a real freak!
Baby, you don't have to try to read my mind
Cause you know I wanna get it in
And tell me why would we just think about
If you wanna feel my body
We can be body to body
Body to body
I don't need to rush you girl
We should be body to body
Body to body, body to body