Uno, dos, tres, cuatro
Good hit, I got that good hit
I got that good hit, I got that good hit
La la la la
Can I please have your attention?!
I'm so dope from head to toe
Armed and big, I drop it low
On the ground, I put it down
Round and round yeah here we go
Push up on me, I'm on the floor
Talk up on it, make me yours
Give you my love, give me love back
Baby I'm here, where you at
Got that New York swagger, Miami bass
Got my California Loub's on, all up in your face
Yeah I'm mid-west pimp tight, Texas fire
Don't you want me to have your babies
Don't you wish I was your Boo
I got that good hit (La la la la)
Don't you wish I was your boo
Palms up yup call them up yup
Tell 'em that I got that gold buy me some Louis stuff
Buy me Gucci stuff yup that I Love Lucy stuff
Baby I'm a classic don't you wanna bag me
Don't you like my outfit looking all flashy
Don't you wanna love me up right in traffic?
All up in my bum bum tryin' to back back
I'm standing here where you at
Got that New York swagger, Miami bass
Got my California Loub's on, all up in your face
Yeah I'm mid-west pimp tight, Texas fire
Don't you want me to have your babies
Don't you wish I was your Boo
I got that good hit (La la la la)
Don't you wish I was your boo
Can I please have your attention?!