Uhm, hello, can we get the party started, yeah!
Uhm, hello, can we get the party started…
Young Money
I'm the fireball, I'm the fireball, I'm the fire
Fire, fire, fire
Since I landed here, I gon' phone up a Obama
Shook the world up, now I caused a little drama
Leader of the new school, and yes I'm gonna
light up the block to the stage when I wanna
Brighter than the stars, throw my head up the curve
Don't get, walk it off, check it I walk with a slur
Levitating in my mom's all weather fur
Imma rock the world, til they follow Willow
I'm the fireball, I'm the fireball, I'm the fire
See I ain't never been the one to toot my own horn, beep, beep
Now watch me put her on
I set fire everywhere I play
make them all go insane, L.A to UK
Now Imma burn it up, when I step on the scene
My whole crew is fresh, and they rolling with me
You can turn me up yep to the extreme
Imma rock the World til they follow with me
Ayo Willow, didn't I just see you in China? (wattup)
Y-y-you're real major even though you a minor
Your daddy keep you in designer
Y-y-your gali-gali-gali ya your Girly kinda
Ok I'm the street fighter, call me Chun-Li
a-a-and it's goin' down, l-l-like a bum knee
Built a guest house to put the coupe in
'cause I'm a fireball, Hadouken
Put you under my wing, I'm the top boss
Ain't from Louisiana but I'm hot sauce
Cuffed the mountain just to go and build a house off
so I ain't never gotta worry what the house cost
If they comin' at you tell'em raise up
When it's time to whip your hair put your braids up
Tell'em escalator, elevator yeah that mean to step your weight up
Ain't nobody greater, Will and Jada is my neighbor, hater!
Watch the fire burn, burn, burn
Watch me heat it up
Watch the fire burn, burn, burn...
[Hook] till fade...