You da one that I dream about all day
You da one that I think about always
You Are da One So I Make Sure I Behave
My love is your love, your love is my love
Baby, I love you, I need you here
Give me all the time
Baby we meant to be
You got me, smiling all the time
Cause you know how to give me that
You know how to pull me back
When I go runnin, runnin
Tryin' to get away from loving ya
You know how to love me hard
I won't lie, I'm falling hard
Yep, I'm falling for ya but there's nothin wrong with that
You da one that I dream about all day
You da one that I think about always
You Are da One So I Make Sure I Behave
My love is your love, your love is my love
You da one that I dream about all day
You da one that I think about always
You Are da One So I Make Sure I Behave
My love is your love, your love is mine
Baby come, tear me now, hold me now
Make me come alive
You got the sweetest touch
I'm so happy, you came in my life
Cause you know how to give me that
You know how to pull me back
When I go runnin, runnin
Tryin' to get away from loving ya
You know how to love me hard
I won't lie, I'm falling hard
Yep, I'm falling for ya but there's nothin wrong with that
You da one that I dream about all day
You da one that I think about always
You Are da One So I Make Sure I Behave
My love is your love, your love is my love
You da one that I dream about all day
You da one that I think about always
You Are da One So I Make Sure I Behave
My love is your love, your love is mine
And Yes I'm kinda crazy,
That's what happens baby,
When you put it down
You should've give it to me
Good like that,
Should've hit it like that,
Had me yellin' like that
Didn't know you would've had me coming back
You da one that i'm feeling
You da one that i'm loving
Ain't no other, that's like you
No there's just one, one, one
No baby just one, one
I bet you wanna know
You da one that I dream about all day
You da one that I think about always
You Are da One So I Make Sure I Behave
My love is your love, your love is my love
You da one that I dream about all day
You da one that I think about always
You Are da One So I Make Sure I Behave
My love is your love, your love is mine