I can't sleep, I'm feeling wide awake
Tonight is taking it's time
How much more before the morning breaks
And I can leave it all behind
'Cause every time I try to close my eyes
I only end up seeing memories of you
And it's never enough, I'm waiting
Even though you're gone I can hear your heart
It's calling out my name like a flash in the dark
If this is just a dream
I won't give it back
I'll find a way to make it last
One more minute, wait, wait, wait, don't go
Just one more minute, wait, wait, wait, don't go
I am keeping every word you say
But how much longer can I hold on
Cause whispers echoing until they fade
Remind me that you're already gone
'Cause every time I try to chase your voice
I end up getting lost and running in circles
And it's never enough, I'm waiting
Even though you're gone I can hear your heart
It's calling out my name like a flash in the dark
If this is just a dream
I won't give it back
I'll find a way to make it last
One more minute wait, wait, wait, don't go
Just one more minute, wait, wait, wait, don't go
Wait, wait, wait, don't go
Oooh yeah, don't go
Even though you're gone I can hear your heart
It's calling out my name like a flash in the dark
If this is just a dream
I won't give it back
I'll find a way to make it last
One more minute, wait, wait, wait, don't go
Just one more minute, wait, wait, wait, don't go