Jaeurazn Presents :
Alexander - I Just
Translator : popgasa
I just wanna know - where you are
I just wanna know - who you're with
I just wanna know - you can tell me everything now
Will you come a bit closer? You just need to take my hand and smile
I will tell you from one to ten
From the moment you smiled at me, I fell for you
Even the smallest and slightest face expressions
Without knowing, I keep noticing and I just keep laughing
(Baby stay by my side, walk with me by my side)
Little by little, I hope my heart touches you
Just like that, come a bit more to my side
Now I will be by your side
I just wanna know - where you are
I just wanna know - who you're with
I just wanna know - you can tell me everything now
Will you come a bit closer? You just need to take my hand and smile
I think I saw you once in my dreams
That expression, the body and hand movements, every single one of them
(Yes you) Yes it's you, it's you
The one one one one person that I was looking for
(Baby stay by my side, walk with me by my side)
Little by little, I hope my heart touches you
Just like that, come a bit more to my side
Now I will be by your side
Now I want to stop having days without you
I don't need anything more
Memories without you have no meaning at all
I just wanna know - where you are
I just wanna know - who you're with
I just wanna know I just wanna know
Will you come a bit closer? You just need to take my hand and smile
I just
Thanks Everybody