Nhacso's Lyric, Timing by Heo Lầu 6
He is mine
I'm the only thing on his mind
He thinks about me all the time
He got my love everywhere
Nobody treats him like I do
Theres no party I'm not in the booth
My song keeps his heart in tune
like bada dadada dadumdum
He loves me and I love him too
He plays me all the night through
He keeps me spinning and grinning
And grinning over from you singing lalalalalala
Everyday lalalalalala he sings with me lalalalalala
He knows me he holds from introphase
Cuz the dj is mine and girl your wasting your time
He only rocks to my music he love the way I do it all night
The dj is mine
My baby my my baby baby (the dj is mine)
My baby my my baby baby
He only rocks to my music he love the way I do it all night
The dj is mine
Girls please don't you even try
My baby keeps me by his side
Even though you keep giving him the eyes
He don't even notice
Everyday lalalalalala he sings with me lalalalalala
He knows me he holds from introphase
Cuz the dj is mine and girl your wasting your time
He only rocks to my music he love the way I do it all night
Cuz the dj is is mine and girl your wasting your time
The dj...
I like the way he listening to blasting through
his head phones
Its me he falling in love with yeah I got
his head gone (head gone)
He cant even answer the phone my music keeps
turning him on n on n on n on n on
He said she said I say I own the dj
Stay yes on top of the charts I am the air play
flier then airplane
I noe u hear me incase u didn't let let me reiterate
Let me re let me re let me reiterate
He is mine
I'm the only thing on his mind
He thinks about me all the time
He got my love everywhere
Cuz the dj is mine and girl your wasting your time
He only rocks to my music he love the way I do it all night
The dj is mine
My baby my my baby baby ( the dj is mine)
My baby my my baby baby
He only rocks to my music he love the way I do it all night
The dj is mine
Nhacso's Lyric, Timing by Heo Lầu 6