I've tried playing it cool
Girl when I'm looking at you
I can never be brave
Cause you make my heart race
Shot me out of the sky
You're my kryptonite
You keep me making me weak
Yeah, frozen and can't breathe
Some things gotta get loud
Cause if not, they just don't make you see
That I need you here with me now
Cause you've got that one thing
So get out, get out, get out of my head
And fall into my arms instead
I don't, I don't, don't know what it is
But I need that one thing
And you've got that one thing
Now I'm climbing the walls
But you don't notice at all
That I'm going out of my mind
All day and all night
Some things gotta get loud
Cause I'm dying just to know your name
And I need you here with me now
Cause you've got that one thing
So get out, get out, get out of my head
And fall into my arms instead
I don't, I don't, don't know what it is
But I need that one thing
So get out, get out, get out of my mind
And come on, come into my life
I don't, I don't, don't know what it is
But I need that one thing
And you've got that one thing
You've got that one thing
Get out, get out, get out of my head
And fall into my arms instead
So get out, get out, get out of my head
I don't, I don't, don't know what it is
But I need that one thing
Get out, get out, get out of my mind
And come on, come into my life
I don't, I don't, don't know what it is
But I need that one thing
And you've got that one thing