With everything happening today
You dont know whether you’re coming or going
But you think that you’re on your way
Life lined up on the mirror dont blow it
Look at me when Im talkin to you
You looking at me but I’m lookin through you
I see the blood in your eyes
I see the love in disguise
I see the pain here in your pride
I see you’re not satisfied
And I dont see nobody else
I see myself I’m looking at the
Mirror on the wall, here we are again
Through my rise and fall
You’ve been my only fan
You told me that they can understand the man I am
So why are we here talkin’ to each other again
Oh, I see the truth in your lies
I see nobody by your side
but I’m with you when you re all alone
And you correct me when Im lookin wrong
I see that guilt beneath the shame
I see your soul through your window pain
I see the scars that remain
I see you Wayne, Im lookin at the..
Mirror on the wall, here we are again
Through my rise and fall
You’ve been my only fan
You told me that they can understand the man I am
So why are we here talkin’ to each other again
Lookin at me now I can see my past
Damn I look just like my f-ckin dad
Light it up, thats smoke at mirrors
I even look good in the broken mirror
I see my momma smile thats a blessin
I see the change, I see the message
and no message could been any clearer
So I’m stared with the man in the…
Mirror on the wall, here we are again
Through my rise and fall
You’ve been my only fan
You told me that they can understand the man I am
So why are we here talkin’ to each other again
Mirror on the wall, here we are again
Through my rise and fall
You’ve been my only fan
You told me that they can understand the man I am
So why are we here talkin’ to each other again
Mirror on the wall
so why are we talkin to each other again