Lembrei desse sentimento
Gritando dentro de nós
Éramos todos meninos
E em cada um vivia uma paixão
Como na cena de um filme
Vencemos pesadelos, enfrentando os dragões
Criados por nossos medos
Fruto da imaginação
De frente a uma nova era
Na onda de uma canção
Nós construímos história
Mente, alma e coração
Long live the walls We crashed through
How the kingdom lights shined just for me and you
I was screaming long live all the magic we made
And bring on all the pretenders
One day we will be remembered
I said: remember this feeling
I passed the pictures around
Of all the years that we stood there
On the side-lines wishing for right now
We are the kings and the queens
You traded your baseball cap for a crown
When they gave us our trophies
And we held them up for our town
De frente a uma nova era
Na onda de uma canção
Nós construímos história
Mente, alma e coração
Long live the walls we crashed through
How the kingdom lights shined just for me and you
I was screaming long live all the magic we made
And bring on all the pretenders
I'm not afraid
Long live all the mountains we moved
I had the time of my life fighting dragons with you
I was screaming long live
The look on your face
And bring on all the pretenders
One day we will be remembered
Hold on, just spinning around
Confetti falls to the ground
May these memories break our fall
Lembrei do momento
Que fiz promessa pra nós dois
Pintando o nosso destino
Puro e simples, pleno e sem fim
Que fosse assim sem "goodbye"
Fosse pra sempre um cheguei
O sonho que construímos
Me vi feliz, eu te achei
Será muito mais que achar
Será muito além que pensar
Long live the walls we crashed through
I had the time of my life with you
Long, long live the walls we crashed through
How the kingdom lights shined Just for me and you
I was screaming long live all the magic we made
And bring on all the pretenders
I'm not afraid
Singing long live all the mountains we moved
I had the time of my life fighting dragons with you
Long, long live
The look on your face
And bring on all the pretenders
One day
We will be remembered