Cold as ice
And more bitter than a december
Winter night
That's how I treated you
And I know that I
I sometimes tend to loose my temper
And I cross the line
Yeah that's the truth
I know it gets hard sometimes
But I could never
Leave your side
No matter what I say
Coz if I wanted to go
I woulda gone by now but
I really need you near me
To keep my mind off the edge
If I wanted to leave
I woulda left by now
But you're the only one that knows me
Better than I know my self.
All along
I tried to pretend it didn't matter
If I was alone
Deep down I know
If you were gone
For even a day I wouldn't know which way to turn
Coz I'm lost without you.
I know it gets hard sometimes
But I could never
Leave your side
No matter what I say
Coz if I wanted to go
I woulda gone by now but
I really need you near me
To keep my mind off the edge
If I wanted to leave
I woulda left by now
But you're the only one that knows me
Better than I know my self.
I get kind of dark
Let it go to far
I can be obnoxious at times
But try and see my heart
Cause I need you now
So don't let me down
You are the only thing in this world
I would die without
Coz if I wanted to go
I woulda gone by now but
I really need you near me
To keep my mind off the edge
If I wanted to leave
I woulda left by now
But you're the only one that knows me
Better than I know my self.
Coz if I wanted to go
I woulda gone by now but
I really need you near me
To keep my mind off the edge
If I wanted to leave
I woulda left by now
But you're the only one that knows me
Better than I know my self.