L-U-V Madonna
Y-O-U You wanna
I see you coming and I don’t wanna know your name
L-U-V Madonna
I see you coming and you’re gonna have to change the game
Y-O-U You wanna
Would you like to try?
Give me a reason why
Give me all that you got
Maybe you’ll do fine
As long as you don’t lie to me
And pretend to be what you’re not
Don’t play the stupid game
Cause I’m a different kind of girl
Every record sounds the same
You’ve got to step into my world
Give me all your love and give me your love
Give me all your love today
Let’s forget about time
And dance our lives away
L-U-V Madonna
Y-O-U You wanna
Keep trying don’t give up, it’s if you want it bad enough
L-U-V Madonna
It’s right in front of you, now tell me what you’re thinking of
Y-O-U You wanna
In another place, at a different time
You can be my lucky star
We can drink some wine
Burgundy is fine
Let’s drink the bottle every drop
Don’t play the stupid game
Cause I’m a different kind of girl
Every record sounds the same
You’ve got to step into my world
Give me all your love and give me your love
Give me all your love today
Let’s forget about time
And dance our lives away
Give me all your love
Give me all your love boy
You can be my boy, you can be my boy toy
In the nick of time, I can say a sicker rhyme
Cause it’s time for change, like a nickel or a dime
I’m roman, i’m a barbarian, i’m conan
You was sleeping on me, you were dosin’
Now move, im goin’ in
You have all the L-U-V
I gave you everything you need (now moooove!)
Now it’s up to Y-O-U
Are you the one, shall we proceed?
Me it. Licks. I’m so swag shit
Glad, no one gave you this
It’s super sonic, bionic, uranium hit
So I break ‘em off tricks
Let’s pray that it sticks
I’mma say this once, yeah, I don’t give a shit
Don’t play the stupid game
Cause I’m a different kind of girl
Every record sounds the same
You’ve got to step into my world
Give me all your love and give me your love
L-U-V Madonna (give me all your love)
Y-O-U You Wanna
Give me all your love and give me your love
Give me all your love today
Let’s forget about time
And dance our lives away