JYP and The Wonder Girls are back
Watching
Cause you got me patiently waiting
I think you are amazing baby It's okay
You're worth the wait
But I just can't take no more
Dreamin
Of you every night and I'm praying
Will you hold me tight and just wrap those arms
Around me boy
I really wanna feel you in my soul
Every time you look in my eyes
I can feel that ya just wanna say
Three little words it's not so impossible
then you start walking away
I can't help it I'm askin the question
I guess there's no other way
For you to just tell-me-right-now
So maybe I should say it out loud
Please Be My Baby
No I don't wanna wonder any more boy
I gotta hear you say the words say the words
Make me your lady
Cause I'm going crazy
I want you and I want the world to know that
I'm your baby and I know you feel the same
Talking
Do you hear a word that I'm saying?
I'm so tired of playing these games with you
I'm so confused
So will you be my baby
Losing
My mind while you over there choosing
I don't wanna ruin this thing we got
Like it or not
Who's baby are you wanting to be?
I can't help it I'm askin the question
I guess there's no other way
For you to just tell-me-right-now
So maybe I should say it out loud~
Please Be My Baby
No I don't wanna wonder any more boy
I gotta hear you say the words say the words
Make me your lady
Cause I‘m going crazy
I want you and I want the world to know that
I'm your baby and I know you feel the same
I can't help it when I want it gotta get it
and it's you I want
Maybe it can happen if you let it baby
Cuz I got you on my mind all the time
And when I see you boy you're looking fine every time
If you would make me the only one in your life
then I'd be like "Sweet"
And mix a little sugar with the spice
Baby take a change, romance, roll the dice
What other girl's gonna ask you something this nice?
Please Be My Baby
No I don't wanna wonder any more boy
I gotta hear you say the words say the words
Make me your lady
Cause I‘m going crazy
I want you and I want the world to know that
I'm your baby and I know you feel the same