I remember tears  streaming down your face
When I said, I’ll never let you go
When all those shadows  almost killed your light
I remember you said,  "Don’t leave me here alone"
But all that’s dead and gone  and passed tonight
Just close your eyes
The sun is going down
You’ll be alright
No one can hurt you now
Come morning light
You and I’ll be safe and sound
Don’t you dare look out  your window darling
Everything’s on fire
The war outside our door  keeps raging on
Hold onto this lullaby
Even when music’s gone
Gone
Just close your eyes
The sun is going down
You’ll be alright
No one can hurt you now
Come morning light
You and I’ll be safe and sound
Just close your eyes
You’ll be alright
Come morning light,
You and I’ll be safe and sound…