Turn up the music, cause this song just came on
Turn up the music, if they try to turn us down
Turn up the music, can I hear it til the speakers blow
Turn up the music, fill your cup and drink it down
If you’re sexy and you know it put your hands up in the air
Put your hands up in the air, girl, put your hands up
Turn up the music, just turn it up loud
Turn up the music, I need it in my life, yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Turn up the music
Tu-turn up the...
Turn up the music cause the sun just came up
Turn up the music, if they try to turn us down
Turn up the music, cause i'm trying to hear the speakers blow
Turn up the music, fill your cup and drink it down
If you’re sexy and you know it put your hands up in the air
Put your hands up in the air, girl, put your hands up
And Turn up the music, just turn it up loud
Turn up the music, I need it in my life, yeah
Turn up the music, just turn it up loud
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Turn up the music
Save my life, all I wanna do is party
So dj turn it up
Girl, dance with me, just dance with me
Girl can I see that, I really wanna touch that
Maybe can I beat that (don't stop the)
Turn it up (just dance with me)
Turn it up
Turn up the music, just turn it up loud
Turn up the music, I need it in my life, yeah
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Can you turn it up, girl
Can you turn it up, baby
Turn it up (just dance with me)
Turn it up
Turn up the music