We Owned The Night
Lady Antebellum
Written:Charles Kelley/Hillary Scott
Dave Haywood/Dallas Davidson
Tell me have you ever wanted
Someone so much it hurts?
Your lips keep trying to speak
But you just can't find the words
Well I had this dream once;
I held it in my hands
She was the purest beauty
But not the common kind
She had a way about her
That made you feel alive
And for a moment
You made the world stand still
Yeah we owned the night
You had me dim the lights;
You danced just like a child
The wine spilled on your dress
And all you did was smile
Yeah, it was perfect
I hold it in my mind
Yeah, we owned the night
When the summer rolls around
And the sun starts sinking down
I still remember you
Oh, I remember you
And I wonder where you are
Are you looking at those same stars again?
Do you remember when?
We woke under a blanket
All tangled up in skin
Not knowing in that moment
We'd never speak again
But it was perfect;
I never will forget
When we owned the night
Yeah, we owned the night