I traveled a long long way
Looking for something unknown
Now you're standing right there
through your smile I've found my way back home
Right in your arms
I feel strong
I feel free and I feel inspired
No matter how the world is turning
I know with you I know I will be fine
And I love
The way that you look at me
Your eyes they tell me everything
You're the only one for me
I love The way that you care for me
Your kiss your touch your gentleness
Puts me in a fantasy
The way you look at me
You melt my heart
The way that you look at me
I know I loved you from the very start
Uh oh Yeah eh oh oh yeah
I loved you from the very start
If you're no longer here
Best believe I'll smile althrough my tears
You touch I'll miss you kiss I'll need
It's not the same unless you're here
Another summer passes
Winter's here and nothing's changed
The way you look at me
Will always remain
And I love
The way that you look at me
Your eyes they tell me everything
You're the only one for me
I love the way that you care for me
Your touch your kiss your gentleness
Puts me in a fantasy
The way you look at me
You melt my heart
The way that you look at me
I know I loved you from the very start
Uh oh Yeah eh oh oh yeah
I loved you from the very start
Baby I know you are hurting
And I am to
Your touch I'll miss
It's you, It's YOU
And I love
The way that you look at me
Your eyes they tell me everything
You're the only one for me
I love the way that you care for me
Your touch your kiss your gentleness
Puts me in a fantasy