Oh, her eyes, her eyes
Make the stars look like they're not shining
Her hair,
Falls perfectly without her trying
She's so beautiful
And I tell her every day
Yeah, I know, I know
When I compliment her she won't believe me
And its so, it's so
Sad to think she don't see what I see
But every time she asks me do I look okay
I say
When I see your face
There's not a thing that I would change
Cause you're amazing just the way you are
And when you smile,
The whole world stops and stares for awhile
Cause girl you're amazing just the way you are
Her lips, her lips
I could kiss them all day if she'd let me
Her laugh, her laugh
She hates but I think its so sexy
She's so beautiful
And I tell her every day
Oh, you know, you know,
I'd never ask you to change
If perfect is what you're searching for
Then just stay the same
So don't even bother asking if you look okay
You know I'll say
When I see your face
There's not a thing that I would change
Cause you're amazing just the way you are
And when you smile,
The whole world stops and stares for awhile
Cause girl you're amazing just the way you are
The way you are,
Girl you're amazing just the way you are
When I see your face
There's not a thing that I would change
Cause you're amazing just the way you are
And when you smile,
The whole world stops and stares for awhile
Cause girl you're amazing just the way you are