Sorry For Party Rocking
Yooo
'll be up in party looking for a hottie to bone
I got a drink in my hand buffalo buffalo
Poppin bottles in the house with models in the V.I.P
All the girls make out for the whole damn club to see
Let's go
People always say that my music's loud
Sorry For Party Rocking
Neighbours complain saying turn it down!
Haters don't like we got the spotlight
Sorry For Party Rocking
When they talk shit, we just pick a line
Baby baby baby I'm awfully crazy
I'm so rocked of patrone shit what ever is tasty
We don't got no manners hanging of the rafters
Lets go drink for drink a hundred bucks she on the lasters
Check my style take a good look
I'm fresh bitch in my way with music so loud I'm deaf bitch
Getting drinks at a redlight with people watching
Sorry For Party Rocking
If you show up already tow up this is what you say
And if you blacked out with you're sack out
This is what you say
Sorry For Party Rocking
And if you throw up in a hoes cup this is what you say
And if she has a hizzefizz cause you whiskeydick
This is what you say
Sorry For Party Rocking
Oh oh oh oh
I'm here for when ever the club sippin buzz
really drunk and I see a fat booty
Got to have it I'm a grab it
Cause its a habbit automatic like uzi
Uzi with the sick flow
Make a chick go crazy and plastered tatta
It's redfoo the dude a true party rockaaaah
I'm true to the game to this is called beerpong
And I can't lose I got some bad bitches in the back
With some vodka on tap and a bit of little of gray goose
Oh of yeah we killin shit with our money
We deal legit so here is a sorry in advance
No hard feelings bitch
Sorry For Party Rocking
People always say that my music's loud
Neighbours complain saying turn it down!
Sorry For Party Rocking
Haters don't like we got the spotlight
When they talk shit, we just pick a line
Sorry For Party Rocking