Ay bay it won't end, won't end, won't end
Let´s talk about love
This is my love story
Boy meets girl and looks in her eyes
Time stands still and two hearts catch fire
Off they go rollercoaster ride
Up & down and around...
Twisted all out they minds
And then his friends
Said "its too soon to settle down"
And then her friends
Said "he's a playa, slow it down"
They couldn't be who they was
Cause it just seemed like love
Wasn't on they side
But this isn't ...
Just another love story
Together we'll make history
I know because it's just too real
They'll be no end to our love story
And this ain't gon end up
Like that Casablanca movie...no
This ain't no fairy tale or fiction
This is truly
Ours for the eternity
They'll be no end to our love story
Baby...
Chapter two...
When they meet up again
Second time around
See but they're just friends
But the feelings still strong
And it's been too long
To be trippin' like they ain't been missing
They on the phone like
Ay bay bay
Let's meet up today
Gots bout an hour or two
You might as well come thru
We can make it like it was
Just the two of us
Back up on that rollercoaster
Like we been supposed to
Cause this isn't
Just another love story
Together we'll make history
I know because it's destiny
They'll be no end to our love story
And this ain't gon end up
Like that Casablanca movie...no
This ain't no fairy tale or fiction
This is truly
Ours for the eternity
They'll be no end to our love story
Baby...
Just when it seemed
Like all the odds
Were stacked against them
They came back stronger then before
Matter fact then some
Stronger then pride
Lookin' like them
Lookin' like her, lookin' like him
Stronger then hate
And the whole world too
Lookin' like me
Lookin' like you
Cause this isn't just another love story
Together we'll make history
I know because it's destiny
They'll be no end to our love story
And this ain't gon end up
Like that Casablanca movie...no
This ain't no fairy tale or fiction
This is truly
Ours for the eternity
They'll be no end to our love story
Baby...
Ay bay bay it won't end, won't end, won't end