Well I couldn't tell you why she felt that way
She felt it every day
And I couldn't help her
I just watched her make the same mistakes again
What's wrong, what’s wrong now?
Too many, too many problems
Don't know where she belongs,
where she belongs
She wants to go home, but nobody's home
That's where she lies, broken inside
With no place to go, no place to go,
to dry her eyes
Broken inside
Open your eyes and look outside,
find the reasons why
You've been rejected, and now you can't
find what you've left behind
Be strong, be strong now
Too many, too many problems
Don't know where she belongs,
where she belongs
She wants to go home, but nobody's home
That's where she lies, broken inside
With no place to go, no place to go,
to dry her eyes
Broken inside
Her feelings she hides
Her dreams she can't find
She's losing her mind
She's fallen behind
She can't find her place
She's losing her faith
She's falling from grace
She's all over the place
Yeah
She wants to go home, but nobody's home
That's where she lies, broken inside
With no place to go, no place to go,
to dry her eyes
Broken inside
She's lost inside, lost inside oh oh