You know that I'm a crazy bitch
I do what I want, when I feel like it
All I wanna do is lose control
Oh, oh
But you don't really give a shit
You go with it, go with it, go with it
'Cause you're fuckin' crazy rock n roll
You said hey, what's your name?
It took one look and now we're not the same
Yeah, you said hey, and since that day
You stole my heart and you're the one to blame
Yeah
And that's why I smile. It's been a while
Since every day and everything has felt this right
And now you turn it all around
And suddenly you're all I need
The reason why I smile
Last night I blacked out, I think
What did you, what did you put in my drink?
I remember making out and then
Oh, oh
I woke up with a new tattoo
Your name is on me and my name is on you
I would do it all over again
You said hey, what's your name?
It took one look and now we're not the same
Yeah, you said hey, and since that day
You stole my heart and you're the one to blame
Yeah
And that's why I smile. It's been a while
Since every day and everything has felt this right
And now you turn it all around
And suddenly you're all I need
The reason why I smile
You know that I'm a crazy bitch
I do what I want, when I feel like it
All I wanna do is lose control
You know that I'm a crazy bitch
I do what I want, when I feel like it
All I wanna do is lose control
And that's why I smile. It's been a while
Since every day and everything has felt this right
And now you turn it all around
And suddenly you're all I need
The reason why I smile
The reason