I don't wanna be left
In this war tonight !
Am I alone in this fight?
Is anybody out there?
Don't wanna be left, left in this world behind
Say you'll run to my side
Something 'bout mary, never won a pageant
Never felt pretty, never looked like cameron
Diaz was her last name, always been abandoned
Keep your head up, baby girl this is your anthem
There goes hannah, showin' off her banner
Rocking that crown, make them boys go bananas
When you're insecure about yourself, it's a fact
You can point a finger,but there's three pointing back
I can see her crying out, yeah
Is there anybody out there?
She's really counting on your love, still struggling uphill,
But you act like you don't care
Right now she could really use a shoulder
Hanging onto the edge til it's over
She's crying for your love tonight
Loneliest heart to survive, she said
I don't wanna be left
In this war tonight
Am I alone in this fight?
Is anybody out there?
Don't wanna be left, left in this world behind
Say you'll run to my side
Is anybody out there? yeah, yeah, yeah
Is anybody out there?
(somebody, anybody)
His name was adam, when his mom had him
Dad was a phantom never took a look at him
Grew up mad and antisocial
Hated outdoors, always in playing madden
Adam was lonely, drugs were the only
Way out of his own life, now he's slowly
losing his fire, close to retire
With one last hope he puts his arms up higher
I can see him crying out, yeah
Is there anybody out there?
He's really counting on your love
Still struggling uphill
But you act like you don't care
Right now he could really use a shoulder
Hanging onto the edge til it's over
He's crying for your love tonight
Loneliest heart to survive, he said
I don't wanna be left
In this war tonight
Am I alone in this fight?
Is anybody out there?
Don't wanna be left, left in this world behind
Say you'll run to my side
Is anybody out there?
If you feel the way I feel
Like you've been talking to yourself
Well this one's for everyone who's felt invisible
Lonely in a crowded room
Searching for someone like you
Can't do it all alone (no one can baby)
Can't do it all alone (no one should baby)
Is anybody out there?
(somebody, anybody)
(I'm right here for you)
Is anybody out there?
I don't wanna be left
In this war tonight
Am I alone in this fight?
Is anybody out there?
Don't wanna be left left in this world behind
Say you'll run to my side
Is anybody out there? yeah, yeah, yeah
(I don't wanna do it all alone)
I don't wanna do it all alone
(I need your love to take me home)
I need your love to take me home
(No one said you should be all alone)
No one said you should be all alone
(I'm right here, right here)
Is anybody out there?