(I love you)
It's been said and done
Every beautiful thought's been already sung
And I guess right now, here's another one
So your melody will play on and on
With the best of' em
You're beautiful
Like a dream come alive, incredible
A centerfold miracle, lyrical
You saved my life again
And i want you to know baby
I, I love you like a love song baby
And I keep hittin' repeat-peat-peat-peat-peat
Constantly
Boy you play through my mind like symphony
There's no way to describe what you do to me
You Just do to me what you do
And it feels like i've been rescued
I've been set free
I'm hypnotized by your destiny
You're magical, lyrical, beautiful
You are
And I want you to know baby
I, I love you like a love song baby
And I keep hittin' repeat-peat-peat-peat-peat
No one compares
You stand alone
To every record I own
Music to my heart
That's what you're
A song that goes on and on
I, I love you like a love song baby
And I keep hittin' repeat-peat-peat-peat-peat
I love you, like a love song