I hope you hang yourself
with your h&m scarf
While jacking off
listening to mozart
You bitch and
moan about LA
Wishing you were in the rain
reading hemingway
You don't eat meat
And drive electrical cars
You're so indie rock
it's almost an art
You need SPF 45
just to stay alive
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No you don't even
like boys
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No you don't even like...
You're so sad maybe
you should buy a happy meal
You're so skinny
you should super size the deal
Secretly you're so amused
That nobody understands you
I'm so mean cause
I can not get your outta your head
I'm so angry
cause you rather myspace instead
I can't believe
I fell in love
With someone that wears
more makeup than...
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No you don't even
like boys
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No you don't even like...
You're so gay
You walk around like
you're oh so debonair
You pull em down
and there's really nothing there
I wish you would
just be real with me
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No you don't even
like boys
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No, no,
no, no
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No you don't even
like boys
You're so gay
and you don't even like boys
No you don't even like
No you don't even
like... pênis!