You gotta help me out
It's all a blur last night
We need a taxi
'Cause you're hung over and I'm broke
I lost my fake ID
But you lost the motel key
Spare me your freaking dirty looks
Now don't blame me
You wanna cash out
And get the hell outta town
Don't be a baby
Remember what you told me
Shut up and put your money where your mouth is
That's what you get for waking up in Vegas
Get up and shake the glitter off your clothes now
Why are these lights so bright?
Did we get hitched last night?
Dressed up like Elvis
Why am I wearing your class ring?

Don't call your mother
'Cause now we're partners in crime
Don't be a baby
Remember what you told me
Shut up and put your money where your mouth is
That's what you get for waking up in Vegas
Get up and shake the glitter off your clothes now
You got me into this
Information overload, situation lost control
Send out an S.O.S.
Ha, and get some cash out
We're gonna tear up the town
No, don't be a baby
Remember what you told me
Told me, told me
Shut up and put your money where your mouth is
That's what you get for waking up in Vegas
Get up and shake the glitter off your clothes now
That's what you get, baby
Shake the glitter
Shake, shake, shake the glitter
Gimme some cash out, baby