Nice legs, Daisy Dukes makes a man go
That's the way they all come through like
Low cut, see through shirts that make ya
That's the way she come through like
'Cause I just set them up, just set them up
Just set them up to knock them down
I think I should know
How to make love to something innocent
Without leaving my fingerprints out
Now, L O V E is just another word
I never learned to pronounce
How do I say I'm sorry
'Cause the word is just never gonna come out
Now, L O V E is just another word
I never learned to pronounce
Tight jeans, double D's makin' me go
All the people on the street know
Iced out, lit up make the kids go
'Cause I just set them up, just set them up
Just set them up to knock them down
I think I should know
How to make love to something innocent
Without leaving my fingerprints out
Now, L O V E is just another word
I never learned to pronounce
How do I say I'm sorry
'Cause the word is just never gonna come out
Now, L O V E is just another word
I never learned to pronounce
You know that type of shit just don`t work on me
whistle and trying to flirt with me
Don`t take it personally
Cause we were never in love
It doesn`t really matter, who you say you are
Sing it out the windows, of your car
Find another girl across the bar
Cause L-O-V-E`s not what this was
I think I should know
How to make love to something innocent
Without leaving my fingerprints out
Now, L O V E is just another word
I never learned to pronounce
How do I say I'm sorry
'Cause the word is just never gonna come out
Now, L O V E is just another word
I never learned to pronounce