I probably shouldn't say this
But at times I get so scared
When I think about the previous
Relationship we've shared
It was awesome but we lost it
It's not possible for me not to care
Now we're standing in the rain
But nothing's ever gonna change
Until you hear, my dear
The 7 things I hate about you
Oh you
You're vain, your games, you're insecure
You love me, you like her
You make me laugh, you make me cry
I don't know which side to buy
Your friends they're jerks
And when you act like them, just know it hurts
I wanna be with the one I know
And the 7th thing I hate the most that you do
You make me love you
It's awkward and it's silent
As I wait for you to say
What I need to hear now
Your sincere apology
And when yuu mean it, I'll believe it
If you text it, I'll delete it
Let's be clear
Oh I'm not coming back
You're taking 7 steps here
The 7 things I hate about you
You're vain, your games, you're insecure
You love me, you like her
You make me laugh, you make me cry
I don't know which side to buy
Your friends they're jerks
And when you act like them, just know it hurts
I wanna be with the one I know
And the 7th thing I hate the most that you do
You make me love you
And compared to all the great things
That would take too long to write
I probably should mention
The 7 that I like
The 7 things I like about you
Your hair, your eyes, you old Levi's
And when we kiss, I'm hypnotized
You make me laugh, you make me cry
But I guess that's both I'll have to buy
Your hand in mine
When we're intertwined everything's alright
I wanna be with the one I know
And the 7th thing I like the most that you do ooh
You make me love you