Bye guys!
See ya!
What did you think?
I was actually really surprised I really liked it.
- Me too.
- Did you?
Yea, I loved it.
Thank you so much.
Are you OK?
Miley, come here. Just want a couple of shots.
Come on, just a couple...come back here. Come here!
You don't understand
what it is
That makes me tick
But you wish
you did
You always second guess,
wonder if
I say yes,
but you just lose out every time
If you only knew
what I talked about
When I'm with my friends
just hangin' out
Then you'd have
the inside scoop
On what to say,
what to do
That way
when you play the game
Maybe you could
never lose
Don't you wish that
you could be a Fly on the Wall?
A creepy little sneaky
little Fly on the Wall
All my precious secrets,
yeah
You'd know them all
Don't you wish that
you could be a Fly on the Wall?
You'd love to know,
the things I do
When I'm with my friends,
and not with you
You always second guess,
wonder if
There's others guys
I'm flirting with
You should know
by now
If you were my boyfriend,
I'd be true to you
If I make a promise,
I'm comin' thru
Don't you wish that you could
See me every second of the day
That way you would
have no doubt
That baby
I'll never stray
Don't you wish that
you could be a Fly on the Wall?
A creepy little sneaky
little Fly on the Wall
All my precious secrets,
yeah
You'd know them all
Don't you wish that
you could be a Fly on the Wall?
A little communication
Well that'll
go a long way
You're getting
misinformation
Too much hearsay,
hearsay
And what I say is
Come a little closer
And what
I'm gonna say is
Don't cha
Don't you wish you were a
Hey!
Don't you wish that
you could be a Fly on the Wall?
A creepy little sneaky
little Fly on the Wall
All my precious secrets,
yeah
You'd know them all
Don't you wish that
you could be a Fly on the Wall?
You would not believe this craziest thing happened.
All these paparazzis and they would not quit chasing me.
They were dancing and I'm not sure why, but they were.
And it was absolutely amazing but still really weird.
And they kept coming after me and
I really could not escape from them.
Every time one thing I did, they would multiply.
And it was so shrieked I just could not escape.
I was out in the ceilings.
I was everywhere and I could not get away from these guys.
It was insane.