I got my sight set on you
And I'm ready to wait
I have a heart that will
Never be tamed
I knew you were something special
When you spoke my name
Now I can't wait
To see you again
I've got a way of knowing
When something is right
I feel like I must have known you
In another life
'Cause I felt this deep connection
When you looked in my eyes
(I can't wait)
Now I can't wait
To see you again
The last time I freaked out
I just kept looking down
I st-st-stuttered
When you asked me
What I'm thinkin' 'bout
Felt like I couldn't breathe
You asked what's wrong with me
My best friend Leslie said
"Oh she's just being Miley"
The next time we hang out
I will redeem myself
My heart it can't rest till then
Woh oh I,
I can't wait
To see you again
I got this crazy feeling
Deep inside
When you called
And asked to see me
Tomorrow night
I'm not a mind reader
But I'm reading the signs
(That you can't wait)
That you can't wait
To see me again
The last time I freaked out
I just kept looking down
I st-st-stuttered
When you asked me
What I'm thinkin' 'bout
Felt like I couldn't breathe
You asked what's wrong with me
My best friend Leslie said
"Oh she's just being Miley"
The next time we hang out
I will redeem myself
My heart can't rest till then
Wohoh oh I,
I can't wait to see you again
I got my sight set on you
And I'm ready to wait
The last time I freaked out
I just kept looking down
I st-st-stuttered
When you asked me
What I'm thinkin' 'bout
Felt like I couldn't breathe
You asked what's wrong with me
My best friend Leslie said
"Oh she's just being Miley"
The next time we hang out
I will redeem myself
My heart it can't rest till then
Woh oh I,
I can't wait to see you again
(To see you again)
Woh oh I,
I can't wait
To see you again