I can almost see it that dream I am dreaming
But there's a voice inside my head saying: "You'll never reach it"
Every step I'm taking, every move I make feels
Lost with no direction, my faith is shaking
But I gotta keep trying
Gotta keep my head held high
There's always gonna be another mountain
I'm always gonna wanna make it move
Always gonna be an uphill battle
Sometimes I'm gonna have to lose
Ain't about how fast I get there
Ain't about what's waiting on the other side
It`s the climb
The struggles I'm facing
the chances I'm taking
Sometimes might knock me down, but no, I'm not breaking
I may not know it
but these are the moments that
I'm gonna remember most yeah
just gotta keep going
And I, I gotta be strong
Just keep pushing on 'cause
There's always gonna be another mountain
I'm always gonna wanna make it move
Always gonna be a uphill battle
Sometimes I'm gonna have to lose
Ain't about how fast I get there
Ain't about what's waiting on the other side
It's the climb
There's always gonna be another mountain
I'm always gonna wanna make it move
Always gonna be an uphill battle
Sometimes You're gonna have to lose
Ain't about how fast I get there
Ain't about what's waiting on the other side
It's the climb
Keep on moving
keep climbing
Keep the faith, baby
It's all about, it's all about the climb
Keep the faith, keep your faith