everybody needs inspiration
everybody needs a song
a beautiful melody
when the nights so long
cause there is no guarantee
that this life is easy
yea when my world is falling apart
when there's no light to break up the dark
that's when I,I...
I look at you
when the waves
are flooding the shore and i cant
find my way home anymore
that's when I,I...
I look at you
when i look at you i see forgiveness
i see the truth
you love me for who i am
like the stars hold the moon
right there where they belong
and i know i'm not alone
yea when my world is falling apart
when there's no light to break up the dark
that's when I,I...
I look at you
when the waves
are flooding the shore and i cant
find my way home anymore
that's when I,I...
I look at you
you appear just like a dream to me
just like kaleidoskope colors that cover me
all i need every breath i breathe
dont you know
you're beautiful
yea yea yea
when the waves are flooding the shore and i cant
find my way home anymore
that's when I,I...
I look at you
Yea Yea oh oh oh
and you appear
just like a dream to me