So, tonight is officially the last show of the Black Star Tour.
And after tonight’s show, it’ll be a complete
wrap on “Goodbye Lullaby”,
this album cycle, and the Black Star Tour,
which I’ve been I’ve been out on the road now for a year.
And it’s been awesome, the shows’ve been amazing.
My fans, you guys have been incredible.
So, thank you for taking the time to listen to it,
to buy my songs, to buy my albums,
and to come out to the shows,
to buy tickets to come hear me sing, it means so much.
So, umm I decided to shoot a little
video for my song “Goodbye”,
umm with my friend Mark Lidell
at the Chateau Marmont in Los Angeles.
And, I just wanted this to be something
to give to you guys,
to say thank you and to complete this album cycle,
umm while I’m here completing the last show of the tour.
So, goodbye, and thank you so much, and I love you guys.
And I hope that you like this video.
And goodbye, little black stars, I’m going to sleep.
Actually, I can’t, I have a concert. One more show.
So, you can check out the video for “Goodbye”
by clicking on the link below
and there’s also another option to click on the other link
and you can donate to the Avril Lavigne Foundation.
Goodbye
Goodbye, my love
I can’t hide
Can’t hide
Can’t hide what has come.
I have to go, I have to go, I have to go
And leave you alone
But always know, always know, always know
That I love you so
I love you so
Oh
Goodbye, brown eyes
Goodbye for now
Goodbye, sunshine
Take care of yourself
I have to go, I have to go, I have to go
And leave you alone
But always know, always know, always know
That I love you so, I love you so, oh.
I love you so.
Oh.
La lullaby. Distract me with your eyes.
La lullaby. la lullaby. Help me sleep tonight.
La lullaby (la lullaby, la lullaby)
I have to go
And leave you alone
But always know, always know, always know
That I love you so
I love you so
(Goodbye)
(Lullaby)
I love you so
(Goodbye)
(Lullaby)
I love you so
(Goodbye)
(Lullaby)
I love you so
(Goodbye)
Goodbye, brown eyes
Goodbye my love