Hey hey, you you, I don't like your girlfriend
No way, no way, I think you need a new one
Hey hey, you you, I could be your girlfriend
Hey hey, you you, I know that you like me
No way, no way, you know it's not a secret
Hey hey, you you, I want to be your girlfriend
You're so fine, I want you mine,
you're so delicious
I think about you all the time,
you're so addictive
Don't you know what I can do
to make you feel alright?
Don't pretend, I think you know
I'm damn precious
And hell yeah
I'm the mother fucking princess
I can tell you like me too
and you know I'm right
She's like so whatever
You can do so much better
I think we should get together now
And that's what everyone's talking about
Hey hey, you you, I don't like your girlfriend
No way, no way, I think you need a new one
Hey hey, you you, I could be your girlfriend
Hey hey, you you, I know that you like me
No way, no way, you know it's not a secret
Hey hey, you you,
I want to be your girlfriend
I can see the way,
I see the way you look at me
And even when you look away
I know you think of me
I know you talk about me
all the time again and again
So come over here and tell me
what I wanna hear
Better yet, make your girlfriend disappear
I don't wanna hear you say
her name ever again
Cause she's like so whatever
And you can do so much better
I think we should get together now
And that's what everyone's talking about
Hey hey, you you, I don't like your girlfriend
No way, no way, I think you need a new one
Hey hey, you you, I could be your girlfriend
Hey hey, you you, I know that you like me
No way, no way, you know it's not a secret
Hey hey, you you,
I want to be your girlfriend
In a second you'll be wrapped
around my finger
Cause I can, ?cause I can do it better
There's no other, so when's it
gonna sink in?
She's so stupid, what the hell
were you thinking?
In a second you'll be wrapped
around my finger
Cause I can, ?cause I can do it better
There's no other, so when's it
gonna sink in?
She's so stupid, what the hell
were you thinking?
Hey hey, you you, I don't like your girlfriend
No way, no way, I think you need a new one
Hey hey, you you, I could be your girlfriend
(No way, no way)
Hey hey, you you, I know that you like me
No way, no way, you know it's not a secret
Hey hey, you you,
I want to be your girlfriend
(No way, no way)
Hey hey, you you, I don't like your girlfriend
No way, no way, I think you need a new one
Hey hey, you you, I could be your girlfriend
(No way, no way)
Hey hey, you you, I know that you like me
No way, no way, you know it's not a secret
Hey hey, you you,
I want to be your girlfriend
(No way, no way)