Oh dang
What is it dawg?
I forgot it's Mothers Day
Didn't get a gift for her
Other plans got in the way. She'll be so disappointed.
Damn I forgot it too
This could have been avoided
What the hell are we gonna do?
My moms been so alone ever since my daddy left
cold
No one to hold her tight. Life has put her to the test
I know just what you mean,
my moms been so sad and gray
Word
My dad can't satisfy her in the
bedroom ever since he passed away
Hold up!
You thinkin what I'm thinkin?
I'm thinkin I'm thinkin too.
Slow up!
What time is it dawg?
It's time for a switcharoo
We both love our moms, women with grown women needs
I say we break em off
Show em how much they really mean
Cause...
I'm a Mother Lover
You're a Mother Lover
We should fuck each others mothers
Fuck each others moms
I'm pushin that lady where you came out as a baby
Ain't no doubt that shit is crazy
Fuckin' each others moms
Cause every Mothers Day needs a Mothers Night
If doing it is wrong, I don't wanna be right
I'm callin on you cause I can't do it myself
To me you're like a brother, so be my mother lover
I'm layin in the cut waitin' for your mom
clutchin' on this lube and roses
I got my digital camera, I'm gonna make
your momma do a million poses
They will be so surprised
We are so cool and thoughtful
Can't wait to pork your mom
I'm gonna be the syrup, she can be my waffle
Sho nuff!
My mother loves bubble bath with chamomile
Straight up!
Give it to my mom d - d- d - d- d - d - doggystyle
This the perfect plan
For a perfect Mothers Day
They have to rename this one
All up under the covers day
Cause...
I'm a Mother Lover
You're a Mother Lover
We should fuck each others mothers
Fuck each others moms
I'm pushin that lady where you came out as a baby
Ain't no doubt that shit is crazy
Fuckin' each others moms
Break it down
It would be my honor to be your new step-father
While your in my mother make me another brother.
And I'm in your mother I'll never use a rubber
Cause every Mothers Day needs a Mothers Night
If doing it is wrong, I don't wanna be right
I'm callin on you cause I can't do it myself
To me you're like a brother, so be my mother lover
They blessed us both with the gift of life
She brought you in this world so I'm a sex her right
This is the second best idea that we've ever had
The choice can be no other
Be my mother lover
Happy Mother's Day