Yeah
Backin' that ass
Your mom says "Hi" — Jinx!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Summertime in the city
And everybody's having sex
You know I just got a page from a girl
that I met last week at the Pay-less
Shoe stores
I also have a cutie to call who loves
the way I knock on her boots
Well let's help them back
Let's handle that
In two-to-six hours,
We'll meet back here and regroup
Now let's shoop
Roll up to her crib with some Bartles & James
Hop off the bus with the Alizé
Now hold up player, whatchu diggity-doing here?
I should diggity-ask you the same
And she sang
Hey, boys I want you both
I hope that you think that's cool
(Say word?)
I know most guys won't freak together
She forgot about the golden rule — a huh huh
It's OK to put us in a three-way
It's not gay when it's in a three-way
With a honey in the middle there's some leeway
The area's grey in a one, two, three-way
Normally, I don't get down with dudes
But tonight is a special exception (Great)
See you're my best friend
Through thick and thin
Now it's time to make a triple connection
Lights off
Here in the dark (Here in the dark)
It's so hard to tell (So hard to tell)
Where her body ends (La la)
And my homie's begins (Ew wee)
This rule dates back (The Golden Rule)
To ancient Greece (Takin' about Cesar)
We're two Jack Trippers and a Chrissy
The new Three's Company
You Guys Still Here ?
It's OK to put us in a three-way
It's not gay when it's in a three-way
With a honey in the middle there's some leeway
The area's grey in a one, two, three-way
Fellas. Get ready.
Doin' us a chick
Helicopter dick, go!
Helicopter dick
Doin' us a chick
Well
And all of that was OK
Cause it was in a three-way
It's quite clear when you see the instant replay (boom)
Maybe two is enough
That's what they'll say
But we'll say, "Hell no! "
One, two, three-way
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
The golden rule