Ay, Let me kick it
to you right quick, partner
Not as a ganster,
but as a grown man
What matters more than
the mistakes you've made
Is what you able
to learn from it.
Big Phil
This for you pimpin'
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone,
dead and gone
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone,
dead and gone
Ever had one of dem days wish
woulda stayed home
Run into a group of suckas
who gettin' they hate on
You walk by
They get wrong
You reply then
things get blown
Way outta proportion
Way past discussion
Just you against them,
pick one then rush 'em
Figure you'll get dropped,
hell that's nuthin'
They don't wanna stop
there now they bussin'
Now you gushin',
ambulance rushin'
You to the hospital
with a bad concussion
Plus ya hit 4 times
Plus it hit ya spine
Paralyzed waist down
now ya wheel chair bound
Nevermind that now
you lucky to be alive
Just think it all started
you fussin' with 3 guys
Now ya pride in the way,
but ya pride is the way
You could mess around,
get shot, die anyday
People die everyday
All over nonsense, dirty money, dice
game, stash box contents
Could this be 'cos
of hip hop music?
Or did the ones with
the good sense not use it?
Usually people don't know
what to do
when their back against the wall so
they just start shootin'
For red or for blue
or for blo I guess
From Bankhead or
from your projects
No more stress, now I'm straight,
now I get it, now I take
Time to think,
before I make mistakes
just for my family's sake
That part of me
left yesterday
The heart of me
is strong today
No regrets
I'm blessed to say
The old me
dead and gone away
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone
dead and gone
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone
dead and gone
I ain't never been scared,
l lived through tragedy
Situation coulda been
dead lookin' back at it
Most of that stuff
didn't even have to happen
But you don't think about it
when you out there trappin'
In apartments, hangin',
smokin', and rappin'
Suckas start something,
next thing ya know we cappin'
Get locked up then
didn't even get mad
Now think about damn
what a life I had
Most of that stuff,
look back, just laugh
Some shit still
look back get sad
Maybe my homeboy
still be around
Had I not hit the sucka
in the mouth that time
I won that fight
l lost that war
I can still see my homie
walkin' out that door
Who'da thought
I'd never see Philant no more?
Got enough dead homies
l don't want no more
Cost a sucka his job
Cost me more
Should walked of and
take that loss for sure
Now think before
l risk my life
Take them chances
to get my stripe
Somebody put his hands
on me alright
Otherwise stand there
talk shit all night
'Cos I hit you,
you sue me,
I shoot you, get locked up,
who me?
No more stress, now I'm straight,
now I get it, now I take
Time to think,
before I make mistakes
just for my family's sake
That part of me
left yesterday
The heart of me
is strong today
No regrets
I'm blessed to say
The old me
dead and gone away
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone,
dead and gone
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone,
dead and gone
I turn my head to the East
l don't see nobody by my side
I turn my head to the West
Still nobody in sight
So I turn my head
to the North
Swallow that pill
that they call pride
That old me
is dead and gone
But that new me
will be alright
I turn my head to the East
l don't see nobody by my side
I turn my head to the West
Still nobody in sight
So I turn my head
to the North
Swallow that pill
that they call pride
That old me is
dead and gone
But that new me
will be alright cause
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone,
dead and gone
I've been travellin' on
this road too long
Just tryna find
my way back home
The old me is dead and gone,
dead and gone, dead...