I've never seen you before. You work at the club?
Leave me alone, I'm with someone
- Really?
- Yeah
- Who?
That guy over there
Look I've never seen you before. You work at the club?
Baby I'm really bored
You're bored?
- Yeah
- Really?
- Yes
- So I'm boring you?
- That's right
-For me
I happen to think I'm a lot of fun
Ok, well, what are you going to do to entertain me?
You like to play? You got a car?
- Let's get out of here
- Let's go
Hey girl, is he everything you wanted in a man
You know I gave you the world
You had me in the palm of your hand
So why your love went away
I just can't seem to understand
Thought it was me and you babe
Me and you until the end
But I guess I was wrong
Don't want to think about it
Don't want to talk about it
I'm just so sick about it
Can't believe it's ending this way
Just so confused about it
Feeling the blues about it
I just can't do without ya
Tell me is this fair?
Is this the way it's really going down?
Is this how we say goodbye?
Should've known better when you came around
That you were gonna make me cry
It's breaking my heart to watch you run around
'Cause I know that you're living a lie
That's okay baby 'cause in time you will find...
What goes around, goes around, goes around
Comes all the way back around
Now girl, I remember everything that you claimed
You said that you were moving on now
And maybe I should do the same
Funny thing about that is
I was ready to give you my name
Thought it was me and you, babe
And now, it's all just a shame
And I guess I was wrong
- So this is her
- This is her
This is the one
The one
Hello
Unless she plays her cards right,
she might even get the keys to the castle
I don't want your keys
Shut up!
You make me shut up
Whoa whoa whoa, slow down, partner
You guys have been what? A month
And you're telling me you're ready to lock it up
and leave all the pretty girls to me?
Maybe
I like girls
Me too
A lot
I like everything
of course you do, of course you do!
Let me tell you something
You're awesome and you're awesome and
you're awesome and you're awesome
- And this deservers a toast, ok?
- OK
Come here, come on
To...
To you, and me.
Don't want to think about it
Don't want to talk about it
I'm just so sick about it
Can't believe it's ending this way
Just so confused about it
Feeling the blues about it
I just can't do without ya
Can you tell me is this fair?
Is this the way things are going down?
Is this how we say goodbye?
Should've known better when you came around
That you were going to make me cry
Now it's breaking my heart to watch you run around
'Cause I know that you're living a lie
That's okay baby 'cause in time you will find
What goes around, goes around, goes around
Comes all the way back around
What goes around comes around
Don't want to think about it (no)
Don't want to talk about it
I'm just so sick about it
Can't believe it's ending this way
Just so confused about it
Feeling the blues about it (yeah)
I just can't do without ya
Tell me is this fair?
What goes around, goes around, goes around
Comes all the way back around
You're my best friend!
What? What? What?
Nothing happended?
Come here, come... ok.
With my friend, huh?
You **** crazy, you don't *** know me.
I *** know you!
Leave me alone!
Get back here!
Open the door! Open the door!
Let me paint this picture for you, baby
You spend your nights alone
And he never comes home
And every time you call him
All you get's a busy tone
I heard you found out
That he's doing to you
What you did to me
Ain't that the way it goes
You cheated girl
My heart bleeds girl
So it goes without saying that you left me feeling hurt
Just a classic case
A scenario
Tale as old as time
Girl you got what you deserved
And now you want somebody
To cure the lonely nights
You wish you had somebody
That could come and make it right
But girl I ain't somebody with a lot of sympathy
You'll see
(What goes around comes back around)
I thought I told ya, hey
See?
You should've listened to me, baby
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Because
(What goes around comes back around)