I keep on fallin' in
And out of love
With you
Sometimes I love ya
Sometimes u make me blue
Sometimes I feel good
At times I feel used
Lovin you darlin'
Makes me so confused
I keep on
Fallin'
In and out of love with you
I never loved someone
The way that I love you
Oh, oh , I never felt this way
How do you give me so much pleasure
And cause me so much pain
Just when I think
Ive taken more than would a fool
I start fallin' back in love with you
I keep on
Fallin'
In and out of love with you
I never loved someone
The way that I love you
Oh baby
Oo, Oo, Oo
I, I, I, I'm fallin'
Fall
I keep on
Fallin'
In and out of love with you
I never loved someone
The way that I love you
Im fallin'
In and out of love with you
I never loved someone
The way that I love you
Im fallin'
In and out of love with you
I never loved someone
The way that I love you
What?