Jai Ho!
I got shivers when you touch my face
I'll make you hot, get all you got
I'll make you wanna say
(Jai Ho! Jai Ho!)
I got fever running like a fire
For you I will go all the way
I'm gonna take you higher
(Jai Ho)
I'll keep it steady, cause steady is how I do it
(Jai ho!)
This beat it heavy, so heavy you're gonna feel it
(Jai Ho!)
You are the reason that I breath
You're the reason that I still believe
(Jai Ho!)
You're are my destiny
Jai ho! Oh, oh, oh, oh
(Jai Ho!)
No, there is nothing that can stop us
Nothing can ever come between us
(Jai Ho!)
So come and dance with me
Jai ho! Oh
Catch me, catch me, catch me
C'mon, catch me, I want you now
I know you can save me
You can save me, I need you now
I am yours forever, yes forever
I will follow
Anyway, and anywhere
Never gonna let go
(Jai Ho!)
Escape away. I'll take you to a place
This fantasy of you and me
I'll never lose the chase
(Jai Ho!)
I can fell you rushing through my veins
There's an ocean in my heart
I will never feel the same
(Jai Ho!)
Just keep it coming, yeah baby, just keep it coming
You're gonna find out, baby, I'm one in a million
(Jai Ho!)
You are the reason that I breath
You re the reason that I still believe
(Jai Ho!)
Your are my destiny
Jai ho! Oh, oh, oh, oh
(Jai Ho!)
No, there is nothing that can stop us
Nothing can ever come between us
(Jai Ho!)
So come and dance with me
Jai ho! Oh
You and me, its destiny
Catch me, catch me, catch me
C'mon, catch me, I want you now
I know you can save me
You can save me, I need you now
I am yours forever, yes forever
I will follow
Anyway, and anywhere
Never gonna let go
(Jai Ho!)
I need you, gonna make it
I'm ready, so take it
(Jai Ho!)
You are the reason that I breath
You re the reason that I still believe
(Jai Ho!)
Your are my destiny
Jai ho! Oh, oh, oh, oh
(Jai Ho!)
No, there is nothing that can stop us
Nothing can ever come between us
(Jai Ho!)
So come and dance with me
Jai ho! Oh
You and me, its destiny
(Jai Ho!)
Baila! Baila!
(Jai Ho! Jai Ho!)