Hey, good girl
With your head in the clouds
I bet you I can tell you
What you're thinkin' about
You'll see a good boy
Gonna give you the world
But he's gonna leave you cryin'
With your heart in the dirt
His lips are dropping honey
But he'll sting you like a bee
So lock up all your loving
Go and throw away the key
Hey good girl
Get out while you can
I know you think you got a good man
Whyyyy, why you gotta be so bliiiind?
Won't you open your eeeyes?
It's just a matter of time 'till you find
He's no good, girl
No good for you
You better get to getting on your goodbye shoes
and go, go, go...
Better listen to me
He's low, low, low...
Hey, good girl
You got a heart of gold
You want a white wedding
And a hand you can hold
Just like you should, girl
Like every good girl does
Want a fairytale ending, somebody to love
But he's really good at lying girl
Yeah, he'll leave you in the dust
'Cause when he says forever
Well, it don't mean much
Hey good girl
So good for him
Better back away honey
You don't know where he's been
Whyyyy, why you gotta be so bliiiind?
Won't you open your eeeyes?
It's just a matter of time 'till you find
He's no good, girl
No good for you
You better get to getting on your goodbye shoes
and go, go, go...
Yeah yeah yeah, he's low
Yeah yeah yeah
He's no good, girl
Why can't you see?
He'll take your heart and break it
Listen to me, yeah
Whyyyy, why you gotta be so bliiiind?
Won't you open your eeeeyes?
It's just a matter of time 'till you find
He's no good, he's no good
Won't you open up your eeeeyes?
It's just a matter of time 'till you find
He's no good, girl
He's no good for you
You better get to getting on your goodbye shoes