All my people
in the crowd
Grab a partner to
take it down!
It's me against the music
It's just me
And me
Yeah,
C'mon
Hey Britney?
Are you ready?
Are you?
And no one cares,
It's whippin' my hair,
it's pullin' my waist
To hell with stares
The sweat is drippin'
all over my face
And no one's there,
I'm the only one
dancin' up in this place
Tonight I'm here
Feel the beat of the drum,
gotta keep it that bass
I'm up against the speaker,
tryin' to take on the music
It's like a competition,
me against the beat
I wanna get in the zone,
If you really wanna battle,
saddle up and get your rhythm
Tryin' to hit it,
you could die in a minute
I'm a take a you on,
All my people on the floor,
let me see you dance
All my people wantin' more,
All my people round and round,
let me see you dance
All my people in the crowd,
I wanna see ya
So how would you like
a friendly competition
Let's take on the song,
It's you and me baby,
we're the music
Time to party
all night long
All night long
Let's go
We're almost there
I'm feelin' it bad
and I can't explain
My soul is bare
My hips are movin'
at a rapid pace
Can you
feel it burn,
From the tip of my toes
runnin' through my veins
And now,
it's your turn
Let me see what you got,
don't hesitate
I'm up against the speaker,
tryin' to take on the music
It's like a competition,
me against the beat
I wanna get in the zone,
If you really wanna battle,
saddle up and get your rhythm
Tryin' to hit it,
you could die in a minute
I'm a take a you on,
All my people on the floor,
let me see you dance
Let me see ya
All my people wantin' more,
let me see you dance
Let me see ya
All my people round and round,
let me see you dance
Let me see ya
All my people in the crowd,
let me see you dance
I wanna see ya
Get on the floor,
baby lose control
Just work your body
and let it go
If you wanna party,
just grab somebody
Hey Britney,
we can dance all night long
You say
you wanna lose control
Come over here,
I got somethin' to show ya
Sexy lady,
I'd rather see you
bare your soul
If you think you're so hot,
better show me what you got
All my people in the crowd,
let me see you dance
C'mon Britney lose control,
watch you take it down
Get on the floor,
baby lose control
Just work your body
and let it go
If you wanna party,
just grab somebody
Hey Britney,
we can dance all night long
All my people on the floor,
let me see you dance
Let me see ya
All my people wantin' more,
let me see you dance
I wanna see ya
All my people round and round,
let me see you dance
Let me see ya
All my people in the crowd,
let me see you dance
I wanna see ya
All my people in the crowd,
let me see you dance
C'mon Britney,
take it down
Make
the music dance
All my people round and round
party all night long
C'mon Britney
lose control,
Watch you
take it down