Ain't this what you came for
Don't you wish you came, oh
Girl what you're playing for
Come on, let me kiss that
Ooh, I know you miss that
What's wrong, let me fix that
Twist that
Baby, tonight's the night I let you know
Baby, tonight's the night we lose control
Baby, tonight you need that, tonight believe that
Tonight I'll be the best you ever had
I don't wanna brag, but I'll be
The best you ever had
I hit you with the best flow,
Freestlying in the restroom
Til you blowing cigarette smoke
And now the bad's gone
So what we gon' do now
* it, round two now
Work it out, then we cool down
Cool down
Baby, tonight's the night I let you know
Baby, tonight's the night we lose control
Baby, tonight you need that, tonight believe that
Tonight I'll be the best you ever had
I don't wanna brag, but I'll be
The best you ever had
Luda, listen...
You ain't even gotta text me
Knowin' me and you got that mental telepathy
Me be up at the spot,
I'll be sending over the chauffeur
Rich nigga bread, stay poppin' like a toaster
Nobody come close to me and you together
Step under my umbrella, we’ll make it through any weather
Except when I make it storm, sex in the greatest form
And hibernate under my body
Yep I keep it warmer than a chinchilla
She know I beat it up like the thriller in Manila
Flying my private jet to villas in Anguilla
Than throw you on a grill
Cause seven days a week you’re my 5 course meal
For real!
Baby, tonight's the night I let you know
Baby, tonight's the night we lose control
Baby, tonight you need that, tonight believe that
Tonight I'll be the best you ever had
I don't wanna brag, but I'll be
The best you ever had