In a time of darkness and greed
It is your light that we need
You came to teach us how to live
Muhmmad, ya Rasoola Allah
You were so caring and kind
Your soul was full of light
You are the best of mankind
Muhammad, khairu khalqi Allah
Sallou ‘ala Rasooli Allah
Habibil Mustafa
Peace be upon the Messenger
The Chosen One
From luxury you turned away
And all night you would pray
Truthful in every word you say
Muhammad, ya Rasoola Allah
Your face was brighter than the sun
Your beauty equalled by none
You are Allah's Chosen One
Muhammad, khayru khalqi Allah
Sallou ‘ala Rasooli Allah
Habibil Mustafa
Peace be upon the Messenger
The Chosen One
I'll try to follow your way
And do my best to live my life
As you taught me
I pray to be close to you
On that day, and see you smile
When you see me
Sallou ‘ala Rasooli Allah
Habibil Mustafa
Peace be upon the Messenger
The Chosen One
Sallou ‘ala Rasooli Allah
Habibil Mustafa
Peace be upon the Messenger
The Chosen One
Sallou ‘ala Rasooli Allah.. Oh
Peace be upon.. Oh
The Chosen One