Every time you feel like you cannot go on
You feel so lost and that you're so alone
All you see is night, and darkness all around
You feel so helpless you can't see which way to go
Don't despair, and never lose hope
‘Cause Allah is always by your side
Insha Allah (God-willing), insha Allah, insha Allah
You'll find your way
Insha Allah, insha Allah, insha Allah
Every time, you commit one more mistake
You feel you can't repent and that it's way too late
You're so confused
Wrong decisions you have made
Haunt your mind and your heart is full shame
But don't despair
And never lose hope
'Cause Allah is always by your side
Insha Allah, insha Allah, insha Allah
You'll find your way
Turn to Allah, He's never far away
Put your trust in Him
Raise your hands and pray
Ooh ya Allah!
Guide my steps, don't let me go astray
You're the only one who can show me the way
Show me the way, show me the way, show me the way
Insha Allah, insha Allah, insha Allah
We'll find our way
Insha Allah, insha Allah, insha Allah..