I praise Allah for sending me you my love
You've found your home it's here with me
And I'm here with you
Now let me let you know
You've opened my heart
I was always thinking that love was wrong
But everything was changed when you came along
Oh,
And there's a couple of words I want to say
For the rest of my life, I'll be with you
I'll stay by your side, honest and true
Till the end of my time
I'll be loving you, loving you
For the rest of my life, through days and nights
I’ll thank Allah for opening my eyes
Now and forever I, I'll be there for you
I know it deep in my heart
I feel so blessed when I think of you
And I ask Allah to bless all we do
You're my wife, and my friend and my strength
And I pray we're together in Jannah
Finally now I've found my self, I feel so strong
Yes everything was changed when you came along
Oh,
And there's a couple of words I want to say
For the rest of my life, I'll be with you
I'll stay by your side, honest and true
Till the end of my time
I'll be loving you, loving you
For the rest of my life, through days and nights
I’ll thank Allah for opening my eyes
Now and forever I, I'll be there for you
I know it deep in my heart
And now that you're here, in front of me
I strongly feel love
And I have no doubt, and I'll sing it loud
And that I will love you eternally
For the rest of my life, I'll be with you
I'll stay by your side, honest and true
Till the end of my time
I'll be loving you, loving you
For the rest of my life, through days and nights
I’ll thank Allah for opening my eyes
Now and forever I, I'll be there for you
I know it deep in my heart