Happy To See You Setting Me Off Like Sparks
You Ignite All The Colours Inside My Heart
On The Doorstep Like We'd Never Been Apart
Hope You Know That I'm Happy To See You
It's Just Another Night
The Boys Are Getting Hype
But Baby In My Head
I'm There With You Instead
It's Just Another Night
Under The Strobe Lights
Can't Hear What I'm Dancing To
Just Wanna Be With You
Ohh, Chest Tight, And I'm Ready To Go
On My Mind I Can't Wait Anymore
Now Happy To See You Setting Me Off Like Sparks
You Ignite All The Colours Inside My Heart
On The Doorstep Like We'd Never Been Apart
Hope You Know That I'm Happy To See You
Them Girls Put On A Show
But They Will Never Know
What Makes You Beautiful
I Watch Them Come And Go
Them Boys Got All The Talk
But They Don't Know A Lot
You Know My Every Thought
That's Why I Make Them Walk
Ohh, Chest Tight, And I'm Ready To Go
On My Mind I Can't Wait Anymore
Happy To See You Setting Me Off Like Sparks
You Ignite All The Colours Inside My Heart
On The Doorstep Like We'd Never Been Apart
Hope You Know That I'm Happy To See You
Nothing Needed To Say
We Got Nothing To Prove
The World Doesn't Matter No When I'm With You
We Got No Games To Play
So We Got No Rules
The World Doesn't Matter
You're Here And...
Happy To See You Setting Me Off Like Sparks
You Ignite All The Colours Inside My Heart
On The Doorstep Like We'd Never Been Apart
Hope You Know That I'm Happy To See You
Happy To See You Setting Me Off Like Sparks
You Ignite All The Colours Inside My Heart
On The Doorstep Like We'd Never Been Apart
Hope You Know That I'm Happy To See You