It's so hypnotic
The way he pulls on me
It's like the force of gravity
Right up under my feet
It's so erotic
This feeling can't be beat
It's coursing through my whole body
Feel the heat
I got that burnin' hot desi-i-i-re
And no one can put out my fi-i-i-re
It's coming right down through the wi-i-i-re
Here it comes
When I hear them 808 drums
It's got me singing
Hey, ey, ey, ey
Ey, ey, ey
Like a girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
I'm like, hey, ey, ey, ey
Ey, ey, ey
Like a girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
Girls they just wanna have some fun
Get fired up like smokin' gun
On the floor til the daylight comes
Girls they just wanna have some fun
A girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
I'm like a girl gone wild
The room is spinning
It must be the tanqueray
I'm about to go astray
My inhibition's gone away
I feel like sinning
You got me in the zone
DJ play my favorite song
Turn me on
I got that burnin' hot desi-i-i-re
And no one can put out my fi-i-i-re
It's coming right down through the wi-i-i-re
Here it comes
When I hear them 808 drums
It's got me singing
Hey, ey, ey, ey
Ey, ey, ey
Like a girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
I'm like, hey, ey, ey, ey
Ey, ey, ey
Like a girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
Girls they just wanna have some fun
Get fired up like smokin' gun
On the floor til the daylight comes
Girls they just wanna have some fun
I know, I know, I know
I shouldn't act this way
Good girls don't misbehave
Misbehave
But i'm a bad girl, anyway
Forgive me
Hey, ey, ey, ey
Ey, ey, ey
Like a girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
I'm like, hey, ey, ey, ey
Ey, ey, ey
Like a girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
Girls they just wanna have some fun
Get fired up like smokin' gun
On the floor til the daylight comes
Girls they just wanna have some fun
A girl gone wild
A good girl gone wild
I'm like a girl gone wild