Days like this I want to drive away
Pack my bags and watch your shadow fade
You chewed me up and spit me out,
Like I was poison in your mouth
You took my light, you drink me down
That was then and this is now
Now look at me !
This is the part of me
That you're never gonna ever take away from me, no
Throw sticks and these stones. Throw your bombs and glows
But you're not gonna break my soul
This is the part of me
That you're never gonna ever take away from me, no
I just wanna throw my phone away
Find out who is really there for me
You ripped me off, your love was cheap,
It's always tearing at the seams,
I fell deep and you let me down,
But that was then and this is now
Now look at me !
This is the part of me
That you're never gonna ever take away from me, no
Throw sticks and these stones. Throw your bombs and glows
But you're not gonna break my soul
This is the part of me
That you're never gonna ever take away from me, no
And look at me, I'm sparkling
A firework, a dancing flame
You won't ever put me out again
I'm glowing ohohoh
So you can keep the diamond ring
It don't mean nothing anyway
In fact you can keep everything
Yeah, yeah
Except for me
This is the part of me
That you're never gonna ever take away from me, no
Throw sticks and these stones. Throw your bombs and glows
But you're not gonna break my soul
This is the part of me
That you're never gonna ever take away from me, no
This is the part of me, no, (away from me)
This is the part of me
This is the part of me, me, me, me, me, me, no
Throw sticks and these stones. Throw your bombs and glows
But you're not gonna break my soul
This is the part of me
That you're never gonna ever take away from me, no