You got a girl
That doesn’t look a thing like me
The girl, your mother always said it would be
So, you could say that, you could say that
I’m hopeless
But that ain’t the girl
That ain’t the girl I want you to be
The girl that keeps up
And I see in my dreams
So, you could say that, you could say that
I love her
So I don’t care what they say
It’s our life life life
We can dance if we want
Make it feel alright
Temperature’s rising
I feel the fire
Tonight, it’s just me and you
Tell me baby, will you be here when I wake up
Even with no make up
I don’t want to fake it
And you don’t gotta doubt a second if I miss you
Everytime I’m with you
I feel naked
Hey! I feel naked, I want it
so let me get it, you say you got it, won’t you come to get it
If I told you girl
Come and run away with me
Now will you throw it all away for me
I need to know that, need to know that
It’s not over
Cause you were the boy
Daddy told you to stay away from me
But you’re nothing but a fantasy
I need to know that, need to know that
You’d be strong enough to believe in us
Cause I don’t care what they say
It’s our life life life
We can dance if we want
Make it feel alright
Temperature’s rising
I feel the fire
Tonight, it’s just me and you
Tell me baby, will you be here when I wake up
I feel naked
Hey! I feel naked, I want it
so let me get it, you say you got it, it’s The Cataracs
I feel naked, I want it, so let me get it
you say you got it, won’t you come to get it