Shinee's back
Shinee's back, back, back, back, back
from now on, it's all stop
it don't matter who you are
you're trapped here, can't escape, and you can't leave
keep your wits about
ya know this scene's so obvious
I found that secret room and
I've never felt so free
no way
I won't miss the way your breath keeps trembling in the night
I been aimin' at the jewel within your heart
the way
that I feel your eyes keep moving all throughout the night
I found you up on the dragon's board and I
Freeze
you look at me, with such innocence so you
can shatter me, you're just waiting for the chance
two alibis (two alibis)
will explode tonight like fireworks baby
Oh I'm curious, yeah
you're smilin' at me
from that frame you're in, oh, why, oh
I'm so curious yeah, yeah
oh I'm so curious yeah
think about ya hundred times over
and I'm tryin' to do my best to forget
and I ask myself a hundred times over
what the hell is it you're tryin' to get
I feel how it flows
and in my heart without a sound I won't forget
feelin' it spin now
oh I'm curious yeah
you're walkin' towards me
from that frame you're in oh, why, oh
I'm so curious yeah, yeah oh
I'm so curious yeah
as of now you don't, don't exist to me but I'm not
gonna give it up, I'm a find you out for sure
'cause I know you
have the answers that I wanted
from your lips they
they shine and, ~*disappear*~
maybe you know exactly how I feel within my heart it's real
and from the start it was never locked away from you
you know it's true
I know that the suspect's in here
can't nobody leave while I'm here
we ain't goin' anywhere - no
I know everything about ya
found the evidence about ya
rest assured that I'm a find - you (blow up baby!)
Oh I'm curious yeah
you're walkin' towards me
from that frame you're in, oh, why, oh
I'm so curious yeah, yeah oh
I'm so curious yeah
tonight, SHINee's in the house
so give it up, give it up, give it up for, SHINee
give it up, give it up, give it up for SHINee
what song are we singing? ...okay
lololol
take that Minho breath
choked on my sulliva
do I look like Minho when I do this?
SHINee's back
he's awesome