Everybody
see's it's you
I'm the one
that lost the view
Everybody says
we're through
I hope you
hadn't said it too
So where do
we go from here?
With all this
fear in our eyes
And where can
love take us now?
We've been
so far down
We can still
touch the sky
If we crawl,
Till we can walk again
Then we'll run
Until we're
strong enough to jump
Then we'll fly
Until there is no wind
So let's crawl,
crawl
Back to love,
Why did
I change the pace?
Hearts were never
meant to race
I always felt
the need for space
But now
I can't reach your face
So where are
you standing now?
Are you in the
crowd of my vouch?
Love,
can you see my hand?
I need one
more chance
We can still
have it all
So we'll crawl,
Till we can
walk again
Then we'll run,
Until we're strong
enough to jump
Then we'll fly
until there is no wind
So let's crawl,
crawl
Back to love,
Everybody see's
it's you
Well I never wanna
lose that view
So we'll crawl,
if we crawl
Till we can
walk again
Then we'll run,
we'll run
Until we're strong
enough to jump
Then we'll fly,
Until there is no wind
So let's crawl,
crawl
So we'll crawl,
Till we can walk again,
Then we'll run,
we'll run
Until we're strong
enough to jump
Then we'll fly,
Until there is no wind
So let's crawl,
let's crawl,
Back to love