There are times
When I just want to look
At your face
With the stars in the night
There are times
When I just want to feel
Your embrace
In the cold night
I just can't believe
That you are mine now
You were just a dream
That I once knew
I never thought
I would be right for you
I just can't compare you with
Anything in this world
You're all I need
To be here with forevermore
All those years
I longed to hold you in my arms
I've been dreamin' of you
Every night
I've been watching all the stars
That fall down
Wishing you will be mine
I just can't believe
That you are mine now
You were just a dream
That I once knew
I never thought
I would be right for you
I just can't compare you with
Anything in this world
You're all I need
To be here with forevermore
Time and again
There are these changes
That we cannot end
As sure as the time
Keeps going on and on
My love for you
Will be forevermore
Oh
Yeah
I just can't believe
That you are mine now
You were just a dream
That I once knew
I never thought
I would be right for you
I just can't compare you with
Anything in this world
As endless as forever
Our love will stay together
You are all I need
To be here with forevermore
Forevermore
You're all I need
To be here with forevermore
Yeah