The day I first met you
You told me you'd never fall in love
But now that I get you
I know fear is what it really was
Now here we are, so close, yet so far
Haven't I passed the test?
When will you realize?
Baby i'm not like the rest
Don't wanna break your heart
Wanna give your heart a break
I know you're scared it's wrong
Like you might make a mistake
There's just one life to live
And there's no time to waste (to waste)
So let me give your heart a break, your heart a break
Let me give your heart a break , your heart a break
oh yeah yeah
On Sunday, you went home alone,
There were tears in your eyes,
I called your cell phone, my love,
But you did not reply
The world is ours if we want it,
We can take it, if you just take my hand,
There's no turning back now
Baby try to understand
Don't wanna break your heart
Wanna give your heart a break
I know you're scared it's wrong
Like you might make a mistake
There's just one life to live
And there's no time to waste (to waste)
So let me give your heart a break, your heart a break,
Let me give your heart a break , your heart a break
There's just so much you can take, give your heart a break
Let me give your heart a break, your heart a break
(oh yeah yeah)
When your lips are on my lips
and our hearts beat as one,
But you slip out of my finger tips
Everytime you run
Don't wanna break your heart,
Wanna give your heart a break,
I know you're scared it's wrong,
Like you might make a mistake
There's just one life to live,
And there's no time to waste (to waste)
So let me give your heart a break,
'cause you've been hurt before,
I can see it in your eyes
You try to smile it away,
Some things you can't disguise
Don't wanna break your heart, maybe I can ease the ache (the ache)
So let me give your heart a break,give your heart a break,
Let me give your heart a break, give your heart a break,
There's just so much you can take, give your heart a break,
Let me give your heart a break, give your heart a break
(oh yeah yeah)
The day I first met you
You told me you'd never fall in love