I gotta find my way back
Back to summer paradise
Sean Paul, Simple Plan
My heart is sinking
As I'm lifting up
Above the clouds away from you
And I can't believe I'm leaving
Oh I don't kno-kno-know what I'm gonna do
But someday
I will find my way back
To where your name
Is written in the sand
Cause I remember every sunset
I remember every word you said
We were never gonna say goodbye
Singing la-la-ta-ta-ta
Tell me how to get back to
Back to summer paradise with you
And I'll be there in a heartbeat (heartbeat)
Oh-oh
I'll be there in a heartbeat (heartbeat)
(Tell 'em)
My soul is broken
Streets are frozen
I can't stop these feelings melting through
And I'd give away a thousand days, oh
Just to have another one with you
(What'd you say)
Where real life can wait
(It can wait)
We're crashing my waves
(Uh-huh)
Playing in the sand
(Me and you)
Holding your hand
(Yeah, yeah, yeah)
Cause I remember every sunset (I remember)
I remember every word you said
We were never gonna say goodbye
Singing la-la-ta-ta-ta
Tell me how to get back to
Back to summer paradise with you
And I'll be there in a heartbeat (heartbeat)
Oh-oh
I'll be there in a heartbeat (heartbeat)
Someday
I will find my way back
To where your name
Is written in the sand
Yeah, yeah, yeah, let's go
Cause I remember every sunset (I remember)
I remember every word you said
We were never gonna say goodbye (no, no, no)
Singing la-la-ta-ta-ta
Tell me how to get back to (back to)
Back to summer paradise with you
And I'll be there in a heartbeat
I remember where we first kissed (I remember)
How I didn't wanna leave your lips
And how I've never ever felt so high (so high)
Singing la-la-ta-ta-ta
So tell me how to get back to (back to)
Back to summer paradise with you
And I'll be there in a heartbeat (heartbeat)
Oh-oh
I'll be there in a heartbeat
(Summer paradise) Oh-oh