Dance, yes (RedOne)
Love, next
Dance, yes (J.Lo)
Shimmy Shimmy yah, Shimmer yam
Shimmer yay
I'm a old dirty dog all day
No way Jose
Your girl only go one way, ay mi madre
You should check that out
Maybe you ain't turn her out
Maybe it's none of my business
But for now work it out
Let's get this, dale
Nobody knows what i'm feeling inside
I find it so stupid
So why should I hide
That I love to make love to you baby
(yeah make love to me)
So many ways wanna touch you tonight
I'm a big girl got no secrets this time
Yeah I love to make love to you baby
(yeah make love to me)
If this would be a perfect world
We'd be together then
(let's do it do it do it)
Only got just one life this i've learned
Who cares what they're gonna say
(let's do it do it do it)
I wanna dance, and love, and dance again
Dance, yes
Love, next
Baby your fire is lighting me up
The way that you move boy is reason enough
That I love to make love to you baby
(yeah make love to me)
I can't behave
Oh I want you so much
Your lips taste like heaven
So why should I stop?
Yeah I love to make love to you baby
(yeah make love to me)
If this would be a perfect world
We'd be together then
(let's do it do it do it)
Only got just one life this i've learned
Who cares what they're gonna say
(let's do it do it do it)
I wanna dance, and love, and dance again
Mr Worldwide, and the world's most beautiful woman
Modern day hugh hed (uh, yes)
Playboy to the death (uh, yes)
Is he really worldwide? (uh, yes)
Mami let me open your treasure chest
Play dates, we play mates
I'm the king snatching queens, checkmate
What you think?
It's a rumor
I'm really out of this world
Moon, luna
Make woman comfortable
Call me bloomer
Can't even show love cause they'll sue ya
But I told them, 'hallelujah, have a blessed day'
So ahead of myself
Everyday's yesterday
Want the recipe? it's real simple
Little bit of vole, and she'll open sesame
Now dance yes
Love next
Dance yes
If this would be a perfect world
We'd be together then
(let's do it do it do it)
Only got just one life this i've learned
Who cares what they're gonna say
(let's do it do it do it)
I wanna dance, and love, and dance again