In the blink of an eye
I was falling from the sky
In the blur, you took my breath away
And my heart starts beating
And my lungs start breathing
And the voice in my head starts screaming
I’m alive
You’re like a laserlight
Burning down, burning down on me
You make me feel good, you make me feel safe
You make me feel like I can live another day
You know I wouldn’t have it any other way
D-D-D-David G
Je-Je-Je-Jessie J
You and me, face to face
And there’s so much I could say
And these words, have forever seen the silence
Can you hear that box b-b-breaking
And the world starts sha-sha-shaking
They keep talking, talking, talking
But we’re walking, walking
To the light tonight, tonight
You’re like a laserlight
Burning down, burning down on me
You make me feel good, you make me feel safe
You make me feel like I can live another day
You know I wouldn’t have it any other way
Have it any other way
There’s no stop, stop, stop
Oh oh Oh
I won’ stop stop, stop
We won’t stop, stop, stop
In the blink of an eye
I was falling from the sky
In the blur, you took my breath away