I thought it would be easy,
but it ain’t for me
It’s kinda hard, when you lay
your heart on a one way street
I really thought by now
You would’ve slipped my mind
But the kind of love sent from
above is a killing kind
Put my mind to rest
and try to sleep it off
It will be alright when
the morning comes
Or ever run
Ain’t no doubt about it
I can’t live without it
Tried to forget you
But I can’t get you
outta my head
Just when I think you’re gone
You come back and turn it on
And just like a simple song
I can’t get you outta my head
Well I saw you dancing,
dancing in my dreams
I saw your face and
I cant erase all the things I see
Even if I try, Cause Lord knows I tried
I can’t escape and I can’t shake
the pain inside, oh
Crazy wind, She comes
so crazy as she goes
I’m holding out my hands
with nothing left to show
I guess its the way it goes
Ain’t no doubt about it
I can’t live without it
Tried to forget you
But I can’t get you
outta my head
Just when I think you’re gone
You come back and turn it on
And just like a simple song
I Can’t get you outta my head
Can’t get you outta my head
Crazy wind, She comes
so crazy as she goes
I’m holding out my hands
with nothing left to show
Guess thats the way it goes
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Can’t get you outta my head
Can’t get you, can’t get you, oh
Ain’t no doubt about it
I can’t live without it
Tried to forget you
But I can’t get you
outta my head
Just when I think you’re gone
You come back and turn it on
And just like a simple song
Can’t get you outta my head