I never gone with the wind
Just let it flow
Let it take me where it wants to go
Till you open the door
There's so much more
I've never seen it before
I was trying to fly but I couldn't find wings
You came along and you changed everything
You lift my feet off the ground
You spin me around
You make me crazier, crazier
Feels like I'm falling and I,
I'm lost in your eyes
You make me crazier, crazier, crazier
I watched from a distance as you
Made life your own
Every sky was your own kind of blue
And I wanted to know how
That would feel
And you made it so real
You showed me something that I couldn't see
You opened my eyes and you made me believe
You lift my feet off the ground
You spin me around
You make me crazier, crazier
Feels like I'm falling and I,
I'm lost in your eyes
You make me crazier, crazier, crazier
Baby you showed me what living is for
I don't want to hide anymore
You lift my feet off the ground
You spin me around
You make me crazier, crazier
Feels like I'm falling and I,
I'm lost in your eyes
You make me crazier, crazier, crazier
Crazier