Once upon a time, we were burning bright
Now all we ever seem to do is fight
On and on, and on and on and on
Once upon a time, on the same side
In the same game
And why'd you have to go
Have to go and throw out all of my things
I could've been the princess
You'd be a king
I could have had a castle
And worn a ring
And go
You let me go
I could've been the princess
You'd be a king
I could have had a castle
And worn a ring
But no
You let me go
You stole my star
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la
Whoa, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh
Cause she really hurt me
No, you really hurt me
Cause she really hurt me, oh
You really hurt me, oh
You really hurt me